cding O
@ O

Syracuse B-ORG
University E-ORG

<b> O
Teo B-PER
Mora E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
( O
Editor ROLE
in I-ROLE
Chief E-ROLE
) O

Via B-ORG
Dodecaneso E-ORG

daniel O
@ O

</b> O
Depto O
. O
de B-PER
Matemáticas E-PER
, O
Estadística S-ORG
y O

michele.elia O
@ O

University O
of O
Buenos B-LOC
Aires E-LOC
, O
Argentina S-LOC

<b> O
Grégoire B-PER
Lecerf E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Innsbruck E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

</b> O
Laboratoire B-ORG
d’Informatique I-ORG
de I-ORG
l’École I-ORG
Polytechnique E-ORG
( O
LIX O

<b> O
Jörn B-PER
Müller-Quade E-PER

david.pointcheval O
@ O

singer O
@ O

</div> O

<b> O
Bernd B-PER
Finkbeiner E-PER
</b> O
, O
Universität B-PER
des I-PER
Saarlandes E-PER
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Monika B-PER
Henzinger E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Vienna E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE

<b> O
Valentin B-PER
E. I-PER
Brimkov E-PER
</b> O
( O
SUNY B-LOC
Buffalo I-LOC
State E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Lev B-PER
Reyzin E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Illinois E-ORG
at O
Chicago S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Sarne E-PER
</b> O
( O
Bar-Ilan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Guillermo B-PER
R. I-PER
Simari E-PER
</b> O
( O
Universidad B-LOC
Nacional I-LOC
del I-LOC
Sur E-LOC
, O
Bahia B-LOC
Blanca E-LOC
, O
Argentina S-LOC

<b> O
György B-PER
Turan E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Illinois E-ORG
at O
Chicago S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Elizabeth B-PER
Yakel E-PER

Review BI-ROLE
Editor ROLE
: O
<b> O
Kathleen B-PER
Richardson E-PER

email O
: O
kathleen.richardson O
@ O

email O
: O
LarryStapleton O
@ O

email O
: O
amystapleton89 O
@ O

<b> O
Kevin B-PER
Warwick E-PER
, O
</b> O
Coventry B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Luciano B-PER
Floridi E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford I-ORG
and I-ORG
The I-ORG
Alan I-ORG
Turing I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
London S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
José-Carlos B-PER
Mariátegui E-PER
, O
</b> O
Alta B-ORG
Tecnología I-ORG
Andina E-ORG
- O
ATA S-ORG
, O
Peru S-LOC

<b> O
Susanne B-PER
Albers E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Humboldt-Universität B-ORG
zu I-ORG
Berlin E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Mohammad B-PER
Hajiaghayi E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maryland E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</div> O

<i> O
Danièle B-PER
Bourcier E-PER
</i> O
, O
CNRS-Université O
, O
Paris S-LOC
2 O
, O
France S-LOC

<i> O
Monica B-PER
Palmirani E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
( O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Law E-ORG
- O
CIRSFID O
) O
, O
Italy S-LOC

<i> O
Hajime B-PER
Yoshino E-PER
</i> O
, O
Meiji B-ORG
Gakuin I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Fumitoshi B-PER
Matsuno E-PER
, O
Kyoto S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Toshio B-PER
Fukuda E-PER
, O
Nagoya S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Jeffery B-PER
H. I-PER
Johnson E-PER
, O
Milton B-LOC
Keynes E-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

Ryohei B-PER
Nakatsu E-PER
, O
Hyogo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Stephen B-PER
Cranefield E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Otago E-ORG
, O
NEW B-LOC
ZEALAND E-LOC

<b> O
Sarit B-PER
Kraus E-PER
</b> O
, O
Bar-Ilan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
ISRAEL S-LOC

<b> O
Sebastian B-PER
Sardina E-PER
, O
</b> O
RMIT O
, O
AUSTRALIA S-LOC

<b> O
Elizabeth B-PER
Sklar E-PER
</b> O
, O
King B-ORG
's I-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Wiebe B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Hoek E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Michael B-PER
Wooldridge E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Stephanie B-PER
Gil E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Harvard B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Cynthia B-PER
Breazeal E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Massachusetts B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Robert B-PER
Fitch E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Dario B-PER
Floreano E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Swiss B-ORG
Federal I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
Vaughan E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Simon B-PER
Fraser E-PER
University O
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Paolo B-PER
Fiorini E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Verona E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Masahiro B-PER
Fujita E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Sony B-ORG
Corporation E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Oussama B-PER
Khatib E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Daniela B-PER
Rus E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Massachusetts B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Charles B-PER
Thorpe E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Swagatam B-PER
Das E-PER

</b> O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
Wien E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

</b> O
National B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Council E-ROLE
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Khan B-PER
Iftekharuddin E-PER

</b> O
Texas B-ORG
A I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
M I-ORG
University E-ORG
at O
Qatar S-LOC
, O
Qatar S-LOC

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Zanjan E-ORG
, O
Iran S-LOC

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kent E-ORG
, O
Canterbury S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Fei-Yue B-PER
Wang E-PER

</div> O

Thomas B-PER
Sterling E-PER
, O
Indiana B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Pavan B-PER
Balaji E-PER
, O
Argonne B-ORG
National I-ORG
Laboratory E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Bingsheng B-PER
He E-PER
, O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

Hong B-PER
Shen E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Adelaide E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Studies E-ORG
( O
ITS S-ORG

Jianhua B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Oslo B-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

<b> O
Book B-ROLE
Review BI-ROLE
Committee E-ROLE

</b> O
Henning B-PER
Boje I-PER
Andersen E-PER
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Klaus B-PER
Bengler E-PER
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Munich E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Oliver B-PER
Carsten E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leeds E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Jianping B-PER
Wu E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Dah B-PER
Ming I-PER
Chiu E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Serge B-PER
Fdida E-PER
, O
Pierre S-PER
and O
Marie B-PER
Curie E-PER
University O
, O
France S-LOC

Xiaoming B-PER
Fu E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Göttingen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Xiaowei B-PER
Yang E-PER
, O
Duke B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Paul S-PER
</b> O
<b> O
Dourish S-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Chengzheng B-PER
Sun E-PER
, O
</b> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

<b> O
Schahram B-PER
Dustdar E-PER
</b> O
, O
TU B-PER
Wien E-PER

<b> O
Elias B-PER
P. I-PER
Duarte E-PER
Jr O
. O
</b> O
, O
Federal B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Paraná E-ORG

<b> O
Miguel B-PER
Gonzalez-Mendoza E-PER
</b> O
, O
Tecnologico B-ORG
de I-ORG
Monterrey E-ORG

<b> O
Kewei B-PER
Sha E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Houston-Clear B-LOC
Lake E-LOC
, O
TX S-LOC

<b> O
Uwe B-PER
Zdun E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Vienna E-ORG


E-mail O
: O
sv.raghavan O
@ O

<b> O
Editors‐in‐Chief O
: O

Prof. O
R B-PER
Balasubramanian E-PER

Amrita B-ORG
Vishwa I-ORG
Vidyapeetham I-ORG
University E-ORG

Prof. O
Abhay B-PER
Karandikar E-PER

E-mail O
: O
karandi O
@ O

E-mail O
: O
prashant O
@ O

Dr. O
Ramesh B-PER
Hariharan E-PER

Prof. O
Shekhar B-PER
Verma E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Melbourne E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Advisory BI-ROLE
Council E-ROLE

Dr. O
R. B-PER
Chidambaram E-PER

Vice‐Chairman O
, O
Tata B-ORG
Consultancy I-ORG
Services E-ORG
( O
TCS S-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bergen E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

AT B-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
T B-ORG
Shannon I-ORG
Lab E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Chunming B-PER
Tang E-PER

Southwest B-ORG
Jiaotong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Xiangyong B-PER
Zeng E-PER

<b> O
APPLICATIONS O
EDITOR ROLE

<b> O
Jean-Charles B-PER
Regin E-PER
</b> O
, O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Nice-Sophia I-ORG
Antipolis E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Stephen B-PER
F. I-PER
Smith E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Markus B-PER
Koskela E-PER
, O
CSC-IT B-ORG
Center I-ORG
for I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
FINLAND S-LOC

Jinsong B-PER
Leng E-PER
, O
Edith B-ORG
Cowan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
AUSTRALIA S-LOC

Eduardo B-PER
F. I-PER
Morales E-PER
, O
INAOE S-ORG
, O
MEXICO S-LOC

Frank B-PER
Puppe E-PER
, O
Würzburg B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
GERMANY S-LOC

Andrzej B-PER
Skowron E-PER
, O
Warsaw B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
POLAND S-LOC

<b> O
Review BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

</i> O
Johannes B-PER
Fürnkranz E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Johannes B-ORG
Kepler I-ORG
University I-ORG
Linz E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Heikki B-PER
Mannila E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Helsinki B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Geoff B-PER
Webb E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Monash B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Kristian B-PER
Kersting E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
TU B-ORG
Darmstadt E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jan B-PER
Ramon E-PER
, O
<i> O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
INRIA B-ORG
Lille I-ORG
Nord I-ORG
Europe E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Myra B-PER
Spiliopoulou E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Otto-von-Guericke B-ORG
University I-ORG
Magdeburg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Anthony B-PER
Bagnall E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
East I-ORG
Anglia E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
Hendrik B-PER
Blockeel E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Katholieke B-ORG
Universiteit I-ORG
Leuven E-ORG
, O
Belgium S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Mario B-PER
Boley E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Monash B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Tom B-PER
Fawcett E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Silicon B-ORG
Valley I-ORG
Data I-ORG
Science I-ORG
LLC E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Eibe B-PER
Frank E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waikato E-ORG
, O
Hamilton S-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

<b> O
Jaako B-PER
Hollmén E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Aalto B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Bing B-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Illinois E-ORG
, O
Chicago S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Katharina B-PER
Morik E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
Dortmund E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Matteo B-PER
Riondato E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Amherst B-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Marko B-PER
Robnik-Sikonja E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Ljubljana E-ORG
, O
Slovenia S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Arno B-PER
Siebes E-PER
, O
<i> O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Universiteit B-ORG
Utrecht E-ORG
, O
Netherlands S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
P O
. O
Wild O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
M.J. B-PER
de I-PER
Resmini E-PER
</b> O
† O
( O
1939-2012 O
) O
, O
<i> O
Università B-ORG
di I-ORG
Roma E-ORG
" O
La B-ORG
Sapienza E-ORG
," O
Italy S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
S.A O
. O
Vanstone S-PER
</b> O
† O
( O
1947-2014 O
) O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
G O
. O
Korchmaros S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Basilicata E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Stéphane B-PER
Lafortune E-PER
, O
<i> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Necmiye B-PER
Ozay E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Advisory BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

Elisa B-PER
Bertino E-PER
, O
<i> O
Purdue B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Amit B-PER
Sheth E-PER
, O
<i> O
Wright B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Ashraf B-PER
Aboulnaga E-PER
, O
<i> O
Qatar B-ORG
Computing I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Qatar S-LOC

Sourav B-PER
Bhowmick E-PER
, O
<i> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

Khuzaima B-PER
Daudjee E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Wolfgang B-PER
Lehner E-PER
, O
<i> O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
Dresden E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Giuseppe B-PER
Polese E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Salerno E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Rui B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Melbourne E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Israel S-LOC

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Paris I-ORG
Diderot E-ORG
- O
Paris S-LOC
7 O
, O
France S-LOC

</div> O

</i> O
<b> O
Torsten B-PER
Brinda E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Duisburg-Essen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Joseph B-PER
Chao E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Bowling B-ORG
Green I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Johannes B-PER
Magenheim E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Paderborn E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Shah B-PER
Miah E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Newcastle B-ORG
Business I-ORG
School E-ORG
, O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Newcastle E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

</b> O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Lionel B-PER
C. I-PER
Briand E-PER

</i> O
<b> O
Andreas B-PER
Zeller E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Saarland B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Bram B-PER
Adams E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Polytechnique B-ORG
Montréal E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jeff B-PER
Carver E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Alabama E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Hadi B-PER
Hemmati E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Calgary E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Natalia B-PER
Juristo E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Universidad B-ORG
Politecnico I-ORG
de I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Yasutaka B-PER
Kamei E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Kyushu B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Andrian B-PER
Marcus E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Dallas S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Maurizio B-PER
Morisio E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
<b> O
, O
</b> O
Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Torino E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Denys B-PER
Poshyvanyk E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
College B-ORG
of I-ORG
William I-ORG
and I-ORG
Mary E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

FOUNDING B-ROLE
EDITORS ROLE

EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

INRIA B-ORG
EPI I-ORG
Gamma3 E-ORG
, O
Saclay B-ORG
Ile-de-France E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Sandia B-ORG
National I-ORG
Laboratory E-ORG
, O
Albuquerque S-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
Mexico E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Managing B-ROLE
Editor ROLE

</i> O
</b> O
<b> O
Lucas B-PER
D. I-PER
Introna E-PER

</i> O
<b> O
Don B-PER
Gotterbarn E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
East B-ORG
Tennessee I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
James B-PER
Moor E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Dartmouth B-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

LORIA S-ORG
, O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Lorraine E-ORG

</b> O
<b> O
Prof. O
E. B-PER
Boiten E-PER

email O
: O
eerke.boiten O
@ O

email O
: O
duke.j.david O
@ O

<b> O
Prof O
</b> O
<b> O
. O
D. B-PER
Kroening E-PER

email O
: O
Ursula.Martin O
@ O

( O
Computational O
logic O
; O
Applied O
formal O
methods O
; O
Computer O
algebra O

</b> O
Departmento B-ORG
de I-ORG
Informática E-ORG
/ O
HASLab O
, O
Universidade B-ORG
do I-ORG
Minho I-ORG
/ I-ORG
INESC I-ORG
TEC E-ORG
, O
4710-057 O
Braga S-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

email O
: O
wehrheim O
@ O

( O
Z O
, O
B O
, O
process O
algebras O
; O
Refinement O
; O
Simulation O
; O
Verification O
; O
Program O
analysis O
; O
Concurrency O
) O

<b> O
Samuel B-PER
L. I-PER
Manzello E-PER
, O
</b> O
National B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Standards I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Gaithersburg S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Panos B-PER
Kotsovinos E-PER
, O
</b> O
Arup S-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Adam B-PER
Krasuski E-PER
, O
</b> O
The O
Main B-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fire I-ORG
Service E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC

<b> O
M.Z O
. O
Naser S-PER
</b> O
, O
Clemson B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

High O
performance O
computing O
, O
computer O

Service O
computing O
, O
artificial O

Wireless O
networks O
and O
their O

Ahmed B-PER
Abou-Zeid E-PER

Semiconductor O

Min B-PER
Gu E-PER

RMIT B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia B-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Shanghai I-ORG
for I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Wei B-PER
Liu E-PER

Systems O
and O

Computer O
vision O
& O
amp O
; O

Himal B-PER
A. I-PER
Suraweera E-PER

Harbin B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Pu B-PER
Wang E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Brasilia E-ORG
, O
Brazil S-LOC

Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG
at O
Binghamton S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC
& O
amp O
; O
Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Mengchu B-PER
Zhou E-PER

Jifeng B-PER
HE I-PER
East I-PER
China I-PER
Normal I-PER
University E-PER
, O
China S-LOC

Jinpeng B-ORG
HUAI I-ORG
Beihang I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

Zhi-Hua B-ORG
ZHOU B-PER
Nanjing I-PER
University E-PER
, O
China S-LOC

Guihai B-PER
Chen I-PER
Nanjing I-PER
University E-PER
, O
China S-LOC

Dengguo B-ORG
FENG I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Software E-ORG
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Keqiu B-PER
LI I-PER
Tianjin I-PER
University E-PER
, O
China S-LOC


Wolfgang B-PER
Banzhaf E-PER
, O
<i> O
Michigan B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

John B-PER
Koza E-PER
, O
<i> O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Marc B-PER
Schoenauer E-PER
, O
<i> O
I.N.R.I.A O
. O
Futurs O
, O
France S-LOC

Sebastian B-PER
Risi E-PER
, O
<i> O
IT B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Copenhagen E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Hitoshi B-PER
Iba E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tokyo E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Una-May B-ORG
O'Reilly E-ORG
, O
<i> O
Massachusetts B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Stephen B-PER
Smith E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
York E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Leonardo B-PER
Vanneschi E-PER
, O
<i> O
ISEGI O
, O
Universidade B-ORG
Nova I-ORG
de I-ORG
Lisboa E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

A.I O
. O
Esparcia-Alcázar S-PER
, O
<i> O
Universitat B-ORG
Politècnica I-ORG
de I-ORG
València E-ORG
</i> O
, O
<i> O
Spain S-LOC

M.A O
. O
Azad S-PER
, O
<i> O
Birmingham B-ORG
City I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

M. B-PER
Castelli E-PER
, O
<i> O
Universidade B-ORG
Nova I-ORG
de I-ORG
Lisboa E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

K. B-PER
Deb E-PER
, O
<i> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

C. B-PER
Gagne E-PER
, O
<i> O
Laval B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

X.H O
. O
Nguyen O
, O
<i> O
Hanoi B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Vietnam S-LOC

M. B-PER
O'Neill E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
Dublin E-ORG
, O
Ireland S-LOC

</b> O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Centre I-ORG
for I-ORG
Geocomputation E-ORG
, O
NCG S-ORG
, O
Social B-ORG
Science I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Maynooth B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Ireland S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Action B-ROLE
Editors ROLE
: O

<b> O
Maria B-PER
Luisa I-PER
Damiani E-PER
, O
</b> O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-PER
Milano E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Goce B-PER
Trajcevski E-PER
, O
</b> O
Northwestern B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Sachio B-PER
Kubo E-PER
, O
</b> O
Keio B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Robert B-PER
Weibel E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich E-ORG
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

<b> O
Leif B-PER
Azzopardi E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Strathclyde E-ORG
, O
Glasgow S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
Alistair B-PER
Moffat E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Melbourne E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jian-Yun O
Nie O
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Montreal E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Nicola B-PER
Tonellotto E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pisa E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Rodney B-PER
Brooks E-PER

</i> O
Ioannis B-ORG
Gkioulekas E-ORG
, O
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG

</i> O
Rei B-PER
Kawakami E-PER
, O
<i> O
Tokyo B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

</i> O
Chen B-PER
Change I-PER
Loy E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG

</i> O
Akihiro B-PER
Sugimoto E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
National B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG

</i> O
Olga B-PER
Veksler E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Ontario E-ORG
</i> O
</b> O
<b> O

TU B-ORG
Hamburg-Harburg E-ORG
, O
FB S-LOC

Computer B-ORG
Science I-ORG
Department E-ORG

mambo O
@ O

<b> O
Xinyi B-PER
Huang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Fujian B-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Reihaneh B-PER
Safavi-Naini E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Calgary E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Angelos B-PER
Stavrou E-PER
</b> O
, O
George B-ORG
Mason I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Fairfax S-LOC
, O
VA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Norihisa B-PER
Doi E-PER
</b> O
, O
Chuo B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
John B-PER
McHugh E-PER
</b> O
, O
Dalhousie B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Halifax S-LOC
, O
NS S-LOC
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Guozhen B-PER
Xiao E-PER
</b> O
, O
Xidian B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Xian S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Ryan B-PER
Baker E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pennsylvania E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Winslow B-PER
Burleson E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Arizona E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Vania B-PER
Dimitrova E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leeds E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Sidney B-PER
D'Mello E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
Boulder E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Kaska B-PER
Porayska-Pomsta E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Roger B-PER
Azevedo E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Central I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Tiffany B-PER
Barnes E-PER
</b> O
, O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Tak-Wai B-PER
Chan E-PER
</b> O
, O
National B-ORG
Central I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

<b> O
Riichiro B-PER
Mizoguchi E-PER
</b> O
, O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Amy B-PER
Ogan E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Rebecca B-PER
Passonneau E-PER
</b> O
, O
Penn B-LOC
State E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</div> O

Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Software I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG

Terre B-LOC
Haute E-LOC
, O
IN I-ROLE

<b> O
Colin B-PER
J. I-PER
Neill E-PER

National B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Rourkela E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Jin B-PER
Song I-PER
Dong E-PER

<b> O
Mikael B-PER
Lindvall E-PER

</b> O
Fraunhofer B-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
MD S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Steve B-PER
Reeves E-PER

<b> O
Kevin B-PER
Ryan E-PER

<b> O
Jim B-PER
Woodcock E-PER

<b> O
Paul B-PER
Curto E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC
, O
TX S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Honghai B-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Portsmouth E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Garrett B-PER
Clayton E-PER
, O
Villanova B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Huaping B-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Haibin B-PER
Yu E-PER
, O
Shenyang B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Automation E-ORG
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Hirokazu B-PER
Akahane E-PER
, O
Chiba B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Tatsuru B-PER
Daimon E-PER
, O
Keio B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Shintaro B-PER
Ono E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tokyo E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Jian B-PER
Sun E-PER
, O
Tongji B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Toshio B-PER
Yoshii E-PER
, O
Ehime B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Hani B-PER
Mahmassani E-PER
, O
Northwestern B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Efstratios B-PER
Gallopoulos E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Patras E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Shlomit B-PER
S. I-PER
Pinter E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
IBM O
</i> O
<i> O
Research B-ORG
Laboratory E-ORG
, O
Haifa S-LOC
, O
Israel S-LOC

</div> O

</b> O
Columbia B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
Harvey E-PER

<b> O
Vincent B-PER
Oria E-PER

<b> O
Stefan B-PER
Rueger E-PER

</b> O
Lenovo S-PER

</b> O
Hella B-ORG
Aglaia I-ORG
Mobile I-ORG
Vision I-ORG
GmbH E-ORG
, O
Berlin S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

Bethlehem S-LOC
, O
PA S-LOC
18015 O
, O
USA S-LOC

50139 O
, O
Florence S-LOC
, O
Italy S-LOC

</b> O
University O
at O
Buffalo S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
</b> O
<b> O
Board E-ROLE
</b> O

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG

Sydney S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
A.R O
. O
Dengel S-PER

<b> O
U O
. O
Garain S-PER

India S-LOC

<b> O
V O
. O
Govindaraju S-PER

masa O
@ O

Sweden S-LOC

Germany S-LOC

<b> O
U O
. O

<b> O
Nabil B-PER
R. I-PER
Adam E-PER

erich.neuhold O
@ O

Texas B-ORG
A I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
M I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
CSDL S-ORG

ingo.frommholz O
@ O

D.H.A S-ORG
. O
, O
Lahore B-LOC
Cantt E-LOC

<b> O
Seamus B-PER
Ross E-PER

<b> O
Costantino B-PER
Thanos E-PER

<b> O
Maristella B-PER
Agosti E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Padua E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Bainbridge E-PER
, O
</b> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waikato E-ORG
, O
Hamilton S-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

<b> O
José B-PER
Borbinha E-PER
, O
</b> O
INESC-ID O
/ O
IST O
, O
Lisboa S-LOC
, O
Portugal S-LOC

<b> O
Edward B-PER
A. I-PER
Fox E-PER
, O
</b> O
Virginia B-ORG
Tech E-ORG
, O
Blacksburg S-LOC
, O
VA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Adam B-PER
Jatowt E-PER
</b> O
, O
Kyoto B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Ee-Peng B-PER
Lim E-PER
, O
</b> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

<b> O
Alfredo B-PER
Sanchez E-PER
, O
</b> O
Universidad B-LOC
de I-LOC
las I-LOC
Americas E-LOC
, O
Puebla S-LOC
, O
Mexico S-LOC

<b> O
Rudi B-PER
Schmiede E-PER
, O
</b> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Darmstadt E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Shigeo B-PER
Sugimoto E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Library I-ORG
and I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
Ibaraki S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Otto-Hahn-Str O
. O

44221 O
Dortmund S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

234 O
Nichols B-PER
Hall E-PER

Kansas B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG

</b> O
Fachbereich B-ORG
Informatik I-ORG
, I-ORG
Programming I-ORG
Systems E-ORG

<b> O
Jérôme B-PER
Hugues E-PER

<i> O
( O
Product O
Lines O
) O

<b> O
Ina B-PER
Schieferdecker E-PER

<i> O
( O
Testing O
) O

<i> O
( O
Process O
Algebra O
, O
Model O
Inference O
) O

Biplav B-ORG
Srivastava E-ORG
, O
AI B-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
South B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Columbia S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Ignacio B-PER
Rojas I-PER
Ruiz E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Granada E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Ruppa B-PER
K. I-PER
Thulasiram E-PER
, O
Department O
of O
Computer B-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Manitoba E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Silvio B-PER
Ghilardi E-PER
, O
</b> O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-PER
Milano E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Assia B-PER
Mahboubi E-PER
, O
</b> O
INRIA S-ORG
, O
LS2N S-LOC
, O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Nantes E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Aart B-PER
Middeldorp E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Innsbruck E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Michael B-PER
Norrish E-PER
</b> O
, O
CSIRO S-PER
, O
Kensington S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Natarajan B-PER
Shankar E-PER
, O
</b> O
SRI B-ORG
International E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tabriz E-ORG
, O
Iran S-LOC

Professor O
, O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

<b> O
Mohammad B-PER
Ghanbari E-PER

Professor O
, O
Computer B-ORG
Engineering I-ORG
and I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Department E-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
Irvine S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Juris B-PER
Borzovs E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Cruz I-LOC
do I-LOC
Sul E-LOC
, O
Brazil S-LOC

Middle B-LOC
East E-LOC
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Northern B-LOC
Cyprus I-LOC
Campus E-LOC
, O
Turkey S-LOC

Aston B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Birmingham S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Mir B-PER
Kamal I-PER
Mirnia E-PER

<b> O
Ali B-PER
Kujoory E-PER

Sharif B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Tehran S-LOC
, O
Iran S-LOC

<b> O
Mohammad B-PER
Mahdian E-PER

<b> O
Mario B-PER
Pavone E-PER

<b> O
Xin-She B-PER
Yang E-PER

Chung-Laung B-ORG
( I-ORG
Dave I-ORG
) I-ORG
Liu E-PER
<<I-ORG> O
i O
<I-ORG>> I-ORG
Tsinghua I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hsinchu B-ORG
</<I-ORG> O
i O

<b> O
Executive B-ROLE
Editors ROLE

Xiaofang B-PER
Zhou E-PER
( O
Data B-ORG
Management I-ORG
and I-ORG
Data I-ORG
Mining E-ORG
) O
<i> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Queensland E-ORG
, O
Brisbane S-LOC

Xi-Lin B-ORG
Chen E-PER
<i> O
ICT O
, O
CAS O
, O
Beijing S-LOC

Xin B-PER
Yao E-PER
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Birmingham E-ORG
, O
Birmingham S-LOC

Chang-Shui B-PER
Zhang E-PER
<i> O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC

Cheng-Qing B-ORG
Zong E-ORG
<i> O
Ins O
. O
Automation O
, O
CAS O
, O
Beijing S-LOC

Chen B-PER
Ding E-PER
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Rochester E-ORG
, O
Rochester S-LOC

Qun-Sheng B-ORG
Peng E-PER
<<I-ORG> O
i O
<I-ORG>> I-ORG
Zhejiang I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hangzhou S-LOC

Qi B-PER
Tian E-PER
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
San B-LOC
Antonio E-LOC
, O
San B-LOC
Antonio E-LOC

Min-Yi B-PER
Guo E-PER
<i> O
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Shanghai S-LOC

Jian B-PER
Pei E-PER
<i> O
Simon B-ORG
Fraser I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Burnaby S-LOC

Shing-Chi B-PER
Cheung E-PER
<i> O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
Univ. O
Sci. O
Technol O
. O
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

Xue-Jia B-PER
Lai E-PER
<i> O
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Shanghai S-LOC

Qiu-Lei B-PER
Dong E-PER
<i> O
Ins O
. O
Automation O
, O
CAS O
, O
Beijing S-LOC

Jin B-PER
Li E-PER
<i> O
Guangzhou B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Guangzhou S-LOC

Xuan-Zhe B-PER
Liu E-PER
<i> O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC

Fa B-PER
Zhang E-PER
<<I-ORG> O
i O
<I-ORG>> I-ORG
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computing I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
CAS S-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC

<b> O
Roy B-PER
C E-PER
. O
PARK O
, O
</b> O
Dongseo B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
South B-LOC
Korea E-LOC

<b> O
Julian B-PER
RRUSHI E-PER
, O
</b> O
Oakland B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

koc O
@ O

<b> O
Çetin B-PER
Kaya I-PER
Koç E-PER

<b> O
Ricardo B-PER
Dahab E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Campinas E-ORG
, O
Brazil S-LOC

<b> O
Peter B-PER
Schwabe E-PER
, O
</b> O
Radboud B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

NTT B-ORG
Laboratories E-ORG

Aarhus B-ORG
Universitet E-ORG

Germany S-LOC

Japan S-LOC

USA S-LOC

kaisa.nyberg O
@ O

Clifton S-LOC
BS8 O

<b> O
Alon B-PER
Rosen E-PER

Efi B-ORG
Arazi I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

<b> O
Edward B-PER
Ip E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Wake B-ORG
Forest I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Medicine E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jiming B-PER
Liu E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

<b> O
Yuan B-PER
Luo E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Northwestern B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Yin-Leng B-PER
Theng E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

<b> O
Chih-Ping B-PER
Wei E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Taiwan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

Founding B-ROLE
Editor ROLE

</i> O
<b> O
Remco B-ORG
Duits E-ORG
, O
</b> O
<i> O
TU B-ORG
Eindhoven E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Lewis B-PER
Griffin E-PER
, O
<i> O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
UC B-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Fredrik B-PER
Kahl E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Chalmers B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Victor B-PER
Lempitsky E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Skoltech O
, O
Russia S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Serena B-PER
Morigi E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
Christian B-PER
Ronse E-PER
, O
<i> O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Université B-ORG
Louis I-ORG
Pasteur E-ORG
, O
Strasbourg S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

</div> O

</i> O
<b> O
Rada B-PER
Hussein E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Information B-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Ministry B-ORG
of I-ORG
Communications I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Giza S-LOC
, O
Egypt S-LOC

<b> O
Hojjat B-PER
Adeli E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Ohio B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Columbus S-LOC
, O
OH S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Maurice B-PER
Margenstern E-PER
</b> O
, O
Metz B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Thomas B-PER
Hinze E-PER
</b> O
, O
Friedrich B-PER
Schiller I-PER
University I-ORG
Jena E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Taishin B-PER
Y. I-PER
Nishida E-PER
</b> O
, O
Toyama B-ORG
Prefectural I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Nasser B-PER
Kehtarnavaz E-PER

<b> O
A O
. O
Nunez S-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Las I-LOC
Palmas I-LOC
Gran I-LOC
Canaria E-LOC
, O
Spain S-LOC

</div> O

<b> O
Metin B-PER
Feridun E-PER
, O
</b> O
Armasuisse S-LOC
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

<b> O
Gregorio B-PER
Martinez E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Murcia E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Kohei B-PER
Shiomoto E-PER
, O
</b> O
Tokyo B-ORG
City I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Anna B-PER
Sperotto E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Twente E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<b> O
TK B-PER
Srinivas E-PER
, O
</b> O
Niksun O
, O
Princeton S-LOC
, O
NJ S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Burkhard B-PER
Stiller E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Zürich E-ORG
and O
ETH S-LOC
, O
Zürich S-LOC
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

<b> O
Co-Editor-in-Chief O
: O

Tampere B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Nitin B-PER
Chandrachoodan E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Madras S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jen-Tzung B-PER
Chien E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Chiao I-ORG
Tung I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Yun B-PER
He E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Branislav B-PER
Kisacanin E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Interphase O
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Amos B-PER
R. I-PER
Omondi E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
SUNY B-LOC
Korea E-LOC
, O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
Korea E-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
An-Yeu O
Wu E-PER
<i> O
, O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Taiwan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Tong B-PER
Zhang E-PER
<i> O
, O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Rensselaer B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE

</b> O
Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
High I-ORG
Performance I-ORG
Computing I-ORG
and I-ORG
Networking E-ORG

Email O
: O
antonio.coronato O
@ O

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Essex E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

Mohammed B-PER
Alani E-PER

Ch O
. O
Charan B-PER
Singh E-PER
University O
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
George B-PER
C. I-PER
Polyzos E-PER

Athens B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Economics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Business E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

<b> O
Alexei B-PER
Sharpanskykh E-PER

<b> O
Manuel B-PER
Wimmer E-PER

Elisabeth B-PER
André E-PER
, O
Univ B-ORG
Augsburg E-ORG
, O

Christian B-PER
Jacquemin E-PER
, O
LIMSI S-ORG
, O

Ana B-PER
Paiva E-PER
, O
IST-UL S-ORG
, O

Rainer B-PER
Stiefelhagen E-PER
, O
Univ B-ORG
Karlsruhe E-ORG
, O

Jianhua B-PER
Tao E-PER
, O
NLPR S-ORG
, O
CN S-LOC

<b> O
Fausto B-PER
Giunchiglia E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Trento E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
José B-PER
Palazzo I-PER
M. I-PER
de I-PER
Oliveira E-PER
</b> O
, O
Universidade B-ORG
Federal I-ORG
do I-PER
Rio B-LOC
Grande I-LOC
do I-LOC
Sul E-LOC
, O
Brazil S-LOC

<b> O
Marta B-PER
Sabou E-PER
</b> O
, O
MODUL B-ORG
University I-ORG
Vienna E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
co-Editors-in-Chief O

Australia S-LOC

USA S-LOC

Ronen B-PER
Feldman E-PER
, O
Hebrew B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Jerusalem E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

Joao B-PER
Gama E-PER
, O
LIAAD-INESC B-ORG
TEC E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Porto E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

Heng B-PER
Huang E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pittsburgh E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Hanghang B-PER
Tong E-PER
, O
Arizona B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Haixun B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Google B-ORG
Research E-ORG

Gary B-PER
Weiss E-PER
, O
Fordham B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Marco B-PER
Ragni E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Freiburg E-ORG

Britta B-PER
Wrede E-PER
, O
Bielefeld B-ORG
University E-ORG

</div> O

<b> O
Editors ROLE

</i> O
Krzysztof B-PER
Dembczynski E-PER
, O
<i> O
Poznan B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

Nathalie B-PER
Japkowicz E-PER
, O
<i> O
American B-ORG
University E-ORG

Viktor B-PER
Bengs E-PER
, O
<i> O
Paderborn B-ORG
University E-ORG

Olivier B-PER
Chapelle E-PER
, O
<i> O
Yahoo O
! O
Research O

Pedro B-PER
Domingos E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Washington E-ORG

</i> O
Tamas B-PER
Horvath E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bonn E-ORG
and O
Fraunhofer B-ORG
IAIS E-ORG

</i> O
Michael B-PER
Kamp E-PER
, O
<i> O
Monash B-ORG
University E-ORG

</i> O
Mark B-PER
Last E-PER
, O
<i> O
Ben-Gurion B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Negev E-ORG

</i> O
Ernestina B-PER
Menasalvas E-PER
, O
<i> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG

</i> O
Risto B-PER
Miikkulainen E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC

</i> O
Kevin B-PER
Murphy E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
British I-ORG
Columbia E-ORG

</i> O
Ruggero B-PER
G. I-PER
Pensa E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Turin E-ORG

</i> O
Prasad B-PER
Tadepalli E-PER
, O
<i> O
Oregon B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
Stefano B-ORG
Teso E-ORG
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Helsinki E-ORG

Stefan B-PER
Wrobel E-PER
<i> O
, O
Fraunhofer B-ORG
IAIS E-ORG
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bonn E-ORG

</i> O
Eric B-PER
Xing E-PER
<i> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

</i> O
Clark B-ORG
Glymour E-ORG
, O
<i> O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG

Google B-ORG
Research E-ORG

Email O
: O
yingwu O
@ O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Central I-ORG
Florida E-ORG

Gang B-PER
Hua E-PER

Xuelong B-PER
Li E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
British I-ORG
Columbia E-ORG
( O
Okanaga S-LOC

UK S-LOC

USA S-LOC

USA S-LOC

USA S-LOC

The O
City B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG

Nirmal B-PER
K. I-PER
Bose E-PER

<b> O
Mu O
Mu O
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Northampton E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Qi B-PER
Tian E-PER
, O
</b> O
Huawei S-ORG
, O
Shenzhen S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<i> O
<b> O
Borko B-PER
Furht E-PER
, O
</b> O
Dept. O
of O
Computer B-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
Florida B-ORG
Atlantic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Harry B-PER
Agius E-PER
, O
</b> O
Brunel B-ORG
University I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

<b> O
Pablo B-PER
Cesar E-PER
, O
</b> O
Centrum O
Wiskunde O
& O
amp O
; O
Informatica O
, O
Netherlands S-LOC

<b> O
Ernesto B-PER
Damiani E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Milano E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
M O
. O
Shamim B-PER
Hossain E-PER
, O
</b> O
King B-ORG
Saud I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia E-LOC

<b> O
Hari B-PER
Kalva E-PER
, O
</b> O
Florida B-ORG
Atlantic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Boca B-LOC
Raton E-LOC
, O
Florida S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC
</i> O

<b> O
Mohan B-PER
Kankanhalli E-PER
, O
</b> O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Singapore E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

<b> O
Hong B-ORG
Man E-ORG
, O
</b> O
Stevens B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Hoboken S-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
Jersey E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Oge B-PER
Marques E-PER
, O
</b> O
Florida B-ORG
Atlantic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Boca B-LOC
Raton E-LOC
, O
Florida S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Liam B-PER
M. I-PER
Mayron E-PER
, O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Florida B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Florida S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Ali B-PER
Asghar I-PER
Nazari I-PER
Shirehjini E-PER
, O
</b> O
Karlsruhe B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Scott B-PER
M. I-PER
Stevens E-PER
, O
</b> O
SEI O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Lars B-PER
Wolf E-PER
, O
</b> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
Braunschweig E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Ion B-PER
Petre E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Turku E-ORG
, O
Turku S-LOC
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Gilles B-PER
Dowek E-PER
</b> O
, O
Inria S-LOC
, O
Paris S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Dirk B-PER
Sudholt E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Passau E-ORG
, O
Passau S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Yaochu B-PER
Jin E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Surrey E-ORG
, O
Guildford S-LOC
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Jiming B-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

Jianxin B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Central B-ORG
South I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jon B-PER
Rokne E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Calgary E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Kishan B-PER
G. I-PER
Mehrotra E-PER
, O
Syracus B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Shafiq B-PER
Burki E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Auckland E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

Tharam B-PER
Dillon E-PER
, O
Curtin B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Bentley S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

Zhongli B-PER
Ding E-PER
, O
Google B-ORG
Inc E-ORG
. O
, O
Mountain B-LOC
View E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Yutaka B-PER
Matsuo E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tokyo E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Ayumi B-PER
Shinohara E-PER
, O
Tohoku B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Robert B-PER
Glück E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Copenhagen E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Teruo B-PER
Higashino E-PER
, O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Gert B-PER
Smolka E-PER
, O
Saarland B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
EDITOR-IN-CHIEF ROLE

Professor O
John B-PER
MacIntyre E-PER

<b> O
FOUNDING B-ROLE
EDITOR ROLE

Haider B-PER
Abbas E-PER
( O
Iran S-LOC
and O
Pakistan S-LOC

India S-LOC

<b> O
Milan B-PER
Stehlík E-PER
( O
Rest B-LOC
of I-LOC
Europe E-LOC

<b> O
Alessia B-PER
Amelio E-PER
</b> O
, O
DIMES B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Calabria E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Oswin B-PER
Krause E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Copenhagen E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
Emanuele B-PER
Principi E-PER
</b> O
, O
Universita B-ORG
Politecnica I-ORG
delle I-ORG
Marche E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Gary B-PER
Weiss E-PER
</b> O
, O
Fordham B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Tina B-PER
Yu E-PER
</b> O
, O
Memorial B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
JOURNAL O
ADMINISTRATOR O

<b> O
<i> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE

<b> O
Ali B-PER
Anwar E-PER
</b> O
, O
IBM B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center-Almaden E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Christian B-PER
Jutten E-PER
</b> O
, O
UJF B-PER
Grenoble E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Julio B-PER
Ortega E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Granada E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Benjamin B-PER
Paassen E-PER
</b> O
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Jaakko B-PER
Peltonen E-PER
</b> O
, O
Tampere B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Jianlong B-PER
Qiu E-PER
</b> O
, O
Linyi B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Zhanshan B-PER
Wang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Northeastern B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Yinyan B-PER
Zhang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Jinan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Guangzhou S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

Claude B-PER
Brezinski E-PER

J. O
- O
P O
. O
Berrut S-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Fribourg E-ORG

K. B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG

D. B-PER
Di I-PER
Pietro E-PER
, O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Montpellier E-ORG

Z. B-PER
Jackiewicz E-PER
, O
Arizona B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG

L. B-PER
Reichel E-PER
, O
Kent B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG

H. B-PER
Sadok E-PER
, O
Université B-PER
du I-PER
Littoral E-PER

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

For O
all O
submission-related O
enquiries O
, O
please O
contact O
the O
Journal B-ORG
Editorial B-ROLE
Office E-ORG
via O
“ O
Contacts O
” O
or O
the O
Senior B-ROLE
Editor ROLE
Dragos B-PER
Calitoiu E-PER
at O
calitoiu O
@ O
math.carleton.ca O

<b> O
J O
. O
SALVADOR B-ORG
SÁNCHEZ I-ORG
GARRETA E-ORG

</b> O
Universidad B-ORG
Autonoma I-ORG
de I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG
( O
UAM S-ORG
) O
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
SEIICHI B-PER
OZAWA E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
Complutense I-ORG
of I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

hjzhang O
@ O

Xuemin S-PER
( O
Sherman S-LOC
) O
Shen E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Lei B-PER
Lei E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Guelph E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Benedetta B-PER
Picano E-PER
, O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-PER
Firenze E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

Professor O
Peter B-PER
Thomas E-PER
</b> O
, O
Manifesto B-ORG
Group E-ORG
, O
London S-LOC
, O
Melbourne B-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
New B-LOC
York E-LOC

Email O
: O
alan.chamberlain O
@ O

<b> O
Yunchuan B-PER
Sun E-PER
</b> O
, O
Beijing B-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Bieke B-PER
Zaman E-PER
</b> O
, O
Meaningful O
Interactions O
Lab O
( O
Mintlab O
) O
, O
KU B-ORG
Leuven E-ORG
, O
Belgium S-LOC

<b> O
Byrav B-PER
Ramamurthy E-PER

</div> O

Yves B-PER
Demazeau E-PER
, O
Laboratoire B-ORG
d’Informatique I-ORG
de I-ORG
Grenoble E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Bartosz B-PER
Krawczyk E-PER
, O
Wroclaw B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC

András B-PER
Lörincz E-PER
, O
Eötvös B-ORG
Loránd I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hungary S-LOC

Carlos B-PER
Soares E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Porto E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

<b> O
Mikhail B-PER
R. I-PER
Kogalovsky E-PER

</b> O
Cand O
. O
Sci. O
( O
Phys. O
– O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
System I-ORG
Programming E-ORG
, O
Russian B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC

<b> O
Aleksander B-PER
N. I-PER
Prokopenya E-PER

COPY O
EDITOR ROLE

</i> O
<b> O
Karl-Erik B-PER
Arzén E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Lund B-ORG
University E-ORG

<b> O
Robert B-PER
Davis E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
York E-ORG

</i> O
<b> O
Enrico B-PER
Vicario E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florence E-ORG

<b> O
EDITOR ROLE
in I-ROLE
CHIEF E-ROLE

<b> O
Peri B-PER
Loucopoulos E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toronto E-ORG
, O
Dept B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

J. B-PER
Mack I-PER
Robinson I-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Business E-ORG

Email O
: O
wrobinson O
@ O
gsu.edu O

Hamad B-PER
Bin I-PER
Khalifa E-PER
University O
, O
Qatar S-LOC

</b> O
Chalmers S-PER
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Gothenburg E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

<b> O
Jaelson B-PER
Castro E-PER

<b> O
Lawrence B-PER
Chung E-PER

<b> O
Paolo B-PER
Giorgini E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toronto E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Raimundas B-PER
Matulevičius E-PER

<b> O
Selmin B-PER
Nurcan E-PER


<b> O
Jolita B-PER
Ralyté E-PER

<b> O
Eric B-PER
Yu E-PER

Haibin B-PER
DUAN E-PER
, O
Beihang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jie B-PER
TIAN E-PER
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Automation E-ORG
, O
CAS S-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jun B-PER
XU E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Qinyu B-PER
ZHANG E-PER
, O
Harbin B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Weiping B-PER
ZHANG E-PER
, O
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O
Ruggero B-PER
S. I-PER
Gilyarevskii E-PER

EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

Price O
Medal O

<b> O
ASSISTANT O
EDITOR ROLE

<b> O
Muhammed B-PER
Younas E-PER
</b> O
, O
Oxford B-ORG
Brook I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Ali B-PER
Selamat E-PER
</b> O
, O
Universiti B-ORG
Teknologi I-ORG
Malaysia E-ORG
, O
Malaysia S-LOC

<b> O
Weiming B-PER
Shen E-PER
</b> O
, O
National B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Council E-ROLE
of I-ORG
Canada E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

S. B-PER
Glesner E-PER

Bundeswehr B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Munich S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Illinois E-ORG
at O
Chicago S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC
and O
Bilkent B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Turkey S-LOC

<b> O
G O
. O
Anbarjafari S-PER
, O
</b> O
iCV B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Group E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tartu E-ORG
, O
Estonia S-LOC

<b> O
P O
. O
Athavale S-PER
, O
</b> O
Clarkson B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
P O
. O
Regalia O
</b> O
, O
National B-ORG
Science I-ORG
Foundation E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC


Przemyslaw B-PER
Kazienko E-PER
, O
Wroclaw B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC

Philippa B-PER
Pattison E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Melbourne E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Guandong B-PER
Xu E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Christopher B-PER
C. I-PER
Yang E-PER
, O
Drexel B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yuan-Chih B-PER
Yu E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Culture I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

Anthony B-PER
Ephremides E-PER
, O
Electrical B-ORG
and I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maryland E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Kam B-PER
Cheong I-PER
Li E-PER
, O
Director O
of O
Research B-ORG
Office E-ORG
, O
The O
Open B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

Ivan B-PER
Bratko E-PER
, O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
and I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Ljubljana E-ORG
, O
Slovenia S-LOC

Byung-Gyu B-PER
Kim E-PER
, O
Intelligent B-ORG
Vision I-ORG
Processing I-ORG
Laboratory E-ORG
( O
IVPL S-ORG
) O
, O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
IT I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
Sookmyung B-ORG
Women I-ORG
’s I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
South B-LOC
Korea E-LOC

Miodrag B-PER
Mihaljević E-PER
, O
Matematički B-ORG
Institut I-ORG
SANU E-ORG
, O
Serbia S-LOC

Alex B-PER
Nicolau E-PER
, O
Center B-ORG
for I-ORG
Embedded I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Systems E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Wojciech B-PER
Rytter E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Warsaw E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC

Ljubisa B-PER
Stankovic E-PER
, O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electrical I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Montenegro E-ORG
, O
Montenegro S-LOC

Dongming B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Beihang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC
and O
CNRS S-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Franz B-PER
Wotawa E-PER
, O
Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Software I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Graz B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Emerging O
Trends O
in I-ROLE
Sensors O
, O
IoT O
and O
Smart O
Systems O
</i> O

Deepal B-PER
Puthal E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New B-LOC
Castle E-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O

<b> O
Aneliese B-PER
K. I-PER
Amschler I-PER
Andrews E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Denver E-ORG
, O
CO S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Ayse B-PER
Basar I-PER
Bener E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Ryerson B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC
</i> O

<b> O
Jeff B-PER
Offutt E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
George B-ORG
Mason I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Fairfax S-LOC
, O
VA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Marc B-PER
Roper E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Strathclyde E-ORG
, O
Glasgow S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Gregg B-PER
Rothermel E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nebraska E-ORG
at O
Lincoln S-LOC
, O
NB S-LOC
, O
, O
USA S-LOC
</i> O

Yijun B-PER
Yu E-PER
</<E-ORG> O
b> O
, O
<i> O
The O
Open B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Milton B-LOC
Keynes E-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG

</i> O
<b> O
Dirk B-PER
Husmeier E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Glasgow E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Geoff B-PER
McLachlan E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Queensland E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
Scott B-PER
Sisson E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
UNSW O
, O
Sydney S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
David B-PER
Woods E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southampton E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</div> O

Tuscaloosa S-LOC
, O
AL S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

RWTH B-ORG
Aachen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Muncie S-LOC
, O
IN I-ROLE
, O
USA S-LOC

Martin B-PER
Schindler E-PER

<b> O
<i> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE

<b> O
<i> O
Advisory BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

<b> O
Manfred B-PER
Broy E-PER
</b> O
( O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

Wil B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Aalst E-PER
</b> O
( O
Germany S-LOC

Gordon B-PER
Blair E-PER
</b> O
( O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Tony B-PER
Clark E-PER
</b> O
( O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Andy B-PER
Schürr E-PER
</b> O
( O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Andrzej B-PER
Wasowski E-PER
</b> O
( O
Denmark S-LOC

Editor-in-Chief ROLE

Andries B-PER
P. I-PER
Engelbrecht E-PER
, O
Stellenbosch B-ORG
University E-ORG

Guy B-PER
Theraulaz E-PER
, O
Université O
Paul B-PER
Sabatier E-PER

Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

Nora B-PER
Ayanian E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
California E-ORG

Anders B-PER
L. I-PER
Christensen E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG

Eliseo B-PER
Ferrante E-PER
, O
Vrije B-ORG
Universiteit I-ORG
Amsterdam E-ORG

Luca B-PER
Maria I-PER
Gambardella E-PER
, O
Istituto B-ORG
Dalle I-ORG
Molle I-ORG
di I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
sull'Intelligenza I-ORG
Artificiale E-ORG

Kirstin B-PER
Petersen E-PER
, O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG

Amir B-PER
Zaib I-PER
Abbasi E-PER
, O
Capital B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Assistant O
Professor O
, O
Islamabad S-LOC
, O
Pakistan S-LOC

Todd B-PER
Green E-PER
, O
Sega S-ORG
- O
Candycrush B-ORG
, I-ORG
Developer E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
States E-LOC

Ian B-PER
Marshall E-PER
, O
Coventry B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Professor O
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

Ryan B-PER
Seiff E-PER
, O
Phoenix B-ORG
Labs E-ORG
, O
Technical O
Director O
, O
United B-LOC
States E-LOC

</b> O
Courant B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematical I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Benjamin B-PER
Bustos E-PER

<b> O
Lap-Pui B-PER
Chau E-PER

<b> O
Jie B-PER
Chen E-PER

<b> O
Jie B-PER
Chen E-PER

<b> O
Jean-Michel B-PER
Dischler E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Calgary E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC
, O
mgavrilo O
@ O

<b> O
Prem B-PER
Kalra E-PER

Konkuk B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
South B-LOC
Korea E-LOC
, O
hyuskim O
@ O
konkuk.ac.kr O

</b> O
Durham B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC
, O
georgios.a.koulieris O
@ O

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
York E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC
, O
mkyan O
@ O

<b> O
Seungyong B-PER
Lee E-PER

</b> O
Pohang B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
( O
POSTECH S-ORG
) O
, O
South B-LOC
Korea E-LOC
, O
leesy O
@ O

</b> O
Lebanese B-ORG
National I-ORG
Council E-ROLE
for I-ORG
Scientific I-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
Lebanon S-LOC
, O
anasri.82 O
@ O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oviedo E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC
, O
bremeseiro O
@ O

</b> O
Leibniz B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
Hannover E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC
, O
rosenhahn O
@ O
tnt.uni-hannover.de O

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Heidelberg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC
, O
sadlo O
@ O

</b> O
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
, O
shengbin O
@ O

</b> O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
, O
wangruiping O
@ O

</b> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC
, O
ASJMZheng O
@ O

<b> O
Wangmeng B-PER
Zuo E-PER

Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

</b> O
Athena B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG

Digital O
& O
amp O
; O
Interactive B-ORG
Media I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
( O
IDMI S-ORG

<b> O
Angela B-PER
Bonifati E-PER

<b> O
Susan B-PER
B. I-PER
Davidson E-PER

<b> O
Murat B-PER
Kantarcioglu E-PER

Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
// O
liguoliang O
@ O

<b> O
Rachel B-PER
Pottinger E-PER

</b> O
IBM B-ORG
Research E-ORG
- O
Almaden S-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
// O
ytian O
@ O

<b> O
Xiaokui B-PER
Xiao E-PER

<b> O
Mitsunori B-PER
Ogihara E-PER

Victoria B-ORG
University E-ORG

School B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electrical I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG

Ramat-Aviv S-PER

guy O
@ O

<b> O
Pierre B-PER
Fraigniaud E-PER

seth.gilbert O
@ O

Fukuoka S-LOC
819-0395 O
, O
Japan S-LOC

Departamento B-ORG
de I-ORG
Informatica I-ORG
e I-ORG
Ingenieria I-ORG
de I-ORG
Sistemas E-ORG

Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Zaragoza E-ORG

Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Munich E-ORG

( O
theoretical O
aspects O
of O
parallel O
algorithms O
and O
architectures O
and O
of O
networks O
; O
applied O
graph O
theory O

rsnbrg O
@ O

338 O
Davis B-PER
Hall E-PER

University O
at O
Buffalo S-LOC

( O
Kolmogorov O
complexity O
; O
distributed O
algorithms O
; O
machine O
learning O
; O
physics O
and O
computation O

<b> O
Gerhard B-PER
Woeginger E-PER

RWTH B-ORG
Aachen I-ORG
University E-ORG

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Constantine B-PER
Stephanidis E-PER

<b> O
Margherita B-PER
Antona E-PER

<b> O
Andreas B-PER
Holzinger E-PER
, O
</b> O
Medical B-ORG
University I-ORG
Graz E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Troy B-PER
McDaniel E-PER
</b> O
, O
Arizona B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Stavroula B-PER
Ntoa E-PER
</b> O
, O
FORTH-ICS O
, O
Greece S-LOC


Founding B-ROLE
Editor ROLE

</i> O
<b> O
David B-PER
</<E-PER> O
b> O
<b> O
Chin S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Hawaii E-ORG
at O
Manoa S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Geert-Jan B-PER
Houben E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Delft B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
Bonnie B-PER
Webber E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Marek B-PER
Rusinkiewicz E-PER
, O
<i> O
NJIT O
, O
USA S-LOC

Rui B-PER
Zhou E-PER
, O
<i> O
Swinburne B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Jie B-PER
Cao E-PER
, O
<i> O
Nanjing B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Finance I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
Economics E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Arbee O
L.P O
. O
Chen E-PER
, O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Chengchi I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Prof. O
Robert B-PER
D. I-PER
Macredie E-PER

ASSOCIATE BI-ROLE
EDITORS ROLE


Chapel B-LOC
Hill E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Prof. O
Dennis B-PER
E. I-PER
Beck E-PER
( O
USA S-LOC

Prof. O
Mark B-PER
Billinghurst E-PER
( O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

Prof. O
John B-PER
A. I-PER
Vince E-PER

Bournemouth B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Prof. O
Dr. O
Dieter B-PER
Schmalstieg E-PER
, O
Austria S-LOC

Suzanne B-PER
Weghorst E-PER
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
EDITORIAL B-ROLE

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O
<div> O
. O
</div> O



Braiden B-PER
Parks E-PER
</b> O



Star B-PER
Luna E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Delhi E-ORG
y O




Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

University B-ORG
College I-ORG
Cork E-ORG
( O



@ O


Kase B-PER
Gesshin E-PER
</b> O
Saarlandes E-PER

Taguchi B-PER
Masafumi E-PER
</b> O
Umea B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O

Marvin B-PER
Logan E-PER
</b> O
SUNY B-LOC
, O

Mihalis B-PER
Yannakakis E-PER
</b> O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tennessee, I-ORG
Knoxville E-ORG
at O

Raphael B-PER
Finkel E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tsukuba E-ORG
, O

Lori B-PER
Schofield E-PER
</b> O
Nacional I-LOC
Sur E-LOC

<b> O
Ramesh B-PER
Jain E-PER
</b> O
- B-ORG
CentraleSuplec E-ORG
at O
USA S-LOC


<b> O

kathleen.richardson O

LarryStapleton O

@ O

Angelina B-PER
Foley E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Newcastle, I-ORG
Australia E-ORG
, O

Kavita B-PER
Conway E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California, I-ORG
Riverside E-ORG
, O

Hector B-PER
Garcia E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Turku E-ORG
- O
, O
Peru S-LOC

Josef B-PER
Rigby E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
Complutense B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG
, O

Iori B-PER
Hirokazu E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Ottawa E-ORG
, O


Oh B-PER
Sang-Jun E-PER
</i> O
, O

Fern B-PER
Sanchez E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bristol E-ORG
( O
Faculty B-ORG
Law E-ORG

Humphrey B-PER
Farley E-PER
, O
, O
Japan S-LOC

Tim B-PER
Finin E-PER
, O
Japan S-LOC

Bethanie B-PER
Healy E-PER
, O
Keynes E-LOC

Hector B-PER
Garcia E-PER
, O

C. B-PER
J. I-PER
van I-PER
Rijsbergen E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Antwerp E-ORG
, O
ZEALAND E-LOC

Star B-PER
Nielsen E-PER
</b> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Kanpur E-ORG
, O
ISRAEL S-LOC

Scott B-PER
Fahlman E-PER
, O
RMIT O
AUSTRALIA S-LOC

Alagesan B-PER
Poduri E-PER
</b> O
National B-ORG
Research I-ORG
University I-ORG
Higher I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Economics E-ORG
, O

Winifred B-PER
"Tim" I-PER
Alice I-PER
Asprey E-PER
</b> O
Sapienza B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Rome E-ORG
, O

Taylah B-PER
Conroy E-PER
</b> O
IE B-ORG
IE I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Neel B-PER
Ramirez E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Connecticut E-ORG
, O

Frances B-PER
E. I-PER
Allen E-PER
, O
<i> O
Waseda B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Trygve B-PER
Reenskaug E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
Ulm E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Kennedy B-PER
Schneider E-PER
, O
National B-ORG
Taiwan I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Dorian B-PER
Casey E-PER
, O

Avidosa B-PER
Vaisakhi E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Sanjeev B-PER
Arora E-PER
, O
<i> O
Wageningen B-ORG
University I-ORG
& I-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O

Star B-PER
Luna E-PER
, O
King B-ORG
Saud I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Mikail B-PER
Thomson E-PER
, O
<i> O
King B-ORG
Fahd I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Petroleum I-ORG
& I-ORG
Minerals E-ORG
, O

Nieve B-PER
Mckenzie E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Reading E-ORG
, O

<b> O

</b> O
Albert-Ludwigs-Universitaet B-ORG
Freiburg E-ORG
, O

National B-ORG
Taiwan I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
Council E-ROLE


The B-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Korea E-ORG
at O
Qatar S-LOC
, O

UCSI B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

California B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

</b> O
Universidade B-ORG
Estadual I-ORG
de I-ORG
Campinas E-ORG
, O
Ancona S-LOC
, O


</div> O

Tamon B-PER
Motoyasu E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Warwick E-ORG
, O

Lance B-PER
Fortnow E-PER
, O
Universiti B-ORG
Sains I-ORG
Malaysia E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Zheng B-PER
Zhi E-PER
, O
Universidade B-ORG
de I-ORG
So I-ORG
Paulo E-ORG
, O

Nannie B-PER
Hatfield E-PER
, O
Xian B-ORG
Jiaotong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Barsati B-PER
Sandipa E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Iowa E-ORG
, O

Eshan B-PER
Morris E-PER
, O
Jagiellonian B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

John B-PER
Vincent I-PER
Atanasoff E-PER
, O
Tokyo B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Universitt B-ORG
Innsbruck E-ORG
( O
ITS S-ORG

Simone B-PER
Vance E-PER
, O
Tilburg B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O

Gabrielius B-PER
Reeve E-PER
, O
Radboud B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Zakariah B-PER
Ahmad E-PER
, O
RUDN B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Bethanie B-PER
Healy E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maryland, I-ORG
College I-ORG
Park E-ORG
, O

L. B-PER
R. I-PER
Ford, I-PER
Jr. E-PER
, O
Belarusian B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Lewie B-PER
Hoover E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O

Johnnie B-PER
Britton E-PER
, O
Humboldt-Universitt B-ORG
zu I-ORG
Berlin E-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

Gregory B-PER
Dale E-PER
, O
, O

Kuramoto B-PER
Takeji E-PER
, O
Universitt B-ORG
Hamburg E-ORG
, O

Aneesa B-PER
Jennings E-PER
, O
Nankai B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Rex B-PER
Hobbs E-PER
, O
Johannes B-ORG
Kepler I-ORG
University I-ORG
Linz E-ORG
, O

Raphael B-PER
Finkel E-PER
</b> O
Sun B-ORG
Yat-sen I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Horiuchi B-PER
Kamatari E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bath E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Nieve B-PER
Mckenzie E-PER
, O
Peter B-ORG
the I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Saint-Petersburg I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Jitendra B-PER
Choudhary E-PER
</b> O
, O

Zhang B-PER
Jian E-PER
Jr O

Kajus B-PER
Ross E-PER
</b> O

Debasis B-PER
Sundhararajan E-PER
</b> O
Albert-Ludwigs-Universitaet B-ORG
Freiburg E-ORG
Houston-Clear B-LOC
Lake E-LOC

Lori B-PER
Schofield E-PER
</b> O



E-mail O
: O




Prof. O

E-mail O
: O

: O



Imperial B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O

<b> O


University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Dundee E-ORG
( O

Swansea B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG
; O


Princeton B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC


APPLICATIONS O

<b> O
Katie B-PER
Hurst E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O

Daniel B-PER
Penn E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O

Arjan B-PER
Diaz E-PER
, O
Bond B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
FINLAND S-LOC

Zakariah B-PER
Ahmad E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Warsaw E-ORG
, O

Amelia-Grace B-PER
Herbert E-PER
, O
- B-ORG
Friedrich-Alexander-Universitt I-ORG
Erlangen-Nrnberg E-ORG
, O

Amrish B-PER
Ilyas E-PER
, O
SOAS B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O

Rahul B-PER
Blair E-PER
, O
KTH B-ORG
Royal I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

<b> O
: O

Abdullah B-PER
Parker E-PER
, O
Beijing B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Kirsty B-PER
Marsden E-PER
, O
</b> O
- B-ORG
Friedrich-Alexander-Universitt I-ORG
Erlangen-Nrnberg E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Star B-PER
Nielsen E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
Australian I-ORG
National I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Star B-PER
Luna E-PER
, O
King B-ORG
Saud I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Tashan B-PER
Duggan E-PER
, O
</i> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tartu E-ORG
, O

Humphrey B-PER
Farley E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Yokohama B-ORG
City I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

D.R.Fulkerson B-PER
, O
<i> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Delhi E-ORG
, O

</i> O
Avantas B-PER
Ghosal E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Georgia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Nieve B-PER
Mckenzie E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wollongong E-ORG
, O

</i> O
Steve B-PER
Ward E-PER
, O
Universit B-ORG
Grenoble-Alpes E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
Frances B-PER
E. I-PER
Allen E-PER
, O
Universiti B-ORG
Brunei I-ORG
Darussalam E-ORG
, O
, O

<b> O
Zhen B-PER
Cheng E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Geneva E-ORG
, O

Aravind B-PER
K. I-PER
Joshi E-PER
, O
Harvard B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Su B-PER
Jiahao E-PER
, O
</b> O
American B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Beirut E-ORG
, O

</i> O
Roy B-PER
Taylor E-PER
, O
<i> O
Universite B-ORG
libre I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bruxelles E-ORG
, O

David B-PER
S. I-PER
Johnson E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Dundee E-ORG
, O

</i> O
Luo B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
Scuola B-ORG
Normale I-ORG
Superiore I-ORG
di I-ORG
Pisa E-ORG
, O

</i> O
. O
<i> O
Gwangju B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Kalyanavata B-PER
Veerender E-PER
</b> O
1939-2012 O
<i> O
KIT, B-ORG
Karlsruhe I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
" O
La B-ORG

Avidosa B-PER
Vaisakhi E-PER
</b> O
( O
) O
Universiti B-ORG
Brunei I-ORG
Darussalam E-ORG
, O

Liao B-PER
Delan E-PER
, O
<i> O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tennessee, I-ORG
Knoxville E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Tamon B-PER
Motoyasu E-PER
, O
Tianjin B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O


Paula B-PER
Steele E-PER
, O
Albert-Ludwigs-Universitaet B-ORG
Freiburg E-ORG
, O

Rojin B-PER
Shepard E-PER
, O
King B-ORG
Fahd I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Petroleum I-ORG
& I-ORG
Minerals E-ORG
, O

Rahul B-PER
Blair E-PER
, O
Julius-Maximilians-Universitt B-ORG
Wrzburg E-ORG
, O
Qatar S-LOC

Ahmad B-PER
Hanson E-PER
, O
<i> O
California B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Chris B-PER
Lattner E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tasmania E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Augustus B-PER
Quinn E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
Australian I-ORG
National I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Manny B-PER
M I-PER
Lehman E-PER
, O
Universiti B-ORG
Malaya E-ORG
, O


North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
- O
Paris S-LOC


<b> O
Rojin B-PER
Shepard E-PER
, O
Universite B-ORG
libre I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bruxelles E-ORG
, O

</i> O
Steve B-PER
Lawrence E-PER
, O
</b> O
Universitt B-ORG
Jena E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Dave B-PER
Oliver E-PER
, O
Technische B-ORG
Universitt I-ORG
Darmstadt E-ORG
, O

Liao B-PER
Delan E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
Boulder E-ORG
, O

Kyung B-ORG
Hee I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O


Aila B-PER
Chester E-PER
, O
Universiti B-ORG
Sains I-ORG
Malaysia E-ORG
, O

Takai B-PER
Eishi E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
at I-ORG
Buffalo I-ORG
SUNY E-ORG
, O

Augustus B-PER
Quinn E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Melbourne E-ORG
, O

Ahmad B-PER
Hanson E-PER
, O
</b> O
Bandung B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Leonard B-PER
Adleman E-PER
, O
<i> O
Pennsylvania B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

</i> O
Cheng B-PER
Yong E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O

Amayah B-PER
Mclaughlin E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
St I-ORG
Andrews E-ORG
at O
USA S-LOC

Aneesa B-PER
Jennings E-PER
, O
SOAS B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O


EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

Kazan B-ORG
Federal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Saclay B-ORG
Ile-de-France E-ORG

Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
, O

Managing B-ROLE

</i> O
</b> O

Kaia B-PER
Silva E-PER
, O
</b> O
Technische B-ORG
Universitt I-ORG
Darmstadt E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Moto B-PER
Shigeru E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC


Universitas B-ORG
Indonesia E-ORG
, O



duke.j.david O
@ O

<b> O

Ursula.Martin O

logic O

Tianjin B-ORG
University E-ORG
/ O
, O
/ I-ORG
TEC E-ORG
, O


, O
B O
Simulation O
Verification O
) O

Bernard B-PER
Galler E-PER
, O
Sogang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Gabrielius B-PER
Reeve E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado, I-ORG
Denver E-ORG
, O

Jiya B-PER
Puckett E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tartu E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yamaha B-PER
Rai E-PER
</b> O
Sorbonne B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

, O
computer O

, O

networks O




The B-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
for I-ORG
Science I-ORG
Technology E-ORG



amp O


University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oslo E-ORG
, O


Universit B-ORG
Grenoble-Alpes E-ORG
, O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Canterbury E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Tecnolgico B-ORG
de I-ORG
Monterrey E-ORG
at O
& O
; O
, O
China S-LOC


Zhen B-PER
Yang E-PER
, O

Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Torino E-ORG
, O


University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Gttingen E-ORG
ZHOU B-PER

Mario B-PER
Tchou E-PER
, O

B?rje B-PER
Langefors E-PER
, O

ETH B-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
- I-ORG
Swiss I-ORG
Federal I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Chinese B-ORG

Bethanie B-PER
Healy E-PER
, O
China S-LOC


Eoin B-PER
Rahman E-PER
, O
Flinders B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Martin B-PER
Richards E-PER
, O
Gwangju B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Mylee B-PER
Neal E-PER
, O
Futurs O

Kiah B-PER
Melendez E-PER
, O
Aston B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Sanjeev B-PER
Arora E-PER
, O
Nanjing B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

National B-ORG
Taiwan I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
of I-ORG

Michael B-PER
I. I-PER
Jordan E-PER
, O
<i> O
Auckland B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Jemimah B-PER
Hirst E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pisa E-ORG
, O

Aamna B-PER
Welsh E-PER
, O
Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Torino E-ORG
</i> O

Bernard B-PER
Richards E-PER
, O
Brunel B-ORG
University I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O

Edano B-PER
Jakuchu E-PER
, O
Georgia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

Jorja B-PER
Armitage E-PER
, O
Dartmouth B-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

Imai B-PER
Namboku E-PER
, O
Utrecht B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

. O
, O
<i> O
Tampere B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Morita B-PER
Kitahachi E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O

City B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong E-ORG
, O
Maynooth B-ORG

</i> O

Jaime B-PER
Teeva E-PER
, O
Vienna B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
di I-PER
Milano E-PER
, O

<b> O
Kajus B-PER
Ross E-PER
, O
Universitt B-ORG
Mannheim E-ORG
, O

Josef B-PER
Rigby E-PER
, O
Harvard B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Chup B-PER
Chong-Hun E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas I-ORG
at I-ORG
Austin E-ORG
, O

Daniel B-PER
Lin E-PER
</b> O
Leiden B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Glasgow S-LOC
UK S-LOC

Kuramoto B-PER
Takeji E-PER
</b> O
ETH B-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
- I-ORG
Swiss I-ORG
Federal I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Jian-Yun O
</b> O
, O
Hiroshima B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Zoubin B-PER
Ghahramani E-PER
</b> O
, O
ETH B-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
- I-ORG
Swiss I-ORG
Federal I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O


Khalifa B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
</b> O

</i> O
Ryker B-PER
Knight E-PER
, O
<i> O

Danielius B-PER
Sharples E-PER
</b> O

Mok B-PER
Songhyon E-PER
</b> O
, O

</i> O
Zakariah B-PER
Ahmad E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambridge E-ORG
</i> O
<b> O

Wageningen B-ORG
University I-ORG
& I-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O


mambo O

<b> O
Divine B-PER
Sierra E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Milana B-PER
Mcpherson E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California, I-ORG
Davis E-ORG
, O

Blossom B-PER
Nguyen E-PER
</b> O
Newcastle B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Fairfax S-LOC

Donald B-PER
Firesmith E-PER
</b> O
TELECOM B-ORG
ParisTech E-ORG
, O

Chante B-PER
Hackett E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kansas E-ORG
, O
NS S-LOC

Tamon B-PER
Motoyasu E-PER
</b> O
, O
The B-ORG
Ohio I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Cecily B-PER
Ventura E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Connecticut E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Cliff B-PER
Jones E-PER
</b> O
Singapore B-ORG
Management I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Mangjol B-PER
Kyung-Min E-PER
</b> O
Flinders B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Uesugi B-PER
Danno E-PER
</b> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O

Star B-PER
Luna E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southampton E-ORG
, O

Cara B-PER
Mellor E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bern E-ORG
, O

Mo B-PER
Gengxin E-PER
</b> O
Qatar B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Gopa B-PER
Trilochana E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Basel E-ORG
, O

Katie B-PER
Hurst E-PER
</b> O
Loughborough B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Horiuchi B-PER
Kamatari E-PER
</b> O
Universidad B-ORG
Austral E-ORG
, O

Edward B-PER
Feigenbaum E-PER
</b> O
USA S-LOC

Taylah B-PER
Conroy E-PER
</b> O
, O
Shandong B-ORG
University E-ORG
Council E-ROLE
Research E-ORG





Linkping B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O

<b> O





The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
at O

Kinoshita B-PER
Heihachiro E-PER
, O
Lomonosov B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Fern B-PER
Sanchez E-PER
, O
Imperial B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O

Kody B-PER
Woodley E-PER
, O
cole B-ORG
Normale I-ORG
Suprieure I-ORG
de I-ORG
Lyon E-ORG
, O

Mildred B-PER
Atkinson E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tasmania E-ORG
, O

Liao B-PER
Jun E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Iowa E-ORG
, O

Kim B-PER
Kyu-Bok E-PER
, O
Humboldt-Universitt B-ORG
zu I-ORG
Berlin E-ORG
, O

Ruby-Mae B-PER
Joseph E-PER
, O
Leiden B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Iram B-PER
Estrada E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
British I-ORG
Columbia E-ORG
, O

Devasru B-PER
Subramanyan E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
York E-ORG
, O

Liao B-PER
Delan E-PER
, O
Shandong B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Ryker B-PER
Knight E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Milan E-ORG
, O
Haifa S-LOC
, O


</b> O
King B-ORG
Fahd I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Petroleum I-ORG
& I-ORG
Minerals E-ORG
, O

<b> O


<b> O


The B-ORG
Chinese I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong E-ORG
, O

PA S-LOC

Florence S-LOC

</b> O

</b> O

</b> O

, O


. O








erich.neuhold O

Dongguk B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
CSDL S-ORG


National B-ORG
Sun I-ORG
Yat-sen I-ORG
University E-ORG
. O



Stacey B-PER
Mccartney E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
St I-ORG
Andrews E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Chup B-PER
Chong-Hun E-PER
, O
</b> O
Dublin B-ORG
City I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hamilton S-LOC

Scott B-PER
Aaronson E-PER
, O
</b> O
, O
Portugal S-LOC

B?rje B-PER
Langefors E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cologne E-ORG
, O
Blacksburg S-LOC
VA S-LOC

Fujima B-PER
Kyoshi E-PER
</b> O
, O
Erasmus B-ORG
University I-ORG
Rotterdam E-ORG
, O

<b> O
C. B-PER
J. I-PER
van I-PER
Rijsbergen E-PER
, O
Gwangju B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Yannis B-PER
Delgado E-PER
, O
Mexico S-LOC

Leen B-PER
Hensley E-PER
, O
Scuola B-ORG
Normale I-ORG
Superiore I-ORG
di I-ORG
Pisa E-ORG
, O

Eoin B-PER
Rahman E-PER
, O
</b> O
The B-ORG
Ohio I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Ibaraki S-LOC
, O

Otto-Hahn-Str O
. O








<i> O

) O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leeds E-ORG
, O
, O

Adrian B-PER
Ball E-PER
, O
Eindhoven B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Adelina B-PER
Potter E-PER
, O
Tulane B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Manitoba E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Pok B-PER
Chunyong E-PER
, O
Singapore B-ORG
Management I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Aamna B-PER
Welsh E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
at I-ORG
Buffalo I-ORG
SUNY E-ORG
, O

Steve B-PER
Lawrence E-PER
</b> O

Seoul B-ORG
National I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Iran S-LOC




University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tartu E-ORG
, O


Sorbonne B-ORG
University E-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Sul E-LOC
, O

Peter B-ORG
the I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Saint-Petersburg I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Turkey S-LOC

Universit B-ORG
de I-ORG
Montral E-ORG
, O



University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O



<b> O

Wuhan B-ORG
University E-ORG
Liu E-PER


Zoubin B-PER
Ghahramani E-PER
( O
Universidad B-ORG
Nacional I-ORG
de I-ORG
Colombia E-ORG
) O
, O

Westflische B-ORG
Wilhelms-Universitt I-ORG
Mnster E-ORG
Chen E-PER
CAS O

Daniel B-PER
Lin E-PER
<i> O
Ecole B-ORG
Polytechnique E-ORG
, O

Pok B-PER
Chunyong E-PER
<i> O
Beijing B-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cape I-ORG
Town E-ORG
<i> O

Jorja B-PER
Armitage E-PER
<i> O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
Peng E-PER
<I-ORG>> I-ORG
Zhejiang I-ORG

Kang B-PER
Chung-Ho E-PER
<i> O
Queensland B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
at O

Zakariah B-PER
Ahmad E-PER
<i> O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tennessee, I-ORG
Knoxville E-ORG
, O

Nishikiri B-PER
Yuji E-PER
<i> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Kanpur E-ORG
, O

Matsuzaki B-PER
Takahiro E-PER
<i> O
Swinburne B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Guo B-PER
Ruogang E-PER
<i> O

Luo B-PER
Li E-PER
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California, I-ORG
Berkeley E-ORG
, O

Zachariah B-PER
Hicks E-PER
<i> O
CAS O

Ye B-PER
Zemin E-PER
<i> O
Ecole B-ORG
des I-ORG
Ponts I-ORG
ParisTech E-ORG
, O

Alec B-PER
Pittman E-PER
<i> O
Rensselaer B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC

Kwon B-PER
Dong-Sun E-PER
<<I-ORG> O
i O
Vienna B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Avidosa B-PER
Vaisakhi E-PER
. O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Miami E-ORG
, O
South B-LOC

Du B-PER
Kun E-PER
, O
Moscow B-ORG
State I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
International I-ORG
Relations E-ORG
, O

koc O
@ O


Zheng B-PER
Zhi E-PER
, O
Wageningen B-ORG
University I-ORG
& I-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O

John B-PER
C. I-PER
Reynolds E-PER
, O
Utrecht B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O



Germany S-LOC





<b> O


Pu B-PER
Yeong-Cheol E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leicester E-ORG
, O

Tao B-PER
Liuxian E-PER
</b> O
Hitotsubashi B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Kong E-LOC

Elyas B-PER
Lambert E-PER
</b> O
KU B-ORG
Leuven E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

David B-PER
Gelernter E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
Rensselaer B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O

Founding B-ROLE

</i> O
Sharif B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

Chen B-PER
Heng E-PER
, O
<i> O
Tel B-ORG
Aviv I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
Avidosa B-PER
Vaisakhi E-PER
, O
Universitt B-ORG
Mannheim E-ORG
, O

</i> O
<b> O
Danny B-PER
Vasquez E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Russia S-LOC

Morita B-PER
Kitahachi E-PER
, O
<i> O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Ontario E-ORG
, O

Yan B-PER
Chang E-PER
, O
</i> O
University B-ORG
Ulm E-ORG
, O

Tim B-PER
Finin E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cape I-ORG
Town E-ORG
- O
Hellas S-ORG
, O


Sang B-PER
Song-Min E-PER
, O
Fudan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
of I-ORG

Edano B-PER
Jakuchu E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O

=" O
placeholder O

<b> O
Kuramoto B-PER
Takeji E-PER
</b> O
Pontificia B-ORG
Universidad I-ORG
Javeriana E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Fujima B-PER
Kyoshi E-PER
</b> O
Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Milano E-ORG
, O

Andrew B-PER
Appel E-PER
</b> O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O

Amara B-PER
Wilkes E-PER
</b> O
, O
Scuola B-ORG
Normale I-ORG
Superiore I-ORG
di I-ORG
Pisa E-ORG
Las I-LOC

</div> O

Yamaha B-PER
Rai E-PER
, O
Armasuisse S-LOC

Rex B-PER
Hobbs E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Strathclyde E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Divine B-PER
Sierra E-PER
, O
Deakin B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Tokyo S-LOC

Leanne B-PER
Sargent E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Porto E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC

<b> O
Anish B-PER
Morse E-PER
, O
Niksun O

Danny B-PER
Vasquez E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
and O


Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Madras E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

Cliff B-PER
Jones E-PER
</b> O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Shen B-PER
Su E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pisa E-ORG
, O

</i> O
Wil B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Aalst E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Auckland E-ORG
, O

Daphne B-PER
East E-PER
, O
</b> O
USA S-LOC

Kwok B-PER
Myung-Hee E-PER
, O
Korea E-LOC
of I-LOC

</i> O
Hal B-PER
Abelson E-PER
<i> O
</i> O
Tongji B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O


class O
"> O

Editors-in-Chief ROLE


: O

Saint B-ORG
Petersburg I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O



Stephen B-PER
C. I-PER
Johnson E-PER
University O
, O

<b> O

The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sheffield E-ORG
, O

<b> O

Linkping B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O


Mylee B-PER
Neal E-PER
, O
Rensselaer B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O

Zoubin B-PER
Ghahramani E-PER
, O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Lois B-PER
Booker E-PER
, O
Queens B-ORG
University I-ORG
Belfast E-ORG
, O

Vijai B-PER
Sritharan E-PER
, O
Curtin B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Mikey B-PER
Haigh E-PER
, O
Universit B-ORG
Paris-Sud E-ORG
, O

Jaye B-PER
Orr E-PER
</b> O
Washington B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Mehreen B-PER
Pritchard E-PER
</b> O
Griffith B-ORG
University E-ORG
do I-PER
, O
Brazil S-LOC

Lai B-PER
ZhenKang E-PER
</b> O
McGill B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC




USA S-LOC

Amayah B-PER
Mclaughlin E-PER
, O
Nagoya B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Ping B-PER
Fu E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
Porto E-ORG

Barry B-PER
Chapman E-PER
, O
Tel B-ORG
Aviv I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Lewie B-PER
Hoover E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oulu E-ORG
at O

Xiang B-PER
Chang E-PER
, O
George B-ORG
Washington I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Domonic B-PER
Christian E-PER
, O

Louis B-PER
Mullins E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O

Imai B-PER
Namboku E-PER
, O

Zachariah B-PER
Hicks E-PER
, O



Shen B-PER
Su E-PER
, O

Anees B-PER
Davis E-PER
, O

Rojin B-PER
Shepard E-PER
, O

Rania B-PER
Fletcher E-PER
, O
<i> O

Avantas B-PER
Ghosal E-PER
, O

Kimberley B-PER
Landry E-PER
, O

Terri B-PER
Cobb E-PER
, O

Kane B-PER
Snow E-PER
, O

Qasim B-PER
Rigby E-PER
<i> O
Shanghai B-ORG
University E-ORG
at O

Milo B-PER
Stark E-PER
<i> O

Adelina B-PER
Potter E-PER
, O

Kase B-PER
Gesshin E-PER
, O
Western B-ORG
Sydney I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Tufts B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
of I-ORG

Ping B-PER
Fu E-PER
<i> O
Lincoln B-ORG
University E-ORG
and O
of I-ORG
Bonn E-ORG

Ehsan B-PER
Millar E-PER
<i> O


editorialboard ROLE
placeholder O

</i> O
Sultan B-ORG
Qaboos I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Mellon I-ORG






University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Delhi E-ORG
( O
Okanaga S-LOC




USA S-LOC



Mu O
National B-ORG
Tsing I-ORG
Hua I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Zakariah B-PER
Ahmad E-PER
, O
</b> O
Rice B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<i> O
<b> O
Yao B-PER
Yating E-PER
, O
of O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Florida B-ORG

Samson B-PER
Abramsky E-PER
, O
IE B-ORG
IE I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

John B-PER
Vincent I-PER
Atanasoff E-PER
, O
</b> O
Informatica O
, O

Bluebell B-PER
Le E-PER
, O
</b> O
Griffith B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Arabia E-LOC

Nieve B-PER
Mckenzie E-PER
, O
SOAS B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

Sapienza B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Rome E-ORG
, O
</b> O
Hoboken S-LOC

Raj B-PER
Reddy E-PER
, O
Tel B-ORG
Aviv I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Zainab B-PER
Whitmore E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Coimbra E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Ruby-Mae B-PER
Joseph E-PER
, O
Rutgers B-ORG
UniversityNew I-ORG
Brunswick E-ORG
, O

Landon B-PER
Dudley E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cologne E-ORG
, O

Trygve B-PER
Reenskaug E-PER
, O
Technische B-ORG
Universitt I-ORG
Darmstadt E-ORG
, O

Chen B-PER
Heng E-PER
</b> O
Pontificia B-ORG
Universidad I-ORG
Catlica I-ORG
Argentina E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

Steve B-PER
Lawrence E-PER
</b> O

Vijai B-PER
Sritharan E-PER
</b> O
Nanjing B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Passau S-LOC

<b> O
Matteo B-PER
Ritter E-PER
</b> O
Complutense B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG
, O
Guildford S-LOC


class O
"> O

Lisa B-PER
Anthony E-PER
, O
Chung-Ang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Editorial B-ROLE

Jorja B-PER
Armitage E-PER
, O
Wageningen B-ORG
University I-ORG
& I-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O

Gbor B-PER
Tardos E-PER
, O
Lund B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

David B-PER
S. I-PER
Johnson E-PER
, O
Qatar B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

To B-PER
Young-Nam E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O

Amaan B-PER
Fleming E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oslo E-ORG
, O

Bernard B-PER
Galler E-PER
, O
Radboud B-ORG
University E-ORG
. O
, O


=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
placeholder-editorialBoard O

He B-PER
Hua E-PER
, O
Universitat B-ORG
de I-ORG
Barcelona E-ORG
, O

Alfred B-PER
Aho E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich E-ORG
, O

Yoshie B-PER
Soshitsu E-PER
, O
Rensselaer B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O

Joyce B-PER
K. I-PER
Reynolds E-PER
, O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Kanpur E-ORG
, O


Professor O


Rex B-PER
Hobbs E-PER
( O


<b> O
Ono B-PER
Yuifum E-PER
( O

<b> O
Ono B-PER
Yuifum E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Twente E-ORG
, O

<b> O
Scott B-PER
Aaronson E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambridge E-ORG
( O
IIIA-CSIC S-ORG
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Louis B-PER
Mullins E-PER
</b> O
Universit B-ORG
Laval E-ORG
, O

Kano B-PER
Seison E-PER
</b> O
La B-ORG
Trobe I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

John B-PER
Vincent I-PER
Atanasoff E-PER
</b> O
, O
Beijing B-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Divine B-PER
Sierra E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waikato E-ORG
, O

<b> O
JOURNAL O


Chino B-PER
Korekiyo E-PER
</b> O
The B-ORG
Ohio I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
va B-PER
Tardos E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nottingham E-ORG
, O

Matsuzaki B-PER
Takahiro E-PER
</b> O
Grenoble E-PER

<b> O
C. B-PER
J. I-PER
van I-PER
Rijsbergen E-PER
</b> O
L.N. B-ORG
Gumilyov I-ORG
Eurasian I-ORG
National I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Kyo B-PER
Do-Hyun E-PER
</b> O
, O
Newcastle B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Stephanie B-PER
Wolfe E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bergen E-ORG
, O

John B-PER
C. I-PER
Reynolds E-PER
</b> O
Mahidol B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Lisa B-PER
Gelobter E-PER
</b> O
Loughborough B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Yaseen B-PER
Gallagher E-PER
</b> O
, O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Buenos I-ORG
Aires E-ORG
, O

<b> O


J. O
Paula B-PER
Steele E-PER
, O

Ryom B-PER
Jae-Wook E-PER
, O

Mangjol B-PER
Yeon-Woo E-PER
, O

Zhang B-PER
Jian E-PER
, O

Ch'u B-PER
Jong-Soo E-PER
, O

Gabrielius B-PER
Reeve E-PER
, O

Leen B-PER
Hensley E-PER
, O
du I-PER


id O


University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas I-ORG
at I-ORG
Austin E-ORG
( O

<b> O

Universiti B-ORG
Teknologi I-ORG
Brunei E-ORG
, O

</b> O
RUDN B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

@ O

Taguchi B-PER
Masafumi E-PER
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Birmingham E-ORG
, O

David B-PER
P. I-PER
Reed E-PER
, O
Pontificia B-ORG
Universidad I-ORG
Catlica I-ORG
del I-ORG
Per E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Takai B-PER
Eishi E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Twente E-ORG
di I-PER

Trygve B-PER
Reenskaug E-PER
</b> O
Brandeis B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

@ O

Scott B-PER
Fahlman E-PER
</b> O
, O
National B-ORG
Sun I-ORG
Yat-sen I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Bernard B-PER
Galler E-PER
</b> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Munich E-ORG
, O



Qian B-PER
Wuhan E-PER
, O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Delhi E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Edward B-PER
Feigenbaum E-PER
, O
Concordia B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Dave B-PER
Oliver E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wisconsin-Madison E-ORG
, O

Edward B-PER
D. I-PER
Lazowska E-PER
, O
ETH B-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
- I-ORG
Swiss I-ORG
Federal I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O

<b> O

( O
– O
) O
Julius-Maximilians-Universitt B-ORG
Wrzburg E-ORG
, O
, O



</i> O
Blossom B-PER
Nguyen E-PER
, O
<i> O

<b> O
Fern B-PER
Sanchez E-PER
, O

Valerie B-PER
Taylor E-PER
, O
<i> O



Kobe B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Science E-ORG

Sally B-PER
Floyd E-PER
Robinson I-ORG
College I-ORG


Shirley B-PER
Kaufman E-PER
University O

</b> O
Liao B-PER
Jun E-PER
and O
McMaster B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

<b> O


Northeastern B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Institute I-ORG
Technology E-ORG


- B-ORG
Indian I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Roorkee E-ORG
, O






Bill B-PER
Gates E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Victoria E-ORG
, O

Kristen B-PER
Haley E-PER
, O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Zaragoza E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Elle-May B-PER
Doyle E-PER
, O
Lomonosov B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Tyreke B-PER
Moses E-PER
, O
Sultan B-ORG
Qaboos I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Cao B-PER
Xinyi E-PER
, O
Ben B-ORG
Gurion I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
The I-ORG
Negev E-ORG
, O





Alagesan B-PER
Poduri E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
at I-ORG
Buffalo I-ORG
SUNY E-ORG
, O

Yang B-PER
Hai E-PER
</b> O
Hitotsubashi B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Pok B-PER
Chunyong E-PER
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kansas E-ORG
Council E-ROLE
Canada S-LOC


EPFL B-ORG
- I-ORG
Ecole I-ORG
Polytechnique I-ORG
Federale I-ORG
de I-ORG
Lausanne E-ORG
, O

The B-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Korea E-ORG
at O
Chicago S-LOC
USA S-LOC
and O
University E-ORG

<b> O
Johnnie B-PER
Britton E-PER
, O
Chung-Ang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
of I-ORG

Eduardo B-PER
Finney E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O

<b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Essex E-ORG
, O


Cecily B-PER
Ventura E-PER
, O
Brown B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

D.R.Fulkerson B-PER
, O
Universidad B-ORG
Autnoma I-ORG
de I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG
, O

Kornelia B-PER
Blackwell E-PER
, O
Ewha B-ORG
Womans I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O

Raj B-PER
Reddy E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bergen E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
University B-ORG
USA S-LOC

Chantelle B-PER
Blaese E-PER
, O
Director O
Korea B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
University I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
Kong E-LOC

Izabelle B-PER
Sinclair E-PER
, O
Qatar B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Slovenia S-LOC

Augustus B-PER
Quinn E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Groningen E-ORG
( O
, O
of I-ORG
, O

Yao B-PER
Yating E-PER
, O
Universiti B-ORG
Brunei I-ORG
Darussalam E-ORG
, O

Jitendra B-PER
Choudhary E-PER
, O
Universidade B-ORG
de I-ORG
So I-ORG
Paulo E-ORG
, O
of I-ORG

D.R.Fulkerson B-PER
, O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
los I-ORG
Andes E-ORG
, O

Dave B-PER
Oliver E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
Montenegro S-LOC

Okabe B-PER
Yuichi E-PER
, O
Vanderbilt B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Augustus B-PER
Quinn E-PER
, O
Universiti B-ORG
Sains I-ORG
Malaysia E-ORG
, O
Graz B-ORG
of I-ORG
Austria S-LOC

<i> O
in I-ROLE
and O
