giusti O
@ O

Syracuse S-LOC
, O
NY S-LOC
13244-4100 O
, O
USA S-LOC

SPAIN S-LOC

hderksen O
@ O

<b> O
Deepak B-PER
Kapur E-PER

Palaiseau S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

KIT S-LOC
, O
Karlsruhe S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

kus O
@ O

<b> O
Pablo B-PER
Solerno E-PER

<b> O
Henning B-PER
Fernau E-PER
</b> O
, O
Universität B-PER
Trier E-PER
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Gerwin B-PER
Klein E-PER
</b> O
, O
NICTA S-LOC
, O
Kensington S-LOC
, O
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
Sydney S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Founding B-ROLE
Editors ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Friedrich B-PER
L. I-PER
Bauer E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
München E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<i> O
<b> O
Senior B-ROLE
Associate BI-ROLE
Editor ROLE

<b> O
Rita B-PER
Osadchy E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Haifa E-ORG

<b> O
Onn B-PER
Shehory E-PER
</b> O
( O
Bar-Ilan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

CMS B-ORG
Faculty I-ORG
of I-ORG
Music E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambridge E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</b> O
De B-ORG
Montfort I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE

email O
: O
organ30001 O
@ O

<b> O
Daniel B-PER
Dennett E-PER
, O
</b> O
Tufts B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Medford S-LOC
, O
MA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Ivan B-PER
da I-PER
Costa I-PER
Marques E-PER
, O
</b> O
Federal B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Rio B-LOC
de I-LOC
Janeiro E-LOC
, O
Brazil S-LOC

<b> O
Parthasarathi B-PER
Banerjee E-PER
, O
</b> O
International B-ORG
Management I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
Delhi E-LOC

<b> O
Seth B-PER
D. I-PER
Baum E-PER
, O
</b> O
Global O
Catastrophic O
Risk O
Institute O
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Nic B-PER
Bidwell E-PER
, O
</b> O
The O
International B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Management E-ORG
, O
Namibia S-LOC

<b> O
Ghislaine B-PER
Boddington E-PER
, O
</b> O
body O
& O
gt O
; O
data O
& O
gt O
; O
space O
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Stephen B-PER
Cowley E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
Georgi B-PER
Marko I-PER
Dimirovski E-PER
, O
</b> O
St. B-LOC
Cyril E-LOC
and O
St. B-LOC
Methodius I-LOC
University I-LOC
of I-LOC
Skopje E-LOC
, O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
Macedonia E-LOC

<b> O
Alla B-PER
G. I-PER
Kravets E-PER
, O
</b> O
Volgograd B-ORG
State I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Russia S-LOC

<b> O
Aldo B-PER
de I-PER
Moor E-PER
, O
</b> O
CommunitySense S-LOC
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<b> O
Tao B-PER
Jiang E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
Riverside S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Robert B-PER
Sedgewick E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Princeton B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Chris B-PER
Umans E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
California B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Guido B-PER
Governatori E-PER
</i> O
, O
NICTA O
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
E-government O
and O
Lawyering O

</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Erich B-PER
Schweighofer E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Vienna E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<i> O
Graham B-PER
Greenleaf E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<i> O
Jeroen B-PER
Keppens E-PER
</i> O
, O
King B-ORG
’s I-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<i> O
Vern B-PER
R. I-PER
Walker E-PER
</i> O
, O
Maurice B-ORG
A. I-ORG
Deane I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law E-ORG
at O
Hofstra B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hempstead S-LOC
, O
NY S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
John B-PER
Zeleznikow E-PER
</i> O
, O
Victoria B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Thomas B-PER
S. I-PER
Ray E-PER
, O
Oklahoma S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Yong-Guang B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Takayasu B-PER
Fuchida E-PER
, O
Kagoshima S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Hee-Hyol B-PER
Lee E-PER
, O
Kitakyushu S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Henrik B-PER
Hautop I-PER
Lund E-PER
, O
Odense S-LOC
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Shinichi B-PER
Sagara E-PER
, O
Kitakyushu S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Sigeru B-PER
Omatu E-PER
, O
Osaka S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Steen B-PER
Rasmussen E-PER
, O
Santa B-LOC
Fe E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE
: O

<b> O
Vincent B-PER
Conitzer E-PER
</b> O
, O
Duke B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Lluís B-PER
Godo E-PER
</b> O
, O
Spanish B-ORG
National I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Council E-ROLE
, O
SPAIN S-LOC

<b> O
Chunyan B-PER
Miao E-PER
, O
</b> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
SINGAPORE S-LOC

<b> O
Paul B-PER
Scerri E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jaime B-PER
Simão I-PER
Sichman E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
São B-LOC
Paulo E-LOC
, O
BRAZIL S-LOC

<b> O
Pingzhong B-PER
Tang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
CHINA S-LOC

<b> O
Gerhard B-PER
Weiss E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maastricht E-ORG
, O
THE B-LOC
NETHERLANDS E-LOC

<b> O
Robert B-PER
J. I-PER
Hall E-PER

</i> O
<b> O
Gerhard B-PER
Fischer E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Michael B-PER
Jackson E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
The O
Open B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Michael B-PER
R. I-PER
Lowry E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
NASA B-ORG
Ames I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Yoky B-PER
Matsuoka E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Washington E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</b> O
Guangdong B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Guangzhou S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC
, O
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Illinois E-ORG
at O
Chicago S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Erik B-PER
Cambria E-PER

<b> O
Amir B-PER
Hussain E-PER

<b> O
Takayuki B-PER
Ito E-PER

Zuoning B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
National B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center I-ORG
of I-ORG
Parallel I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Engineering I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Ninghui B-ORG
Sun E-ORG
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Xing B-ORG
Cai E-ORG
, O
Simula B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Lab E-ORG
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oslo E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

Xiaosong B-PER
Ma E-PER
, O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Jiannong B-PER
Cao E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Dakuo B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
IBM B-ORG
T.J E-ORG
. O
Watson B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Xing-Dong B-PER
Yang E-PER
, O
Dartmouth B-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Founding B-ROLE
Editors ROLE

Katja B-PER
Kircher E-PER
, O
VTI S-ORG
( O
Swedish B-ORG
National I-ORG
Road I-ORG
and I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
) O
, O
Sweden S-LOC

Michel B-PER
A I-PER
Masson E-PER
, O
European B-ORG
Union I-ORG
Aviation I-ORG
Safety I-ORG
Agency E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

David B-PER
D I-PER
Woods E-PER
, O
Ohio B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

Falko B-PER
Dressler E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Paderborn E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Xing B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Radu B-PER
Stoleru E-PER
, O
Texas B-ORG
A I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
M I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Book B-ROLE
Review BI-ROLE
Editor ROLE
: O
</i> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Advisory BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

<b> O
Geoffrey B-PER
C. I-PER
Bowker E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
Irvine S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Elihu O
</b> O
<b> O
Gerson S-PER
, O
</b> O
Tremont B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Antonietta B-PER
Grasso E-PER
, O
</b> O
Naver B-ORG
Labs I-ORG
Europe E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Paul B-PER
K. I-PER
Luff E-PER
, O
</b> O
King O
’s O
College O
London S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Giorgio B-PER
De I-PER
Michelis E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Milano-Bicocca E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Carman B-PER
Neustaedter E-PER
</b> O
, O
Simon B-PER
Fraser E-PER
University O
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Volker B-PER
Wulf E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Siegen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Harald B-PER
C. I-PER
Gall E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich E-ORG

<b> O
George B-PER
Pallis E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cyprus E-ORG
, O
Nicosia S-LOC

<b> O
Sabri B-PER
Pllana E-PER
</b> O
, O
Linnaeus B-ORG
University E-ORG

<b> O
Rajiv B-PER
Ranjan E-PER
</b> O
, O
Newcastle B-ORG
University E-ORG

E-mail O
: O
balu O
@ O

Prof. O
Gautam B-PER
Barua E-PER

Hyderabad S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

E-mail O
: O
venkat O
@ O

IIT B-ORG
Mumbai E-ORG

India S-LOC

Former O

Bangalore S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

CTO S-ORG
, O
Strand B-ORG
Genomics E-ORG

IIIT B-ORG
Allahabad E-ORG

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

Hubei B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
LETTERS O
EDITOR ROLE

<b> O
Christian B-PER
Bessiere E-PER
</b> O
, O
LIRMM O
( O
CNRS S-LOC
/ O
Univ. B-LOC
Montpellier E-LOC
) O
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Michele B-PER
Lombardi E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Bart B-PER
Selman E-PER
</b> O
, O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Songcan B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
Parnec B-ORG
CHINA E-ORG

Alexander B-PER
Felfernig E-PER
, O
Graz B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
AUSTRIA S-LOC

Bogdan B-PER
Filipic E-PER
, O
Jozef B-PER
Stefan I-PER
Institute E-PER
, O
SLOVENIA S-LOC

Igor B-PER
Kononenko E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
Of I-ORG
Ljublijana E-ORG
, O
SLOVENIA S-LOC

Kishan B-PER
G. I-PER
Mehrotra E-PER
, O
Syracuse B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

</i> O
<b> O
Eamonn B-PER
Keogh E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
Riverside S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Nikolaj B-PER
Tatti E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Helsinki B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Aalto B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC
</i> O

</b> O
</i> O
<b> O
Albrecht B-PER
Zimmerman E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Universite B-ORG
Caen I-ORG
Normandie E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Bruno B-PER
Cr E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
émilleux O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Universite B-ORG
de I-ORG
Caen I-ORG
Normandie E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
João B-PER
Gama E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Porto E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Eyke B-PER
Hüllermeier E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Paderborn E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Meng B-PER
Jiang E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Notre I-ORG
Dame E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Bernhard B-PER
Pfahringer E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waikato E-ORG
, O
Hamilton S-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jilles B-PER
Vreeken E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Max B-ORG
Planck I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
for I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG
and O
Saarland B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC
</i> O

<b> O
Honorary O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

</i> O
<b> O
M O
. O
Albrecht S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Royal B-ORG
Holloway E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jung B-PER
Hee I-PER
Cheon E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Seoul B-ORG
National I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
South B-LOC
Korea E-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
T O
. O
Etzion O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Technion O
IIT O
, O
Israel S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
T O
. O
Helleseth O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bergen E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

<b> O
J. O
- O
L O
. O
Kim S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Sogang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
South B-LOC
Korea E-LOC

<b> O
M O
. O
Lavrauw S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Padua E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
G O
. O
McGuire S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
Dublin E-ORG
, O
Ireland S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
L O
. O
Storme O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Ghent B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Belgium S-LOC

</i> O
Christoforos B-ORG
Hadjicostis E-ORG
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cyprus E-ORG
, O
Cyprus S-LOC

Sophie B-PER
Pinchinat E-PER
, O
<i> O
IRISA O
, O
Universitairé B-ORG
de I-ORG
Rennes E-ORG
1 O
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
Rong B-PER
Su E-PER
, O
<i> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

Manuel B-PER
Silva E-PER
, O
<i> O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Zaragoza E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

David B-PER
D. I-PER
Yao E-PER
, O
<i> O
Columbia B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

<b> O
Founding B-ROLE
Editor ROLE
: O

Wil B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Aalst E-PER
, O
<i> O
Technische B-ORG
Universiteit I-ORG
Eindhoven E-ORG
, O
Netherlands S-LOC

Sunil B-PER
Prabhakar E-PER
, O
<i> O
Purdue B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Feifei B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Utah E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Azza B-PER
Abouzied E-PER
, O
<i> O
NYU O
Abu B-LOC
Dhabi E-LOC
, O
UAE S-LOC

Kaushik B-PER
Chakrabarti E-PER
, O
<i> O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Sudipto B-PER
Das E-PER
, O
<i> O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Zhiguo B-PER
Gong E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Macau E-ORG
, O
Macau S-LOC

Takahiro B-PER
Hara E-PER
<i> O
, O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Mourad B-PER
Ouzzani E-PER
, O
<i> O
Qatar B-ORG
Computing I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Qatar S-LOC

Florin B-PER
Rusu E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California I-ORG
Merced E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Shazia B-PER
Sadiq E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Queensland E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Jagan B-PER
Sankaranarayanan E-PER
, O
<i> O
Google O
, O
USA S-LOC

Stratis B-ORG
Viglas E-ORG
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Peleg E-PER

<b> O
Davide B-PER
Sangiorgi E-PER

<b> O
Fred B-PER
B. I-PER
Schneider E-PER

</i> O
<b> O
Monique B-PER
Grandbastien E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Lorraine E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Robert B-PER
Feldt E-PER

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

</i> O
<b> O
Eric B-PER
Bodden E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Heinz B-ORG
Nixdorf I-ORG
Institut E-ORG
at O
Paderborn B-ORG
University I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
Fraunhofer B-ORG
IEM E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Paul B-PER
Grünbacher E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Johannes B-ORG
Kepler I-ORG
University I-ORG
Linz E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Dan B-PER
Hao E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Zhi B-PER
Jin E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Emerson B-PER
Murphy-Hill E-PER
<i> O
, O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O

</div> O

Director O
Scientific B-ORG
Computation I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
Rensselaer B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Troy S-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
York E-LOC
12180-3590 O
, O
USA S-LOC

Sandia B-ORG
National I-ORG
Laboratories E-ORG
, O
Albuquerque S-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
Mexico E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Robert B-PER
H. I-PER
Dodds E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Illinois E-ORG
, O
Urbana S-LOC
, O
Illinois S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Assad B-PER
A. I-PER
Oberai E-PER

Yongjie B-PER
Jessica I-PER
Zhang E-PER

<b> O
<i> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

</b> O
Dept. O
of O
Philosophy O
, O
Delft B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
The B-ORG
Netherlands I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
Centre B-ORG
for I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Philosophy I-ORG
and I-ORG
Public I-ORG
Ethics E-ORG
, O
The O
Australian B-ORG
National I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canberra S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Co-Editor ROLE

Herman B-PER
Tavani E-PER

</i> O
<b> O
Philip B-PER
Brey E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
Twente E-ORG
, O
Enschede S-LOC
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Richard B-PER
T. I-PER
De I-PER
George E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kansas E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Dag B-PER
Elgesem E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
</<E-ORG> O
i> O
<i> O
Bergen S-LOC
, O
Norway S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Simon S-PER
</b> O
<b> O
Rogerson S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
De B-PER
Montfort E-PER
</i> O
<i> O
University O
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
John B-PER
Weckert E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Charles B-PER
Sturt E-PER
</i> O
<i> O
University O
, O
Canberra S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Steve B-PER
Woolgar E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

email O
: O
jim.woodcock O
@ O

Loughborough B-ORG
University E-ORG

Loughborough S-LOC
, O
LE11 S-LOC
3TU O
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Prof. O
J. B-PER
M. I-PER
Wing E-PER

</b> O
550 O
W O
. O
120th O
St. O
MC O
4720 O

NY O
10027 O
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Prof. O
C. B-PER
B. I-PER
Jones E-PER

<b> O
Prof. B-PER
M. I-PER
J. I-PER
Butler E-PER

<b> O
Prof. O
Ana B-PER
Cavalcanti E-PER

email O
: O
ewen.w.denney O
@ O

( O
Formal O
methods O
in I-ROLE
human-computer O
interaction O
; O
Visualization O
; O
Graphics O
; O
Functional O
programming O
) O

( O
Formal O
methods O
; O
Software O
specification O
; O
Specification-based O
testing O
; O
Testing O
strategies O

<b> O
Prof. O
J. B-PER
Nuno I-PER
Oliveira E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Augsburg E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Software I-ORG
and I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
( O
ISSE S-ORG
) O
, O
Universitaetsstrasse O
<B-MISC> O
6a O
<E-MISC> O
, O
86159 O
Augsburg S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

</b> O
<b> O
John B-PER
M. I-PER
Watts E-PER
Jr O
. O
, O
</b> O
Fire B-ORG
Safety I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Middlebury S-LOC
, O
VT S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Steve B-PER
M.V E-PER
. O
Gwynne S-PER
, O
</b> O
NRC S-ORG
, O
Ottawa S-LOC
, O
ON S-LOC
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Xinyan B-PER
Huang E-PER
, O
</b> O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

<b> O
Eleni B-PER
Asimakopoulou E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Central I-ORG
Lancashire E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

<b> O
Katherine B-PER
A. I-PER
Cashell E-PER
</b> O
, O
Brunel B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
United B-ORG
Kongdom E-ORG

<b> O
Ofodike B-PER
A. I-PER
Ezekoye E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Alberto B-PER
Fina E-PER
, O
</b> O
Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Torino E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Tuula B-PER
Hakkarainen E-PER
</b> O
, O
VTT B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
of I-ORG
Finland I-ORG
Ltd E-ORG
. O
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Ruggiero B-PER
Lovreglio E-PER
, O
</b> O
Massey B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

<b> O
Juan B-PER
Hidalgo I-PER
Medina E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Queensland E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Ruben B-PER
Van I-PER
Coile E-PER
</b> O
, O
Ghent B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Belgium S-LOC

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

Cross-media O
intelligence O
, O
big O
data O

Xin-ping B-PER
Guan E-PER

F. B-PER
Richard I-PER
Yu E-PER

Carleton B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Tongji B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Ji-ming B-PER
Chen E-PER

Xidian B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Computer O
science O
& O
amp O
; O

Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Czestochowa E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC

Colin B-PER
Sheppard E-PER

Networked O
control O

University O
of O
Peradeniya S-LOC
, O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka E-LOC

Laurence B-PER
T. I-PER
Yang E-PER

Jun-ping B-PER
Zhang E-PER

Wireless O
communications O
and O
networking O
, O
signal O
and O
information O

Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Wen B-ORG
GAO I-ORG
Peking I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Wei B-ORG
ZHAO I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Macau E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jian B-ORG
ZHANG I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Software E-ORG
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Fujisaka B-ORG
Hisato I-ORG
Hiroshima I-ORG
City I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

M. B-PER
Tamer I-PER
Özsu E-PER
University O
of O
Waterloo S-LOC
, O
Canada S-LOC

Shiguang B-ORG
SHAN I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Computing I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Area O
Editor ROLE
for O
Life B-ORG
Sciences E-ORG

Moshe B-PER
Sipper E-PER
, O
<i> O
Ben-Gurion B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

<b> O
Baihua B-PER
Zheng E-PER
, O
</b> O
Singapore B-ORG
Management I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

<b> O
Leila B-PER
DeFloriani E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Genova E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Mike B-PER
Goodchild E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Tapani B-PER
Sarjakoski E-PER
, O
</b> O
Finnish B-ORG
Geospatial I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
FGI O
, O
Helsinki S-LOC
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
J O
. O
Shane B-PER
Culpepper E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
RMIT B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Melbourne S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jaana B-PER
Kekäläinen E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tampere E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Massimo B-PER
Melucci E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Padua E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Edie B-PER
Rasmussen E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
British I-ORG
Columbia E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Arjen B-PER
P. I-PER
de I-PER
Vries E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Radboud B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC
</i> O


</i> O
Kristen B-PER
Grauman E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC

<b> O
Christoph B-PER
Lampert E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
IST O
Austria S-LOC

</i> O
Zhouchen B-PER
Lin E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG

</i> O
Yasuhiro B-PER
Mukaigawa E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG

</i> O
Florent B-PER
Perronnin E-PER
<i> O
, O
NAVER O
LABS O
Europe S-LOC
</i> O
</b> O

</i> O
Yoichi B-PER
Sato E-PER
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
, O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tokyo E-ORG

</i> O
</b> O
<b> O
Kwan-Yee B-PER
Kenneth I-PER
Wong E-PER
, O
<i> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong E-ORG

<b> O
Dieter B-PER
Gollmann E-PER

<b> O
Joonsang B-PER
Baek E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wollongong E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Elisa B-PER
Bertino E-PER
</b> O
, O
Purdue B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
West B-LOC
Lafayette E-LOC
, O
IN I-ROLE
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Mark B-PER
Manulis E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Surrey E-ORG
, O
Guildford S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

Rolf B-PER
Oppliger E-PER
</b> O
, O
eSECURITY B-ORG
Technologies E-ORG
, O
Bern S-LOC
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

<b> O
Mark B-PER
D I-PER
Ryan E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Birmingham E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Vincent B-PER
Aleven E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Danielle B-PER
McNamara E-PER
</b> O
, O
Arizona B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Ido B-PER
Roll E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
British I-ORG
Columbia E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

</i> O
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O
</b> O
<b> O
<i> O
</i> O

<b> O
Andrew B-PER
Olney E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Memphis E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jonathan B-PER
Rowe E-PER
</b> O
, O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Valerie B-PER
Shute E-PER
</b> O
, O
Florida B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Philip B-PER
Winne E-PER
</b> O
, O
Simon B-PER
Fraser E-PER
University O
, O
Canada S-LOC

Ireland S-LOC

Associate BI-ROLE
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
( O
Academia S-ORG
) O

<b> O
Sten B-PER
F. I-PER
Andler E-PER

<b> O
Harold B-PER
" I-PER
Bud I-PER
" I-PER
Lawson E-PER

</b> O
Lawson B-ORG
Konsult I-ORG
AB E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

</div> O

Santosh B-PER
Devasia E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Washington E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yunhua B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
Beihang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Xinjun B-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Kenn B-PER
R. I-PER
Oldham E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Wei B-PER
Chong E-PER
, O
Beijing B-ORG
Jiaotong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Keping B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
Tongji B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Evangelos B-PER
Mitsakis E-PER
, O
Hellenic B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Transport E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

Hiroko B-PER
Mori E-PER
, O
Aichi B-ORG
Shukutoku I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Hiroaki B-PER
Nishiuchi E-PER
, O
Kochi B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Nobuyuki B-PER
Ozaki E-PER
, O
Nagoya B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Jun B-PER
Sakamoto E-PER
, O
Kochi B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Kazunori B-PER
Shidoji E-PER
, O
Kyushu B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

</i> O
<b> O
Paraskevas B-PER
Evripidou E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cyprus E-ORG
, O
Cyprus S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
José B-PER
A.B E-PER
. O
Fortes S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Kazuki B-PER
Joe E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Nara B-ORG
Women I-ORG
's I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Arun B-PER
Kejariwal E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Twitter O
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
David B-PER
J. I-PER
Kuck E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Illinois E-ORG
at O
</i> O
<i> O
Urbana-Champaign S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Yoichi B-PER
Muraoka E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Waseda B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Keshav S-PER
</b> O
<b> O
Pingali S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
, O
Austin S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Harry B-PER
Wijshoff E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Leiden B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Advanced I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
The B-ORG
Netherlands E-ORG

<b> O
Senior B-ROLE
Editors ROLE

<b> O
Mark B-PER
Zhang E-PER

<b> O
Alberto B-PER
del I-PER
Bimbo E-PER

<b> O
Tat-Seng B-PER
Chua E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
East I-ORG
Anglia E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Joemon B-PER
Jose E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southampton E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
S O
. O
Marchand-Maillet S-PER

<b> O
Yong B-PER
Rui E-PER

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE

Tel O
. O
: O
+ O

lopresti O
@ O

Buffalo S-LOC
, O
NY S-LOC
14260-2500 O
, O
USA S-LOC

Boise S-LOC
, O
Idaho S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

liucl O
@ O

Braunschweig B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG

jean-marc.ogier O
@ O

Montreal S-LOC
, O
Quebec S-LOC
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
S O
. O
Setlur S-PER

setlur O
@ O

Spain S-LOC

ernest O
@ O

<b> O
R O
. O
Zanibbi S-PER

rxzvcs O
@ O

<b> O
<i> O
Executive B-ROLE
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
</i> O

1090 O
Vienna S-LOC
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
Furuta E-PER

Tel O
. O
+ O
1 O
( O
979 O
) O

<b> O
Ingo B-PER
Frommholz E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bedfordshire E-ORG

54792 O
Lahore S-LOC
, O
Pakistan S-LOC

Ireland S-LOC

VERIMAG S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<i> O
( O
Verification O
and O
Embedded O
Systems O
) O

Chin-Teng B-PER
Lin E-PER
, O
National B-ORG
Chiao-Tung I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Nishanth B-PER
Chandran E-PER
, O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research I-ORG
India I-ORG
Bangalore E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

Ugo B-PER
Fiore E-PER
, O
Parthenope B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Peter B-PER
Müller E-PER
, O
</b> O
ETH B-LOC
Zürich E-LOC
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

<b> O
Andreas B-PER
Podelski E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Freiburg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Christoph B-PER
Weidenbach E-PER
, O
</b> O
Max-Planck-Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Professor O
, O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Melbourne E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
Davis S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Professor O
, O
School B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

Professor O
, O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

Professor O
, O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Alabama E-ORG
, O
Tuscaloosa S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Sharif B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Tehran S-LOC
, O
Iran S-LOC

Professor O
, O
Computer B-ORG
Engineering I-ORG
Department E-ORG

<b> O
Florin B-PER
Popentiu I-PER
Vlãdicescu E-PER

Bath B-ORG
Spa I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Leading O
Editors ROLE

David B-PER
Z. I-PER
Pan E-PER
<i> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC
, O
Austin S-LOC

Weisong B-ORG
Shi E-ORG
<i> O
Wayne B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Detroit S-LOC

Ji-Wu B-PER
Huang E-PER
<i> O
Shenzhen B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Shenzhen S-LOC

Chong-Wah B-ORG
Ngo E-ORG
<i> O
City B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

Jian B-ORG
Lv I-ORG
<<I-ORG> O
i O
<I-ORG>> O
Nanjing B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Nanjing S-LOC

<b> O
Computer O
Architecture O
and O
Systems O

Ji-Dong B-PER
Zhai E-PER
<i> O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC

Jing B-PER
Liu E-PER
<i> O
Ins O
. O
Automation O
, O
CAS O
, O
Beijing S-LOC

<b> O
Software O
Systems O

<b> O
Grégoire B-PER
JACOB E-PER
</b> O
, O
Télécom B-PER
SudParis E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Grant B-PER
MALCOLM E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Université B-ORG
catholique I-ORG
de I-ORG
Louvain E-ORG
, O
Belgium S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O
</i> O

<b> O
Debdeep B-PER
Mukhopadhyay E-PER
</b> O
, O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Kharagpur E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

Péter B-PER
Kacsuk E-PER
, O
MTA B-ORG
SZTAKI I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
and I-ORG
Automation I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Budapest S-LOC
, O
Hungary S-LOC
and O
the O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Westminster E-ORG
, O
London S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

Franck B-PER
Cappello E-PER
, O
CNRS S-ORG
, O
Paris S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

Jon B-PER
Crowcroft E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambridge E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Jack B-PER
Dongarra E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tennessee E-ORG
, O
Knoxville S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Fabrizio B-PER
Gagliardi E-PER
, O
Microsoft S-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Alexander B-PER
Reinefeld E-PER
, O
ZIB B-ORG
Berlin E-ORG
and O
Humboldt B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
zu I-ORG
Berlin E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Ramin B-PER
Yahyapour E-PER
, O
GWDG S-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

kenny.paterson O
@ O

<b> O
EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Serge B-PER
Fehr E-PER

64293 O
Darmstadt S-LOC

Fairfax S-LOC
, O
VA S-LOC

katz O
@ O

44780 O
Bochum S-ORG

eike.kiltz O
@ O

<b> O
Hugo B-PER
Krawczyk E-PER

New B-LOC
York E-LOC
, O
NY S-LOC

USA S-LOC

</b> O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG

Kasteelpark B-ORG
Arenberg E-ORG

Place B-ORG
de I-ORG
Levant E-ORG
, O

B-1348 O
Louvain-la-Neuve S-ORG

USA S-LOC

serge.vaudenay O
@ O

3001 O
Heverlee S-PER

Belgium S-LOC

<b> O
Larry B-PER
F. I-PER
Hodges E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Clemson B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Thomas B-PER
Karopka E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
European B-ORG
Federation I-ORG
for I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Qing B-PER
Qian E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Gregor B-PER
Stiglic E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maribor E-ORG
, O
Slovenia S-LOC

<b> O
Vincent B-PER
Tseng E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Chiao I-ORG
Tung I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

<b> O
Fei B-PER
Wang E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Daniela B-PER
Calvetti E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
CWRU O
, O
Cleveland S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Krzysztof B-PER
Chris I-PER
Ciesielski E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
West B-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
David B-PER
Coeurjolly E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
CNRS O
, O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Lyon E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Xue-Cheng B-PER
Tai E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Martin B-PER
Welk E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
for I-ORG
Health I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Medical B-ORG
Informatics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Sana B-PER
Ullah E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Polytechnic B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Porto E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

<b> O
Social O
Media O
Editor ROLE

<b> O
Giancarlo B-PER
Mauri E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Milano-Bicocca E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
K.G O
. O
Subramanian S-PER
</b> O
, O
Madras B-ORG
Christian I-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC


</i> O

</b> O
<b> O
M O
. O
Akil O
</b> O
, O
Ecole B-ORG
Supérieure I-ORG
d’Ingénieurs I-ORG
en I-ORG
Electronique I-ORG
et I-ORG
Electrotechnique E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
D O
. O
Ginhac O
</b> O
, O
Le2i O
UMR6306 O
- O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bourgogne E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
V O
. O
Ponomaryov S-PER
</b> O
, O
Instituto B-ORG
Politécnico I-ORG
Nacional E-ORG
, O
Mexico S-LOC

<b> O
Luciano B-PER
Paschoal I-PER
Gaspary E-PER

<b> O
Rémi B-PER
Badonnel E-PER
, O
</b> O
( O
IFIP O
WG O
6.6 O
Chair O
) O
, O
LORIA S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Paul B-PER
Brusil E-PER
, O
</b> O
Strategic O
Management O
Directions O
, O
Beverly S-LOC
, O
MA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Breitgand E-PER
</b> O
, O
IBM B-ORG
Haifa I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Lab E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Antonio B-PER
Liotta E-PER
, O
</b> O
Edinburgh B-ORG
Napier I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Malgorzata B-PER
Steinder E-PER
, O
</b> O
IBM O
T.J O
. O
Watson B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
Hawthorne S-LOC
, O
NY S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
T O
. O
Venkatesh O
, O
</b> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology-Guwahati E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

</div> O

Dept. O
of O
Electrical B-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
Princeton B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
NJ S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jarmo B-PER
Takala E-PER

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

</i> O
<b> O
Neal B-PER
Bambha E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
US B-ORG
Army I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Laboratory E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Andreas B-PER
Burg E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
EPFL O
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Joseph B-PER
Cavallaro E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Rice B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Edwin B-PER
Sha E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
</<E-ORG> O
i> O
<i> O
Notre B-ORG
Dame E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Chang B-PER
D. I-PER
Yoo E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
, O
KAIST O
, O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
Korea E-LOC

<b> O
Antonio B-PER
Coronato E-PER

Google S-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Alfredo B-PER
Cuzzocrea E-PER

<b> O
Kristof B-PER
Van I-PER
Laerhoven E-PER

<b> O
Paulo B-PER
Maciel E-PER

<b> O
Hedda B-PER
Schmidtke E-PER

<b> O
Hissam B-PER
Tawfik E-PER

Sotirios B-PER
Terzis E-PER

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Jean-Philippe B-PER
Thiran E-PER
, O
EPFL S-ORG
, O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
<i> O
Honorary O
Editors-ín-Chief O
</i> O

<b> O
Heiner B-PER
Stuckenschmidt E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Mannheim E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

Larry B-PER
Kerschberg E-PER
</b> O
, O
George B-ORG
Mason I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Michael B-PER
Kifer E-PER
</b> O
, O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG
at O
Stony B-LOC
Brook E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Klaus-Dieter B-PER
Schewe E-PER
</b> O
, O
Software O
Competence O
Center O
Hagenberg O
, O
Austria S-LOC

email O
: O
kais-eic O
@ O

email O
: O
kais-eic O
@ O

Berkeley S-LOC
, O
CA S-LOC

Josep B-PER
Domingo-Ferrer E-PER
, O
Universitat B-ORG
Rovira E-ORG
i O
Virgili S-PER
, O
Catalonia S-LOC

Ralf B-PER
Möller E-PER
, O
Universitat B-ORG
zu I-ORG
Lubeck E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Wamberto B-PER
Vasconcelos E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aberdeen E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

Yonggang B-PER
Wen E-PER
, O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

Bernd B-PER
Ludwig E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Regensburg E-ORG

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

</i> O
Paolo B-PER
Frasconi E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florence E-ORG

</i> O
Derek B-PER
Greene E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
Dublin E-ORG

Eyke B-PER
Hüllermeier E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Marburg E-ORG

Samy B-PER
Bengio E-PER
, O
<i> O
Google B-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc E-ORG
. O

</i> O
Colin B-PER
De I-PER
la I-PER
Higuera E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nantes E-ORG
</i> O

</i> O
Inderjit B-PER
Dhillon E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC

Tapio B-PER
Elomaa E-PER
, O
<i> O
Tampere B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

</i> O
Marcus B-PER
Hutter E-PER
<i> O
, O
Australian B-ORG
National I-ORG
University E-ORG

</i> O
Alexandros B-PER
Kalousis E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Geneva E-ORG

Adam B-PER
Klivans E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC

</i> O
John B-PER
Langford E-PER
<i> O
, O
Yahoo B-ORG
! I-ORG
Research E-ORG

</i> O
Phillip B-PER
Long E-PER
, O
<i> O
Google B-ORG
Research E-ORG

</i> O
Nina B-PER
Mishra E-PER
<i> O
, O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG

</i> O
Sriraam B-PER
Natarajan E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG

</i> O
Foster O
Provost O
<i> O
, O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O

</i> O
Jan B-PER
van I-PER
Rijn E-PER
, O
<i> O
Leiden B-ORG
University E-ORG

Maytal B-PER
Saar-Tsechansky E-PER
<i> O
, O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC

</i> O
Enver B-ORG
Sangineto E-ORG
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Trento E-ORG

</i> O
Michele B-ORG
Sebag E-ORG
<i> O
, O
Université B-ORG
Paris-Sud E-ORG

</i> O
Masashi B-PER
Sugiyama E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tokyo E-ORG

</i> O
Nikolaj B-ORG
Tatti E-ORG
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Helsinki E-ORG

Yee-Whye B-PER
Teh E-PER
<i> O
, O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG

<b> O
Editor ROLE
in I-ROLE
Chief E-ROLE
: O

</i> O
Gregory B-PER
R. I-PER
Wheeler E-PER
, O
<i> O
Frankfurt B-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
finance I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
Management E-ORG

Rahul B-PER
Sukthankar E-PER

USA S-LOC

Marius B-PER
Leordeanu E-PER

Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG

Jean-Marc B-PER
Odobez E-PER

IDIAP S-ORG

Devi B-PER
Parikh E-PER

Georgia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

Fairleigh B-ORG
Dickinson I-ORG
University E-ORG

Concetto B-ORG
Spampinato E-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Catania E-ORG

USA S-LOC


Anton B-PER
Kummert E-PER

<b> O
P O
. O
Agathoklis O
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Victoria E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Choon B-PER
Ki I-PER
Ahn E-PER
, O
PhD O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Korea B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Korea S-LOC
</i> O
; O
<b> O
O O
. O
Bachelier O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Poitiers E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
J.Cao O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Hangzhou B-ORG
Dianzi I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
C. O
- O
Y O
. O
Chang S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Yunlin I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC
</i> O
; O
<b> O
D O
. O
Fu O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Intel O
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
J O
. O
Han O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Northwestern B-ORG
Polytechnical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
N.P O
. O
Karampetakis O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Aristotle B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Thessaloniki E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC
</i> O
; O
<b> O
A.H O
. O
Kayran O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Istanbul B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Turkey S-LOC
</i> O
; O
<b> O
A O
. O
Khong O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
X O
. O
Lai O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Hangzhou B-ORG
Dianzi I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
B O
. O
Liao O
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Shenzhen B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
</i> O
<i> O
; O
</i> O
<b> O
A O
. O
Madanayake O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Akron E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Sasan B-ORG
Mahmoodi E-ORG
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southampton E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Marek B-PER
Majewski E-PER
, O
PhD O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Lodz E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
A O
. O
Makur O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
L O
. O
Ntogramatzidis O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Curtin B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
S O
. O
Oraintara O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
, O
Arlington S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
T-P B-ORG
Azevedo I-ORG
Perdicoulis E-ORG
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tras-os-Montes I-ORG
e I-ORG
Alto I-ORG
Douro E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
H O
. O
Pillai S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Indian B-ORG
Institue I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Bombay E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<i> O
</i> O
<b> O
A O
. O
Quadrat O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
INRIA O
Sarclay O
, O
France S-LOC
</i> O
; O
<b> O
R O
. O
Rabenstein O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
Erlangen-Nuremberg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
P O
. O
Rapisarda O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southampton E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
J O
. O
Ren O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Strathclyde E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
E O
. O
Skubalska-Rafajłowicz O
</b> O
<i> O
<b> O
, O
</b> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Wroclaw E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<i> O
</i> O
<b> O
J O
. O
Velten O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wuppertal E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Y O
. O
Wang O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Beijing B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chemical I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Y O
. O
Wu O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Bar-Ilan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
H O
. O
Zhao O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Fairleigh B-ORG
Dickinson I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
X O
. O
Zhuang O
, O
</b> O
<i> O
City B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong E-ORG
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

</div> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Marie B-PER
Katsurai E-PER
, O
</b> O
Doshisha B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Kyoto S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Rongrong B-PER
Ji E-PER
, O
</b> O
Xiamen B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Harald B-PER
Kosch E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Passau E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Clement B-PER
Leung E-PER
, O
</b> O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

<b> O
Qi B-PER
Wang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Northwestern B-ORG
Polytechnical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Nadrian B-PER
C. I-PER
Seeman E-PER
</b> O
, O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
York E-LOC
, O
NY S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Natalio B-PER
Krasnogor E-PER
</b> O
, O
Newcastle B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Newcastle S-LOC
upon O
Tyne S-LOC
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

<b> O
Jose B-PER
Principe E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O
Gainesville S-LOC
, O
FL S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Carme B-PER
Torras E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Barcelona E-ORG
, O
Barcelona S-LOC
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Stefan B-PER
Wermter E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Hamburg E-ORG
, O
Hamburg S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Przemysław B-PER
Prusinkiewicz E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Calgary E-ORG
, O
Calgary S-LOC
, O
AB S-LOC
, O
Canada S-LOC

Thomas B-PER
Schmidt E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
Odense S-LOC
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Konstantinos B-PER
Exarchos E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Ioannina E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

Mehmet B-PER
Tan E-PER
, O
TOBB B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Ankara S-LOC
, O
Turkey S-LOC

Tamer B-PER
Kahveci E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
at O
Gainesville S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Yanqing B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Georgia B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Atlanta S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Cognitive O

Noboru B-PER
Babaguchi E-PER
, O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Ken-ichi B-PER
Fukui E-PER
, O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Kohei B-PER
Hatano E-PER
, O
Kyushu B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Raymond B-PER
J. I-PER
Mooney E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Shojiro B-PER
Nishio E-PER
, O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Tomonobu B-PER
Ozaki E-PER
, O
Nihon B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Janusz B-PER
Sobecki E-PER
, O
Wroclaw B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC

Akihiko B-PER
Konagaya E-PER
, O
Tokyo B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

For O
all O
queries O
relating O
to O
papers O
after O
submission O
, O
please O
contact O
the O
Journal B-ORG
Editorial B-ROLE
Office E-ORG
only O
via O
“ O
contact O
us O
” O
at O
Editorial B-ROLE
Manager O
. O
Do O
not O
contact O
the O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
directly O

</b> O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Security E-ORG

Pakistan S-LOC

Batman B-ORG
University E-ORG


</b> O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Physics E-ORG

<b> O
Pablo B-PER
A. I-PER
Estevez E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Chile E-ORG
, O
Chile S-LOC

<b> O
Weinan B-PER
Gao E-PER
</b> O
, O
Georgia B-ORG
Southern I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Fernando B-PER
Antônio I-PER
Campos I-PER
Gomide E-PER
</b> O
, O
UNICAMP S-PER
, O
Brazil S-LOC

<b> O
Miha O
</b> O
<b> O
Moškon S-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Ljubljana E-ORG
, O
Slovenia S-LOC

<b> O
Dario B-PER
Landa I-PER
Silva E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nottingham E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Guo-Cheng B-PER
Wu E-PER
</b> O
, O
Neijiang B-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

</i> O

<b> O
<i> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE

<b> O
Fatemeh B-PER
Afghah E-PER
</b> O
, O
Northern B-ORG
Arizona I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Cecilio B-PER
Angulo E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Catalonia E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Antonio B-PER
Braga E-PER
</b> O
, O
Federal B-ORG
University I-ORG
Minas I-ORG
Gerais E-ORG
, O
Brazil S-LOC

<b> O
Suash B-PER
Deb E-PER
, O
</b> O
Cambridge B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Bingzhe B-PER
Li E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Minnesota E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Xi B-PER
Li E-PER
</b> O
, O
Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Jianquan B-PER
Lu E-PER
</b> O
, O
Southeast B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Qi B-PER
Wang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Northwestern B-ORG
Polytechnical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Wankou B-PER
Yang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Southeast B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Jun B-PER
Yu E-PER
</b> O
, O
Hangzhou B-ORG
Dianzi I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Xian-Ming B-PER
Zhang E-PER
</b> O
, O
Swinburne B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

N. B-PER
Andrei E-PER
, O
Research B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
for I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG

K. B-PER
Burrage E-PER
, O
Oxford B-ORG
University E-ORG
/ O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Queensland E-ORG

K. B-PER
Diethelm E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
Würzburg-Schweinfurt E-ORG

R. B-PER
Garrappa E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bari E-ORG

H. B-PER
Kaneko E-PER
, O
Old B-ORG
Dominion I-ORG
University E-ORG

Lek-Heng B-PER
Lim E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Chicago E-ORG

M. B-PER
Redivo-Zaglia E-PER
, O
Università B-PER
di I-PER
Padova E-PER

M. B-PER
Redivo-Zaglia E-PER
, O
Università B-PER
di I-PER
Padova E-PER

rodriguez O
@ O

<b> O
EDITORS ROLE

aladjem O
@ O

<b> O
ERIK B-PER
CUEVAS E-PER

erik.cuevas O
@ O

salvador.sanchez O
@ O

debayle O
@ O

<b> O
XUELONG O

xuelong O
_ O
li O
@ O

a.sowmya O
@ O

<b> O
JINHUI B-PER
TANG E-PER

<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-table O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Igor O
B. O
Gurevich O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Phys. O
- O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
Federal B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG
“ O
Computer B-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Control E-ORG
” O
, O
Russian B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

Nelson B-PER
L E-PER
. O
S. B-PER
da I-PER
Fonseca E-PER
, O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Campinas E-ORG
, O
Brazil S-LOC

Mohamed B-PER
M E-PER
. O
E. B-PER
A. I-PER
Mahmoud E-PER
, O
Tennessee B-ORG
Tech I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Mohammad B-PER
Shojafar E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Surrey E-ORG
, O
Uk S-LOC

Shan B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Beihang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC


<b> O
Emilia B-PER
Barakova E-PER
</b> O
, O
Eindhoven B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<b> O
Jofish B-PER
Kaye E-PER
</b> O
- O
Mozilla S-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Alexandra B-PER
Weilenmann E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Gothenburg E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

<b> O
Luca B-PER
Chittaro E-PER
</b> O
, O
HCI O
Lab O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Udine E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Gheorghita B-PER
Ghinea E-PER
</b> O
, O
Brunel B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
José B-PER
M. I-PER
Noguera E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Jaen E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Enrico B-PER
Rukzio E-PER
</b> O
, O
Ulm B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Elhadi B-PER
M. I-PER
Shakshuki E-PER
</b> O
, O
Acadia B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Christian B-PER
Bessiere E-PER
, O
Université B-ORG
Montpellier E-ORG
2 O
, O
France S-LOC

Humberto B-PER
Bustince E-PER
, O
Public B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Pamplona E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

F. B-PER
Javier I-PER
Cabrerizo E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Granada E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Oscar B-PER
Cordón E-PER
, O
European B-ORG
Center I-ORG
of I-ORG
Soft I-ORG
Computing E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Francesc B-PER
Ferri E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Valencia E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Marco B-PER
Gori E-PER
, O
University O
of O
Siena S-LOC
, O
Italy S-LOC

Álvaro B-PER
Herrero E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Burgos E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Manuel B-PER
Mucientes E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Santiago I-LOC
de I-LOC
Compostela E-LOC
, O
Spain S-LOC

Rainer B-PER
Unland E-PER
, O
Universiät B-LOC
Duisburg-Essen E-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Alexander B-PER
K. I-PER
Petrenko E-PER

<b> O
Sergei B-PER
A. I-PER
Abramov E-PER

</b> O
Dr. B-PER
Sci. E-PER
( O
Phys. O
– O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
Prof. O
, O
Keldysh B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Mathematics E-ORG
, O
Russian B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

<b> O
Advisory BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

<b> O
Kang B-PER
Shin E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG

</i> O
<b> O
Giuseppe B-PER
Lipari E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Scuola O
Superiore O

DL B-ORG
Pratt I-ORG
Bld E-ORG
, O
6 O
Kings B-LOC
College I-LOC
Road E-LOC


</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
Berntsson I-PER
Svensson E-PER

</b> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Madrid E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Martin B-PER
Feather E-PER

Marina B-PER
Jirotka E-PER

<b> O
Christos B-PER
Kalloniatis E-PER

</b> O
Aalto B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

</b> O
Iowa B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Case B-ORG
Western I-ORG
Reserve I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cincinnati E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bergen E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

Naveen B-PER
Prakash E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Geneva E-ORG
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

</b> O
Georgia B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Ji-Feng B-ORG
ZHANG I-ORG
, I-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
CAS S-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jie B-PER
HUANG E-PER
, O
The O
Chinese B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

</div> O

Wolfgang B-PER
Glänzel E-PER
</b> O
, O
Wolfgang.Glanzel S-PER
@ O

<b> O
Boualem B-PER
Benatallah E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Chun-Feng B-PER
Liao E-PER
</b> O
, O
National B-ORG
Chengchi I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

I. B-PER
Schaefer E-PER

Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Braunschweig E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Prof. O
Dr. O
Frédéric B-PER
Mallet E-PER
, O
Université B-ORG
Côte I-ORG
d'Azur E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

</div> O

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

<b> O
Enis B-PER
Cetin E-PER

aecyy O
@ O

<b> O
V O
. O
Carotenuto O
</b> O
, O
CNIT O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Naples I-ORG
Federico I-ORG
II E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
C O
. O
Chen O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Central I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
A O
. O
Farina S-PER
</b> O
, O
Leonardo B-PER
Company E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
K O
. O
Kose S-PER
, O
</b> O
Memorial B-ORG
Sloan I-ORG
Kettering I-ORG
Cancer I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Jie B-PER
Tang E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Derek B-PER
Doran E-PER
, O
Wright B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Shang B-PER
Gao E-PER
, O
Jilin B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jun B-PER
Huan E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kansas E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Matthieu B-PER
Latapy E-PER
, O
LIP6-CNRS B-ORG
et I-ORG
Université I-ORG
Pierre E-ORG
et O
Marie B-PER
Curie E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

Barry B-PER
Wellman E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toronto E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Ivor B-PER
Tsang E-PER
, O
Professor O
of O
Artificial O
Intelligence O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG
( O
UTS S-ORG
) O
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Section B-ROLE
Editors ROLE
</b> O
– O
Saraju B-ORG
P. I-ORG
Mohanty I-ORG
, I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
North I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Wil B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Aalst E-PER
, O
Process B-ORG
and I-ORG
Data I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
RWTH B-ORG
Aachen I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Johan B-PER
van I-PER
Benthem E-PER
, O
Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Logic I-ORG
, I-ORG
Language I-ORG
and I-ORG
Computation E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Amsterdam E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

Johannes B-PER
Aldert I-PER
Bergstra E-PER
, O
Informatics B-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Amsterdam E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

Cristian B-PER
S I-PER
Calude E-PER
, O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Auckland E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

Xiaoming B-ORG
Fu E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
Georg-August-University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Goettingen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Jozef B-PER
Gruska E-PER
, O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG
, O
Masaryk B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Czech B-LOC
Republic E-LOC

Bertrand B-PER
Meyer E-PER
, O
Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Milano E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Wolfgang B-PER
Nejdl E-PER
, O
Institut B-ORG
für I-ORG
Verteilte I-ORG
Systeme E-ORG
, O
Leibniz B-ORG
University I-ORG
Hannover E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Franco B-PER
Zambonelli E-PER
, O
Dipartimento B-ORG
di I-ORG
Scienze E-ORG
e O
Metodi B-PER
dell'Ingegneria E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Modena E-ORG
and O
Reggio B-LOC
Emilia E-LOC
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE
of O
Sections O

</div> O

<b> O
Sudipto B-PER
Ghosh E-PER
</b> O

</i> O
<i> O
Colorado B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Jeffrey B-PER
Carver E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Alabama E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Benoit B-PER
Combemale E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toulouse E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Robert B-PER
Feldt E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Chalmers B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Filippo B-PER
Lanubile E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bari E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Tim B-PER
Menzies E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
, O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Marek B-PER
Reformat E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Alberta E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Philippe B-PER
Robert E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
ISOSCOPE O
, O
Toulouse S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Brendan S-PER
</b> O
<b> O
Murphy S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
Dublin E-ORG
, O
Ireland S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Sumeetpal B-PER
S. I-PER
Singh E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Cambridge B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

huseyin.ergin O
@ O

RWTH B-ORG
Aachen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Benoit B-PER
Baudry E-PER
</b> O
( O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Nelly B-PER
Bencomo E-PER
</b> O
( O
UK S-LOC
) O

<b> O
Ruth B-PER
Breu E-PER
</b> O
( O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Lionel B-PER
Briand E-PER
</b> O
( O
Luxembourg S-LOC

<b> O
Jordi B-PER
Cabot E-PER
</b> O
( O
Spain S-LOC

<b> O
Oystein B-PER
Haugen E-PER
</b> O
( O
Norway S-LOC

<b> O
Antonio B-PER
Vallecillo E-PER
</b> O
( O
Spain S-LOC

Marco B-PER
Dorigo E-PER
, O
Université B-ORG
Libre I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bruxelles E-ORG

Ofer B-PER
Feinerman E-PER
, O
Weizmann B-ORG
Institute E-ORG

M. B-PER
Ani I-PER
Hsieh E-PER
, O
Drexel B-ORG
University E-ORG

Naomi B-PER
Leonard E-PER
, O
Princeton B-ORG
University E-ORG

John B-PER
Sutherland E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
St. B-LOC
Andrews E-LOC
, O
Scotland S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

Olga B-PER
De I-PER
Troyer E-PER
, O
Vrije B-ORG
Universiteit I-ORG
Brussel E-ORG
, O
Professor O
, O
Belgium S-LOC

Sajid B-PER
Farooq E-PER
, O
Ra'ed B-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
/ I-ORG
COMSATS E-ORG
, O
CEO O
, O
Australia S-LOC

Matt B-PER
Seeney E-PER
, O
Gameology B-ORG
Consultancy E-ORG
, O
Director O
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

Robin B-PER
Sloan E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Abertay I-ORG
Dundee E-ORG
, O
Researcher O
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

Kasapakis B-PER
Vlasios E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Aegean E-ORG
, O
Research B-ORG
Associate BI-ROLE
, O
Greece S-LOC

</b> O
Shenzhen B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

</b> O
Abeja B-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc E-ORG
. O
, O
Japan S-LOC
, O
kunii O
@ O

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Nicolas B-PER
Bonneel E-PER

CNRS B-ORG
/ I-ORG
Univ. I-ORG
Lyon E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC
, O
nicolas.bonneel O
@ O

</b> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC
, O
elpchau O
@ O

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Haute I-ORG
Alsace E-ORG
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Strasbourg E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC
, O
Frederic.Cordier S-LOC
@ O

<b> O
Naser B-PER
Damer E-PER

</b> O
York B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC
, O
pfal O
@ O

<b> O
Xifeng B-PER
Gao E-PER

<b> O
Ramakrishna B-PER
Kakarala E-PER

Florent B-PER
Lafarge E-PER

<b> O
Yu-Kun B-PER
Lai E-PER

<b> O
Xiaoyang B-PER
Mao E-PER

<b> O
Ahmad B-PER
H. I-PER
Nasri E-PER

<b> O
George B-PER
Papagiannakis E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Crete E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC
, O
papagian O
@ O

</b> O
Snap B-ORG
Inc E-ORG
. O
, O
USA S-LOC
, O
renzhou200622 O
@ O

<b> O
Jianbing B-PER
Shen E-PER

</b> O
Beijing B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
, O
shenjianbingcg O
@ O

<b> O
Claudio B-PER
T. I-PER
Silva E-PER

</b> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC
, O
assourin O
@ O

<b> O
Tien-Tsin B-PER
Wong E-PER

Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
, O
yandongming O
@ O

<b> O
Quanzeng B-PER
You E-PER

</b> O
Microsoft B-ORG
Azure I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
AI O
, O
USA S-LOC
, O
quyou O
@ O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Dallas S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC
, O
kzhang O
@ O

</b> O
Southeast B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC
, O
wenming O
_ O
zheng O
@ O

Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
SAR S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Artemidos S-ORG
6 O
& O
amp O
; O
Epidavrou S-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Karlsruhe E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC
// O
klemens.boehm O
@ O

<b> O
Nicolas B-PER
Anciaux E-PER

<b> O
Luna B-PER
Dong E-PER

<b> O
Zi B-PER
Helen I-PER
Huang E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Miami E-ORG

<b> O
Harry B-PER
M. I-PER
Buhrman E-PER

Kruislaan S-PER

School B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computing E-ORG

( O
combinatorial O
pattern O
matching O
; O
dynamic O
data O
structures O
; O
external O
memory O
algorithms O
; O
string O
algorithms O
; O
text O
indexing O

lohrey O
@ O

Universität B-ORG
Bremen E-ORG

Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computing E-ORG

Division O
of O
ICS S-ORG

Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Elvira B-PER
Mayordomo E-PER

Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG

Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematical I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG

Taramani S-LOC
, O
Chennai S-LOC
, O
600 O
113 O
India S-LOC

D-89069 O
Ulm S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

Computer B-ORG
Science I-ORG
Department E-ORG

Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG
( O
ICS S-ORG

and O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Weiqin B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
</b> O
Oslo B-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

Eleni B-PER
Efthimiou E-PER
, O
</b> O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Language I-ORG
and I-ORG
Speech I-ORG
Processing E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

<b> O
Iosif B-PER
Klironomos E-PER
, O
</b> O
FORTH-ICS O
, O
Greece S-LOC

<b> O
Pei-Luen B-PER
Patrick I-PER
Rau E-PER
, O
</b> O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Konstantinos B-PER
Votis E-PER
, O
</b> O
Centre B-ORG
for I-ORG
Research I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Hellas E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

</b> O
<i> O
Utrecht B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC
, O
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aberdeen E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Cristina B-PER
Gena E-PER
<i> O
, O
</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
</i> O
<i> O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Torino E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Bamshad S-PER
</b> O
<b> O
Mobasher S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
DePaul B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Marko B-PER
Tkalčič E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Primorska E-ORG
, O
Slovenia S-LOC

<b> O
Diego B-PER
Zapata-Rivera E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Educational O
Testing O
Service O
( O
ETS O
<S-MISC> O
) O
, O
USA S-LOC
</i> O

</div> O

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

Philip B-PER
A. I-PER
Bernstein E-PER
, O
<i> O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Wookey B-PER
Lee E-PER
, O
<i> O
INHA B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Korea S-LOC

Qing B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
<i> O
City B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Zhihong B-PER
Tian E-PER
, O
<i> O
Guangzhou B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jeffrey B-PER
Xu I-PER
Yu E-PER
, O
<i> O
Chinese B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Prof. O
Woodrow B-PER
Barfield E-PER
( O
USA S-LOC

HTLab S-ORG
, O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Padova E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

Prof. O
Doug B-PER
Bowman E-PER
, O
USA S-LOC

Dr. O
Pietro B-PER
Cipresso E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

Dr. O
Stephen B-PER
R. I-PER
Ellis E-PER
, O
USA S-LOC

Dr. O
Thomas B-PER
Furness E-PER
, O
USA S-LOC

Prof. O
Masahiko B-PER
Inami E-PER
, O
Japan S-LOC

Prof. O
Kay B-PER
Stanney E-PER
, O
USA S-LOC

Prof. O
Peter B-PER
Thomas E-PER
, O
Australia S-LOC

</b> O
Kathryn B-PER
Baxter E-PER

