<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
<i> O
Managing B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Cunsheng B-PER
Ding E-PER

</b> O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG

Clear B-LOC
Water I-LOC
Bay E-LOC
, O
Kowloon S-LOC
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Marc B-PER
Giusti E-PER


Campus B-ORG
de I-ORG
l'École I-ORG
Polytechnique E-ORG

1 O
, O
rue O
Honoré B-PER
d'Estienne I-PER
d'Orves E-PER

Bâtiment B-PER
Alan I-PER
Turing E-PER

91120 O
Palaiseau S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Iiro B-PER
Honkala E-PER

</b> O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Statistics E-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Turku E-ORG

Vesilinnantie S-ORG

20014 O
Turun B-PER
yliopisto E-PER
, O
Finland S-LOC

honkala O
@ O

<b> O
H.F O
. O
Mattson B-PER
Jr E-PER
. O

EECS S-ORG
4-206 O

hmattson O
@ O

Dipartimento B-PER
di I-PER
Matematica E-PER

Università B-ORG
di I-ORG
Genova E-ORG

16146 O
Genova S-LOC
, O
Italy S-LOC

mbaaecc O
@ O

<b> O
Daniel B-PER
Panario E-PER

</b> O
School B-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Statistics E-ORG

Carleton B-ORG
University E-ORG

1125 O
Colonel O
By B-PER
Drive E-PER

Ottawa S-LOC
, O
ON O
K1S O
5B6 O
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Luis B-PER
M. I-PER
Pardo E-PER

FACULTAD B-ORG
DE I-ORG
CIENCIAS E-ORG

UNIVERSIDAD B-ORG
DE I-ORG
CANTABRIA E-ORG

Avda S-ORG
. O
Los B-ORG
Castros E-ORG
, O
s O
/ O

E-39071 O
SANTANDER S-ORG

luis.m.pardo O
@ O

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Anne B-PER
Canteaut E-PER

</b> O
Inria S-LOC
, O
Paris S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

Anne.Canteaut O
@ O

<b> O
Harm B-PER
Derksen E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
Ann B-LOC
Arbor E-LOC
, O
MI S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Heiko B-PER
Dietrich E-PER

Monash B-ORG
University I-ORG
VIC I-ORG
Australia E-ORG

heiko.dietrich O
@ O

<b> O
Michele B-PER
Elia E-PER

Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Torino E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Graham B-PER
Ellis E-PER

</b> O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ireland E-ORG
, O
Galway S-LOC
, O
Ireland S-LOC

graham.ellis O
@ O

<b> O
Dmitry B-PER
Grigoryev E-PER

Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Lille E-ORG
, O
Villeneuve B-LOC
d'Ascq E-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

Dmitry.Grigoryev S-LOC
@ O

<b> O
Joos B-PER
Heintz E-PER

joos O
@ O

<b> O
W O
. O
Cary B-PER
Huffman E-PER

</b> O
Loyola B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Chicago S-LOC
, O
IL S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

whuffma O
@ O

<b> O
Tibor B-PER
Jager E-PER

Ruhr-University B-ORG
Bochum E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

tibor.jager O
@ O

<b> O
Dieter B-PER
Jungnickel E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Augsburg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

jungnickel O
@ O

kapur O
@ O

Laboratoire B-ORG
d'Informatique I-ORG
de I-ORG
l'École I-ORG
Polytechnique E-ORG
( O
LIX S-ORG

lecerf O
@ O

<b> O
Aart B-PER
Middeldorp E-PER

Aart.Middeldorp S-LOC
@ O

<b> O
François B-PER
Morain E-PER

Palaiseau S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

morain O
@ O

crypto-info O
@ O

<b> O
Jacques B-PER
Patarin E-PER

Université B-LOC
de I-LOC
Versailles I-LOC
St. I-LOC
Quentin-en-Yvelines E-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

jpatarin O
@ O

<b> O
David B-PER
Pointcheval E-PER

</b> O
École B-ORG
Normale I-ORG
Supérieure E-ORG
, O
Paris S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Massimiliano B-PER
Sala E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Trento E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

maxsala.aaecc O
@ O

<b> O
Kai-Uwe B-PER
Schmidt E-PER

</b> O
Paderborn B-ORG
University E-ORG

<b> O
Michael B-PER
Singer E-PER

N.C S-LOC
. O
State O
University O
, O
Raleigh S-LOC
, O
NC S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

University O
of O
Buenos B-LOC
Aires E-LOC
, O
Argentina S-LOC

psolerno O
@ O

<b> O
Horacio B-PER
Tapia I-PER
Recillas E-PER

htr O
@ O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Christel B-PER
Baier E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
Dresden E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

baier O
@ O

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Alessandro B-PER
Abate E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Roderick B-PER
Bloem E-PER
, O
</b> O
Graz B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

<b> O
Ahmed B-PER
Bouajjani E-PER
</b> O
, O
Université B-PER
Paris I-PER
Diderot E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Patricia B-PER
Bouyer-Decitre E-PER
</b> O
, O
CNRS B-PER
Cachan E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Manfred B-PER
Broy E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
München E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Jérémie B-PER
Chalopin E-PER
, O
</b> O
LIF O
, O
CNRS B-ORG
et I-ORG
Aix-Marseille I-ORG
Université E-ORG
<b> O
, O
</b> O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Ugo B-PER
Dal I-PER
Lago E-PER
, O
</b> O
Università B-ORG
di I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Giuseppe B-PER
De I-PER
Giacomo E-PER
, O
</b> O
Sapienza B-ORG
Università I-ORG
di I-ORG
Roma E-ORG
<b> O
, O
</b> O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Martin B-PER
Dietzfelbinger E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
Ilmenau E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Leah B-PER
Epstein E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Haifa E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Javier B-PER
Esparza E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
München E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Erol B-PER
Gelenbe E-PER
</b> O
, O
Imperial B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Antonín B-PER
Kučera E-PER
</b> O
, O
Masaryk B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Czech B-LOC
Republic E-LOC

<b> O
Leonid B-PER
Libkin E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Madhavan B-PER
Mukund E-PER
</b> O
, O
Chennai B-ORG
Mathematical I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Ernst-Rüdiger B-PER
Olderog E-PER
</b> O
, O
Universität B-PER
Oldenburg E-PER
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Luke B-PER
Ong E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Catuscia B-PER
Palamidessi E-PER
</b> O
, O
INRIA B-ORG
Saclay E-ORG
, O
and O
LIX O
, O
Ecole B-ORG
Polytechnique E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Prakash B-PER
Panangaden E-PER
</b> O
, O
McGill B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Nir B-PER
Piterman E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leicester E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
André B-PER
Platzer E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Arto B-PER
Salomaa E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Turku E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Davide B-PER
Sangiorgi E-PER
</b> O
, O
Università B-PER
di I-PER
Bologna E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Uli B-PER
Sattler E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Manchester E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Nicole B-PER
Schweikardt E-PER
</b> O
, O
Humboldt-Universität B-ORG
zu I-ORG
Berlin E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Paul B-PER
Spirakis E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Ofer B-PER
Strichman E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technion S-LOC
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Geoff B-PER
Sutcliffe E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Miami E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Luca B-PER
Viganò E-PER
</b> O
, O
King O
’s O
College O
London S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Nobuko B-PER
Yoshida E-PER
</b> O
, O
Imperial B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Peter B-PER
J. I-PER
Denning E-PER
</b> O
, O
Monterey S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Michael B-PER
J. I-PER
Fischer E-PER
</b> O
, O
Yale B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Donald B-PER
E. I-PER
Knuth E-PER
</b> O
, O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Zohar B-PER
Manna E-PER
</b> O
, O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Dana B-PER
Scott E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE

</i> O
</b> O
<b> O
Martin B-PER
Charles I-PER
Golumbic E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Haifa E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

</b> O
</i> O
<b> O
Jérôme B-PER
Lang E-PER
</b> O
( O
Université B-LOC
Paris-Dauphine E-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
Bo O
An O
</b> O
( O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

<b> O
Noa B-PER
Agmon E-PER
</b> O
( O
Bar-Ilan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Reneta B-PER
P. I-PER
Barneva E-PER
</b> O
( O
The O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG
at O
Fredonia S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Radim B-PER
Belohlavek E-PER
</b> O
( O
Palacky B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Czech B-LOC
Republic E-LOC

<b> O
Salem B-PER
Benferhat E-PER
</b> O
( O
Université B-LOC
d'Artois E-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Endre B-PER
Boros E-PER
</b> O
( O
Rutgers B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Piscataway S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Yixin B-PER
Chen E-PER
</b> O
( O
Washington B-ORG
University E-ORG
in I-ROLE
St. B-LOC
Louis E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jürgen B-PER
Dix E-PER
</b> O
( O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Clausthal E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Jacques B-PER
Fleuriot E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Hélène B-PER
Kirchner E-PER
</b> O
( O
INRIA B-ORG
Bordeaux E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Xuelong B-PER
Li E-PER
</b> O
( O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Xi’an S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Mehryar B-PER
Mohri E-PER
</b> O
( O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Aniello B-PER
Murano E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Naples E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Francesca B-PER
Rossi E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Padua E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Jörg B-PER
Rothe E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Düsseldorf E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Sasha B-PER
Rubin E-PER
</b> O
( O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG

<b> O
Christine B-PER
Solnon E-PER
</b> O
( O
INSA B-PER
Lyon E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Yisong B-PER
Wang E-PER
</b> O
( O
Guizhou B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
</i> O
</b> O

</i> O
<b> O
R O
. O
Battiti O
, O
</b> O
Università B-ORG
di I-ORG
Trento E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC
; O
<b> O
B O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Buchberger S-PER
, O
</b> O
Universität B-ORG
Linz E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC
; O
<b> O
A O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Bundy O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC
; O
<b> O
B.Y O
. O
Choueiry O
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nebraska-Lincoln E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
B O
. O
Faltings O
</b> O
, O
Ecole B-ORG
Polytechnique I-ORG
Fédérale I-ORG
de I-ORG
Lausanne E-ORG
, O
Switzerland S-LOC
; O
<b> O
M O
. O
Feldman S-PER
, O
</b> O
Tel B-ORG
Aviv I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC
; O
<b> O
M O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Fisher O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC
; O
<b> O
J O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Franco O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cincinnati E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
D O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Gabbay O
, O
</b> O
King B-ORG
's I-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC
; O
<b> O
G O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Gottlob O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC
; O
<b> O
H.J O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Greenberg S-PER
, O
</b> O
Denver S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
F O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Hoffman S-PER
, O
</b> O
Florida B-ORG
Atlantic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
L O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Joskowicz S-PER
, O
</b> O
The O
Hebrew B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Jerusalem E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC
; O
<b> O
D O
. O
Keren S-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Haifa E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC
; O
<b> O
A O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Kogan S-PER
, O
</b> O
Rutgers B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
Sarit B-PER
Kraus E-PER
, O
</b> O
Bar-Ilan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC
; O
<b> O
J. O
- O
L O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Lassez O
, O
</b> O
Coastal B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
V O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Lifschitz O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
J O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Minker O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maryland E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
L O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Morgenstern S-PER
, O
</b> O
Leidos S-PER
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
A O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Nerode O
</b> O
, O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
J O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Pearl O
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
M.M O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Richter S-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kaiserslautern E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC
; O
<b> O
B O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Selman S-PER
, O
</b> O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
V.S O
. O
Subrahmanian O
</b> O
, O
Dartmouth B-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
; O
<b> O
W O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Wahlster O
, O
</b> O
DFKI O
, O
Saarbrücken S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC
; O
<b> O
S O
. O
</b> O
<b> O
Zilberstein S-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Massachusetts E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

<b> O
Karen B-PER
Anderson E-PER

Mid B-LOC
Sweden E-LOC
University O
, O
Sweden S-LOC

<b> O
Gillian B-PER
Oliver E-PER

Monash B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Caulfield B-LOC
East E-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
Ann B-LOC
Arbor E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

Erik B-PER
Borglund E-PER
, O
<i> O
Mid B-ORG
Sweden I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

</i> O
Richard B-PER
Cox E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
</<E-ORG> O
i> O
<i> O
Pittsburgh S-LOC
, O
PA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
Maria B-PER
Guercio E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Urbino E-ORG
, O
</i> O
<i> O
Italy S-LOC

</i> O
Verne B-PER
Harris E-PER
, O
<i> O
Nelson B-PER
Mandela E-PER
Foundation O
, O
South B-LOC
Africa E-LOC

</i> O
Margaret B-PER
Hedstrom E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
Ann B-LOC
Arbor E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
Feng B-ORG
Huiling E-ORG
, O
<i> O
Renmin B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
China E-ORG

</i> O
Eric B-PER
Ketelaar E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Amsterdam E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

</i> O
Sabine B-PER
Mas E-PER
, O
<i> O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Montréal E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

</i> O
Sue B-PER
McKemmish E-PER
, O
<i> O
Monash B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

</i> O
Angelika B-PER
Menne-Haritz E-PER
, O
<i> O
Bundesarchiv O
, O
Berlin S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

</i> O
Christine B-PER
Nougaret E-PER
, O
<i> O
L'Ecole B-ORG
Nationale I-ORG
des I-ORG
Chartes E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

</i> O
Istvan B-PER
Rev E-PER
, O
<i> O
Central B-ORG
European I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Hungary S-LOC

</i> O
Fernanda B-PER
Ribeiro E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Porto E-ORG
, O
Portugal S-LOC

</i> O
Peter B-PER
Sebina E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Botswana E-ORG

</i> O
Elizabeth B-PER
Shepherd E-PER
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O
<b> O
Karamjit B-PER
S. I-PER
Gill E-PER

Professor O
Emeritus E-ROLE
, O
Human B-ORG
Centred I-ORG
Systems E-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Brighton E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

submission O
email O
: O
editoraisoc O
@ O

Editor ROLE
/ O
North B-LOC
America E-LOC
: O
<b> O
Victoria B-ORG
Vesna E-ORG

Professor O
Design B-ORG
Media I-ORG
Arts E-ORG

email O
: O
vesna O
@ O

Managing B-ROLE
Editor ROLE
: O
<b> O
Satinder O
P. O
Gill O

email O
: O
spg12 O
@ O

Open O
Forum O
Editor ROLE
: O
<b> O
David B-PER
Smith E-PER

Emeritus E-ROLE
Professor O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
Newport S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

email O
: O
athrylith O
@ O

Curmudgeon B-ORG
Corner E-ORG
Editor ROLE
: O
<b> O
Sha B-PER
Xin I-PER
Wei E-PER

</b> O
Professor O
in I-ROLE
the O
School B-ORG
of I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
, I-ORG
Media I-ORG
+ I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
( O
AME S-ORG

Arizona B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

email O
: O
shaxinwei O
@ O

<b> O
Student B-ORG
Forum E-ORG

</b> O
Editor ROLE
: O
<b> O
Larry B-PER
Stapleton E-PER

INSYTE S-ORG
, O
Waterford B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

<b> O
Amy B-PER
Stapleton E-PER
</b> O
( O
Trinity B-ORG
College I-ORG
Dublin E-ORG

<b> O
John B-PER
Organ E-PER
</b> O
( O
WIT B-LOC
Ireland E-LOC

<b> O
Katharine B-PER
Schulmann E-PER
</b> O
( O
Trinity B-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
Dublin S-LOC

email O
: O
schulmak O
@ O

<i> O
Mentor O
: O
</i> O
<b> O
Dietrich B-PER
Brandt E-PER
</b> O
( O
Aachen B-ORG
University E-ORG

Email O
: O
brandtdietrich O
@ O

<b> O
Advisory BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

</b> O
<b> O
Margaret B-PER
Boden E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Sussex E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Albert B-PER
Borgmann E-PER
, O
</b> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Montana E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Peter B-PER
Broedner E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Siegen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Joanna B-PER
J. I-PER
Bryson E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bath E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Alan B-PER
Bundy E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Ian B-PER
Cross E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambridge E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
Ennals E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Agder E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC
and O
Kingston B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Bo B-PER
Göranzon E-PER
, O
</b> O
Royal B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Stockholm S-LOC
, O
Sweden S-LOC

<b> O
Ashok B-PER
Jain E-PER
, O
</b> O
National B-ORG
institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
, I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and I-ORG
Development I-ORG
Studies E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Zhouying B-PER
Jin E-PER
, O
</b> O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Social I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
( O
CASS S-ORG
) O
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Ajit B-PER
Narayanan E-PER
, O
</b> O
Aukland B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

<b> O
Massimo B-PER
Negrotti E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Urbino E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Abbe B-PER
Mowshowitz E-PER
</b> O
, O
The B-ORG
City I-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG
( O
CUNY S-LOC
) O
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Takao B-PER
Nuki E-PER
, O
</b> O
Musashi B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Caterina B-PER
Rehm-Berbenni E-PER
, O
</b> O
PROMIS O
, O
Luxembourg S-LOC

<b> O
Guglielmo B-PER
Tamburrini E-PER
, O
</b> O
Universita B-PER
di I-PER
Napoli I-PER
Federico I-PER
II E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Steve B-PER
Torrance E-PER
, O
</b> O
Middlesex B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Diane B-PER
Whitehouse E-PER
, O
</b> O
The B-ORG
Castlegate I-ORG
Consultancy E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Terry B-PER
Winograd E-PER
, O
</b> O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE

</b> O
<b> O
Zinaida B-PER
K. I-PER
Avdeeva E-PER
, O
</b> O
National B-ORG
Research I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC

<b> O
Houda B-PER
Chakiri E-PER
, O
</b> O
Al B-ORG
Akhawayn I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Morocco S-LOC

<b> O
Elizabeth B-PER
F. I-PER
Churchill E-PER
, O
</b> O
Google S-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Mark B-PER
Coeckelbergh E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Vienna E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Kerstin B-PER
Dautenhahn E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Peter B-PER
Day E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Brighton E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Jon B-PER
Dron E-PER
</b> O
, O
Athabasca B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Clare B-PER
L.E E-PER
. O
Foster S-PER
, O
</b> O
Cambridge B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Marcus B-PER
Foth E-PER
, O
</b> O
QUT O
Urban O
Informatics O
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Tania B-PER
Fraga E-PER
, O
</b> O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Arts E-ORG
of O
Sao B-LOC
Paulo E-LOC
: O
IMA-SP S-ORG
, O
Brazil S-LOC

<b> O
Renate B-PER
Fruchter E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Stanford E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Francesco B-PER
Garibaldo E-PER
, O
</b> O
Fondazione B-PER
Claudio I-PER
Sabattini E-PER
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
John-Stewart B-PER
Gordon E-PER
, O
</b> O
Vytautas B-ORG
Magnus I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Lithuania S-LOC

<b> O
Petros B-PER
Groumpos E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Patras E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

<b> O
Rajakishore B-PER
Nath E-PER
, O
</b> O
IIT B-LOC
Bombay E-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Caroline B-PER
Nevejan E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Amsterdam E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<b> O
Ignacio B-PER
Nieto E-PER
, O
</b> O
Laboratorio B-ORG
de I-ORG
Aprendizaje E-ORG
a O
Distancia B-ORG
y I-ORG
Comunicación E-ORG
, O
Chile S-LOC

<b> O
Toyoaki B-PER
Nishida E-PER
, O
</b> O
Kyoto B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Simon B-PER
Penny E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
Irvine S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Matthias B-PER
Rehm E-PER
</b> O
, O
Aalborg B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
Klaus B-PER
Ruth E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bremen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Douglas B-PER
Schuler E-PER
, O
</b> O
The O
Evergreen B-ORG
State I-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jagjit B-PER
Singh I-PER
Srai E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambridge E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Reiji B-PER
Suzuki E-PER
, O
</b> O
Nagoya B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Arun B-PER
Tripathi E-PER
, O
</b> O
Independent O
Scholar O
, O
Central B-ORG
University I-ORG
Tibetan I-ORG
Studies E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Jeff B-PER
White E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Twente E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Editor-in-Chief ROLE

<b> O
Ming-Yang B-PER
Kao E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Northwestern B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Founding B-ROLE
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
( O
1984-2004 O

<b> O
C O
. O
K. B-PER
Wong E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
IBM O
, O
USA S-LOC
/ O
The O
Chinese B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

Application O
Experience-Editor O
: O
<b> O
D O
. O
T. B-PER
Lee E-PER

Problems-Editor O
: O
<b> O
Bernard B-PER
Chazelle E-PER

Executive B-ROLE
Committee E-ROLE

<b> O
John B-PER
E. I-PER
Hopcroft E-PER
, O
Ming-Yang B-PER
Kao E-PER
, O
Richard B-PER
M. I-PER
Karp E-PER

C. B-PER
L. I-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
Franco B-PER
P. I-PER
Preparata E-PER


Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

</i> O
<b> O
Andris B-PER
Ambainis E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Latvia E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC

<b> O
Lars B-PER
Arge E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aarhus E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
James B-PER
Aspnes E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Yale B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Allan B-PER
B. I-PER
Borodin E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toronto E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Xi B-PER
Chen E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Columbia B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Joseph B-PER
Cheriyan E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Edith B-PER
Cohen E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
AT O
& O
amp O
; O
T O
Labs O
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
Cole E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Marek B-PER
Cygan E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Warsaw E-ORG
, O
Poland S-LOC

<b> O
Xiaotie B-PER
Deng E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Fedor B-PER
V. I-PER
Fomin E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bergen E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

<b> O
Harold B-PER
N. I-PER
Gabow E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Anupam B-PER
Gupta E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Prahladh B-PER
Harsha E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Tata B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fundamental I-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
John B-PER
E. I-PER
Hopcroft E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Giuseppe B-PER
F. I-PER
Italiano E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Università B-PER
di I-PER
Roma E-PER
" O
Tor B-PER
Vergata E-PER
," O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Kazuo B-PER
Iwama E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Kyoto B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Haim B-PER
Kaplan E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Tel B-ORG
Aviv I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
M. I-PER
Karp E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
ICSI O
( O
International B-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
) O
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Ken-ichi B-PER
Kawarabayashi E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
National B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Samir B-PER
Khuller E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maryland E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Lap B-PER
Chi I-PER
Lau E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
D O
. O
T. B-PER
Lee E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Academia B-PER
Sinica E-PER
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

<b> O
Konstantin B-PER
Makarychev E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Nimrod B-ORG
Megiddo E-ORG
</b> O
, O
<i> O
The O
IBM B-ORG
Almaden I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Joseph B-PER
Mitchell E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG
at O
Stony B-LOC
Brook E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Joseph S-PER
( O
Seffi S-PER
) O
Naor S-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Technion O
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Seth B-PER
Pettie E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Yuval B-PER
Rabani E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
The O
Hebrew B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Jerusalem E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Ronitt B-PER
Rubinfeld E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
MIT O
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Paul B-PER
G. I-PER
Spirakis E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Patras E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editors ROLE

</b> O
<i> O
Kevin B-PER
D. I-PER
Ashley E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pittsburgh E-ORG
, O
PA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
Trevor B-PER
Bench-Capon E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<i> O
Giovanni B-PER
Sartor E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Section B-ROLE
Editors ROLE

<i> O
Agents O
and O

<b> O
<i> O
Argumentation O
</i> O

<i> O
Katie B-PER
Atkinson E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Liverpool E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Tom B-PER
M. I-PER
van I-PER
Engers E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Amsterdam E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Law O
and O

</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Bart B-PER
Verheij E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Utrecht E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Legal O
Information O

<b> O
<i> O
Machine O
Learning O
</i> O

<i> O
Matthias B-PER
Grabmair E-PER
</i> O
, O
Language B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Pittsburgh S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
NLP O
and O
Text O

</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Adam B-PER
Wyner E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Swansea E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Ontology O
and O
Knowledge O

</i> O
</b> O
<i> O
Enrico B-PER
Francesconi E-PER
</i> O
, O
ITTIG-CNR O
, O
Florence S-LOC
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Book B-ROLE
Review BI-ROLE
Editor ROLE

</b> O
<i> O
Adam B-PER
Wyner E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Swansea E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Technology O

</b> O
<i> O
Marc B-PER
Lauritsen E-PER
</i> O
, O
Capstone B-ORG
Practice I-ORG
Systems E-ORG
, O
Harvard S-LOC
, O
MA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

</b> O
<i> O
Michał B-PER
Araszkiewicz E-PER
</i> O
, O
Jagiellonian B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Krakow S-LOC
, O
Poland S-LOC

<i> O
L O
. O
Karl B-PER
Branting E-PER
</i> O
, O
The B-ORG
MITRE I-ORG
Corporation E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
Scott B-PER
Brewer E-PER
</i> O
, O
Harvard B-ORG
Law I-ORG
School E-ORG
, O
Cambridge S-LOC
, O
MA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
Jack B-PER
G. I-PER
Conrad E-PER
</i> O
, O
Thomson B-ORG
Reuters I-ORG
Research I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
Development O
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
Anne O
v.d O
. O
L. B-PER
Gardner E-PER
</i> O
, O
Atherton S-LOC
, O
CA S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
Rinke B-ORG
Hoekstra E-ORG
</i> O
, O
Elsevier S-ORG
B.V O
. O
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<i> O
Andrew B-PER
J.I E-PER
. O
Jones S-PER
</i> O
, O
King B-ORG
’s I-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<i> O
Daniel B-PER
Katz E-PER
</i> O
, O
Michigan B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
East B-LOC
Lansing E-LOC
, O
MI S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
L O
. O
Thorne B-PER
McCarty E-PER
</i> O
, O
Rutgers B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
Jersey E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
Katsumi B-PER
Nitta E-PER
</i> O
, O
Tokyo B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<i> O
Juliano B-PER
Souza I-PER
de I-PER
Albuquerque I-PER
Maranhão E-PER
, O
</i> O
Universidade B-ORG
de I-ORG
São I-ORG
Paulo-USP E-ORG
, O
Brazil S-LOC

<i> O
Henry B-PER
Prakken E-PER
</i> O
, O
Utrecht B-ORG
University E-ORG
; O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Groningen E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

<i> O
Edwina B-ORG
L. I-ORG
Rissland E-ORG
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Massachusetts E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<i> O
Antonio B-PER
Rotolo E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<i> O
Ken B-PER
Satoh E-PER
</i> O
, O
National B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG
, O
Chiyoda-ku S-LOC
, O
Hitotsubashi S-LOC
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

<i> O
Burkhard B-PER
Schafer E-PER
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
Scotland S-LOC

<i> O
Uri B-PER
J. I-PER
Schild E-PER
</i> O
, O
Bar B-ORG
Ilan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Ramat B-LOC
Gan E-LOC
, O
Israel S-LOC

<i> O
Serena B-PER
Villata E-PER
</i> O
, O
INRIA B-ORG
Sophia-Antipolis E-ORG
- O
Mediterranee S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<i> O
Radboud B-ORG
Winkels E-ORG
</i> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Amsterdam E-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Editor-in-Chief ROLE

Hiroshi B-PER
Tanaka E-PER
, O
Tokyo B-ORG
Medical I-ORG
and I-ORG
Dental I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE

John B-PER
L. I-PER
Casti E-PER
, O
Vienna S-LOC
, O
Austria S-LOC

Joshua B-PER
M. I-PER
Epstein E-PER
, O
Washington B-LOC
DC E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Hidenori B-PER
Kimura E-PER
, O
Nagoya S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Ju-Jang B-PER
Lee E-PER
, O
Taejon S-LOC
, O
Korea S-LOC

Deputy B-ROLE
Editors ROLE

Takaya B-PER
Arita E-PER
, O
Nagoya S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Hideki B-PER
Hashimoto E-PER
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Ken B-PER
Naitoh E-PER
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Kazushi B-PER
Nakano E-PER
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Masahiro B-PER
Nishibori E-PER
, O
Tochigi S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Keigo B-PER
Watanabe E-PER
, O
Okayama S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Changshui B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

Christopher B-PER
L. I-PER
Barrett E-PER
, O
Los B-LOC
Alamos E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Mark B-PER
A. I-PER
Bedau E-PER
, O
Portland S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Young-Im B-PER
Cho E-PER
, O
Hwaseong S-LOC
, O
Korea S-LOC

Thomas B-PER
Christaller E-PER
, O
Sankt B-PER
Augustin E-PER
, O
Germany S-LOC

Noriyasu B-PER
Homma E-PER
, O
Sendai S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Kazushi B-PER
Ikeda E-PER
, O
Nara S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

D.J.Glyndwer B-PER
James E-PER
, O
Conventry S-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Hiroshi B-PER
Kashiwagi E-PER
, O
Kumamoto S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Kazuo B-PER
Kyuma E-PER
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Jang-Myung B-PER
Lee E-PER
, O
Pusan S-LOC
, O
Korea S-LOC

Atsuko B-PER
Mutoh E-PER
, O
Nagoya S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Marion B-PER
Oswald E-PER
, O
Vienna S-LOC
, O
Austria S-LOC

Luigi B-PER
Pagliarini E-PER
, O
Odense S-LOC
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Rolf B-PER
Pfeifer E-PER
, O
Zurich S-LOC
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

Takanori B-PER
Shibata E-PER
, O
Tsukuba S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Noritaka B-PER
Shigei E-PER
, O
Kagoshima S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Katsunori B-PER
Shimohara E-PER
, O
Kyoto S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Charles B-PER
E. I-PER
Taylor E-PER
, O
Los B-LOC
Angeles E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Shinjiro B-PER
Umezu E-PER
, O
Tokyo S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Kazuko B-PER
Yamasaki E-PER
, O
Chiba S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

</div> O

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

<b> O
Kate B-PER
Larson E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
CANADA S-LOC

<b> O
Michael B-PER
Luck E-PER
</b> O
, O
King B-ORG
's I-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Noah B-PER
Agmon E-PER
</b> O
, O
Bar B-ORG
Ilan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
ISRAEL S-LOC

<b> O
Natasha B-PER
Alechina E-PER
, O
</b> O
Utrecht B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
NETHERLANDS S-LOC

<b> O
Bo O
An O
</b> O
, O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
SINGAPORE S-LOC

<b> O
Elisabeth B-PER
André E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Augsburg E-ORG
, O
GERMANY S-LOC

<b> O
Haris B-PER
Aziz E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
AUSTRALIA S-LOC

<b> O
Bikramjit B-PER
Banerjee E-PER
</b> O
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Mississippi E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Elizabeth B-PER
Black E-PER
</b> O
, O
King B-ORG
's I-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Rafael B-PER
Bordini E-PER
, O
</b> O
PUCRS O
, O
BRAZIL S-LOC

<b> O
Ronen B-PER
Brafman E-PER
</b> O
, O
Ben-Gurion B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
ISRAEL S-LOC

<b> O
Mehdi B-PER
Dastani E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Utrecht E-ORG
, O
NETHERLANDS S-LOC

<b> O
Prashant B-PER
Doshi E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Georgia E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Edith B-PER
Elkind E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Maria B-PER
Gini E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Minnesota E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jonathan B-PER
Gratch E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Charles B-PER
Isbell E-PER
</b> O
, O
Georgia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Sven B-PER
Koenig E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jérôme B-PER
Lang E-PER
</b> O
, O
CNRS O
, O
PSL O
- O
Université B-ORG
Paris-Dauphine E-ORG
, O
FRANCE S-LOC

<b> O
Alessio B-PER
Lomuscio E-PER
, O
</b> O
Imperial B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Nicolas B-PER
Maudet E-PER
</b> O
, O
Sorbonne B-ORG
Université E-ORG
, O
FRANCE S-LOC

<b> O
Jörg B-PER
Müller E-PER
</b> O
, O
TU B-PER
Clausthal E-PER
, O
GERMANY S-LOC

<b> O
Anne B-PER
Nowe E-PER
</b> O
, O
Vrije B-ORG
Universiteit I-ORG
Brussel E-ORG
, O
BELGIUM S-LOC

<b> O
Anna B-PER
Paiva E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Lisbon E-ORG
, O
PORTUGAL S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Parkes E-PER
</b> O
, O
Harvard B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
H O
. O
Van B-PER
Dyke I-PER
Parunak E-PER
</b> O
, O
ABC B-ORG
Research I-ORG
, I-ORG
LLC E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Daniel B-PER
Polani E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Hertfordshire E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Birna B-PER
Van I-PER
Riemsdijk E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Twente E-ORG
, O
NETHERLANDS S-LOC

<b> O
Jeffrey B-PER
S. I-PER
Rosenschein E-PER
</b> O
, O
The O
Hebrew B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Jerusalem E-ORG
, O
ISRAEL S-LOC

<b> O
Michael B-PER
Rovatsos E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Tuomas B-PER
Sandholm E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Sandip B-PER
Sen E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tulsa E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Munindar B-PER
P. I-PER
Singh E-PER
</b> O
, O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Peter B-PER
Stone E-PER
</b> O
, O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Austin S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Katia B-PER
Sycara E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Matthew B-PER
E. I-PER
Taylor E-PER
</b> O
, O
Borealis B-PER
AI E-PER
, O
CANADA S-LOC

<b> O
Kagan B-PER
Tumer E-PER
</b> O
, O
Oregon B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Karl B-PER
Tuyls E-PER
</b> O
, O
Google O
DeepMind O
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Yevgeniy B-PER
Vorobeychik E-PER
, O
</b> O
Washington B-ORG
University E-ORG
in I-ROLE
St. B-LOC
Louis E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Danny B-PER
Weyns E-PER
</b> O
, O
KU B-ORG
Leuven E-ORG
, O
BELGIUM S-LOC
and O
Linnaeus B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
SWEDEN S-LOC

<b> O
Makoto B-PER
Yokoo E-PER
</b> O
, O
Kyushu B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
JAPAN S-LOC

<b> O
Neil B-PER
Yorke-Smith E-PER
, O
</b> O
TU B-ORG
Delft E-ORG
, O
NETHERLANDS S-LOC

<b> O
Pinar B-PER
Yolum E-PER
</b> O
, O
Utrecht B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
THE B-LOC
NETHERLANDS E-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O

AT B-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
T B-ORG
Laboratories I-ORG
Research E-ORG

180 O
Park B-ORG
Ave E-ORG
, O
Bldg S-LOC
. O

Florham B-LOC
Park E-LOC
, O
NJ S-LOC
07932 O
, O
USA S-LOC

Bob.ASEJ O
@ O

<b> O
Editor ROLE
Emeritus E-ROLE
: O

<b> O
Bashar B-PER
Nuseibeh E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
The O
Open B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Milton B-ORG
Keynes E-ORG
</i> O
<i> O
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Assistant O
Editors ROLE
: O

<b> O
John B-PER
Grundy E-PER
, O
</b> O
Monash B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Tim B-PER
Menzies E-PER
, O
</b> O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

<b> O
Jamie B-PER
Andrews E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Ontario E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Alex B-PER
Borgida E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Rutgers O
</i> O
<i> O
University O
, O
USA S-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
Stephen B-PER
F. I-PER
Fickas E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oregon E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Anthony B-PER
Finkelstein E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
</i> O
<i> O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Sol B-PER
J. I-PER
Greenspan E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
The O
National B-ORG
Science I-ORG
</<I-ORG> O
i O
<E-ORG>> O
<i> O
Foundation O
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Takuya B-PER
Katayama E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Japan B-ORG
Advanced I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
</<E-ORG> O
i> O
<i> O
Science B-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Ishikawa S-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
John B-PER
Mylopoulos E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toronto E-ORG
, O
</i> O
<i> O
Canada S-LOC
</i> O

</i> O
<b> O
Leon B-PER
J. I-PER
Osterweil E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Massachusetts E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Douglas B-PER
R. I-PER
Smith E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Kestrel O
</i> O
<i> O
Institute O
, O
USA S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Ian O
</b> O
<b> O
Sommerville S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
St. B-ORG
Andrews I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Scotland S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Alistair B-PER
Sutcliffe E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Manchester E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

</i> O
<b> O
Axel B-PER
van I-PER
Lamsweerde E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Université B-ORG
Catholique I-ORG
de I-ORG
</<E-ORG> O
i> O
<i> O
Louvain S-ORG
, O
Belgium S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O
Ruggero B-PER
S. I-PER
Gilyarevskii E-PER

EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

EDITOR-IN-CHIEF ROLE
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-table O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Ruggero B-PER
S. I-PER
Gilyarevskii E-PER
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Professor O
, O
Dr. B-PER
Sci. E-PER
( O
Philol O
. O
) O
, O
Head O
, O
Dept. O
of O
Theoretical B-ORG
and I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Problems I-ORG
of I-ORG
Informatics E-ORG
, O
All-Russia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Scientific I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
Information E-ORG
( O
VINITI O
) O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
</div> O
Coordinating B-ROLE
Editor ROLE
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-table O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
N O
. O
P. O
Zhukova O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Researcher O
, O
VINITI O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
</div> O
EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-table O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Oleg O
M. O
Anshakov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Russian O
<S-MISC> O
State O
University O
for O
the O
Humanities O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Eugene O
M. O
Beniaminov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Russian O
<S-MISC> O
State O
University O
for O
the O
Humanities O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Rebecca O
M. O
Frumkina O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Institute O
of O
Linguistics O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Tomas O
Gergely O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Applied O
Logic O
Laboratory O
, O
Budapest S-LOC
, O
Hungary S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Alexander O
A. O
Grusho O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Federal O
Research O
Centre O
“ O
Informatics O
and O
Control O
” O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Andrei O
P. O
Kovalenko O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Moscow B-ORG
New I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Delir O
G. O
Lakhuti O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Russian O
<S-MISC> O
State O
University O
for O
the O
Humanities O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Maria O
A. O
Mikheenkova O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Gennady O
S. O
Osipov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Federal O
Research O
Centre O
“ O
Informatics O
and O
Control O
” O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Elena O
V. O
Paducheva O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
VINITI O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Konstantin O
V. O
Rudakov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Federal O
Research O
Centre O
“ O
Informatics O
and O
Control O
” O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Vadim O
N. O
Vagin O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Moscow B-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dmitry O
V. O
Vinogradov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Federal O
Research O
Centre O
“ O
Informatics O
and O
Control O
” O
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
</div> O
</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-table O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
EDITOR-IN-CHIEF ROLE
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Modris O
Greitans O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Comp O
. O
) O
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
DEPUTY B-ROLE
EDITOR-IN-CHIEF ROLE
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Michael B-PER
Broitman E-PER
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Comp O
. O
) O
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Alexander O
M. O
Andronov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
Riga B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Transport B-ORG
and I-ORG
Telecommunication I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Janis O
Barzdinsh O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Phys. O
- O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Latvia E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Nikolajs O
Bogdanovs O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
Riga B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Telecommunications E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Yuri O
A. O
Chizhov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
Riga B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Alexander O
N. O
Dudin O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Phys. O
- O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
Belarus B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Minsk S-LOC
, O
Belarus S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Peter B-PER
Grabusts E-PER
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
Rezekne B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technologies E-ORG
, O
Rezekne S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Janis O
Grundspenkis O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
Riga B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Department B-ORG
Of I-ORG
Artificial I-ORG
Intelligence I-ORG
and I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Valery O
V. O
Khutortsev O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Tech O
. O
) O
, O
Rostov B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
Communication E-ORG
, O
Rostov-on-Don S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Nicholas O
A. O
Nechval O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
Baltic B-ORG
International I-ORG
Academy E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Agris O
Nikitenko O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
Riga B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Ernests O
Petersons O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Comp O
. O
) O
, O
Riga B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Faculty B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Telecommunications E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Alexander O
S. O
Rybakov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Comp O
. O
) O
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
Riga S-LOC
, O
Latvia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Vladimir O
V. O
Rykov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Phys. O
- O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
Russian B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Oil I-ORG
and I-ORG
Gas E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Konstantin O
E. O
Samouylov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
Peoples' B-ORG
Friendship I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Moscow S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Valery O
Sokolov O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Phys. O
- O
Math O
. O
) O
, O
Yaroslavl B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Yaroslavl S-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Peter O
D. O
Zegzhda O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Dr. O
Sci. O
( O
Eng O
. O
) O
, O
St. B-LOC
Peterburg I-LOC
State I-LOC
Polytechnical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
St. B-LOC
Peterburg E-LOC
, O
Russia S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-tr O
"> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Yinyan O
Zhang O
</div> O
<div O
class O
=" O
jflow-td O
"> O
Ph.D O
. O
( O
Comp O
. O
) O
, O
College B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cyber I-ORG
Security E-ORG
, O
Jinan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Guangzhou S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC
</div> O
</div> O
</div> O
</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
EDITOR-IN O
- O
<i> O
CHIEF E-ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
ASSOCIATE BI-ROLE
EDITORS ROLE

<b> O
Javier B-PER
Alonso-Mora E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Delft B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Netherlands S-LOC

<b> O
Geoff B-PER
Hollinger E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Oregon B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Amanda B-PER
Prorok E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cambridge E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Shaojie B-PER
Shen E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
HKUST O
, O
Hong B-LOC
Kong E-LOC

<b> O
EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE
: O

<b> O
Oliver B-PER
Brock E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Technische B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
Berlin E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Wolfram B-PER
Burgard E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Freiburg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Brian B-PER
Gerkey E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Willow O
Garage O
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Hiroshi B-PER
Ishiguro E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Vijay B-PER
Kumar E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pennsylvania E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Larry B-PER
Matthies E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
NASA B-ORG
Jet I-ORG
Propulsion I-ORG
Laboratory E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Daniela B-PER
Rus E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Massachusetts B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
ADVISORY BI-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE
: O

<b> O
Ronald B-PER
C. I-PER
Arkin E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Georgia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Minoru B-PER
Asada E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Osaka B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Randall B-PER
Beer E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Indiana B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Rodney B-PER
Brooks E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Massachusetts B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Paolo B-PER
Dario E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Scuola O
Superiore O
Sant'Anna O
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Hugh B-PER
Durrant-Whyte E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Sydney E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Dario B-PER
Floreano E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Swiss B-ORG
Federal I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

<b> O
Toshio B-PER
Fukuda E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Nagoya B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Shigeo B-PER
Hirose E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Tokyo B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Gerd B-PER
Hirzinger E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Deutsches B-ORG
Zentrum I-ORG
fur I-ORG
Luft E-ORG
- O
und O
Raumfahrt O
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Jessica B-PER
Hodgins E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Takeo B-PER
Kanade E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Hiroaki B-PER
Kitano E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Kitano B-ORG
Symbiotic I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Project E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Alois B-PER
Knoll E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Munich E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Kurt B-PER
Konolige E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Stanford B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Kazuhiro B-PER
Kosuge E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Tohoku B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Vijay B-PER
Kumar E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pennsylvania E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jean-Claude B-PER
Latombe E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Sukhan B-PER
Lee E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Sungkyunkwan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Korea S-LOC

<b> O
Larry B-PER
Matthies E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
NASA B-ORG
Jet I-ORG
Propulsion I-ORG
Laboratory E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Atsuo B-PER
Takanishi E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Waseda B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Manuela B-PER
Veloso E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Junku B-PER
Yuh E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Korea B-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Korea S-LOC

<b> O
Shin-ichi B-PER
Yuta E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Tsukuba B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Autonomous O
Robots O
Blog O
: O
</b> O
<b> O
www.autonomousrobotsblog.com O
</b> O

MEDIA O
EDITOR ROLE
: O
Sabine B-PER
Hauert E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bristol E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Derong B-PER
Liu E-PER

<b> O

<b> O
Choon B-PER
Ki I-PER
Ahn E-PER

</b> O
Korea B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Seoul S-LOC
, O
Korea S-LOC

<b> O
Flora B-PER
Amato E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Naples I-ORG
Federico I-ORG
II E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Elena B-PER
Bellodi E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Ferrara E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

</b> O
Nanyang B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Singapore S-LOC

<b> O
Federico B-PER
Chesani E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Erik B-PER
Cuevas E-PER

</b> O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Guadalajara E-ORG
, O
Mexico S-LOC

<b> O
Sanmay B-PER
Das E-PER

</b> O
Washington B-ORG
University E-ORG
in I-ROLE
St. B-LOC
Louis E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

</b> O
Indian B-ORG
Statistical I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Sebastien B-PER
Destercke E-PER

<b> O
Shukai B-PER
Duan E-PER

Southwest B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Thomas B-PER
Eiter E-PER

<b> O
Massimo B-PER
Esposito E-PER

<b> O
Qingbin B-PER
Gao E-PER

<b> O
Xingyu B-PER
Gao E-PER

</b> O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Evgin B-PER
Göçeri E-PER

</b> O
Akdeniz B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Turkey S-LOC

<b> O
Haibo B-PER
He E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Rhode I-ORG
Island E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Eyke B-PER
Hüllermeier E-PER

Paderborn B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Stirling E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Old B-ORG
Dominion I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</b> O
Nagoya B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Anna B-PER
Jordanous E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kent E-ORG
, O
Canterbury S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Philipp B-PER
Koehn E-PER

</b> O
Johns B-ORG
Hopkins I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC
, O
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Constantine B-PER
Kotropoulos E-PER

</b> O
Aristotle B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Thessaloniki E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

<b> O
Dhireesha B-PER
Kudithipudi E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas I-ORG
San B-LOC
Antonio E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Jimmy B-PER
Ho-Man I-PER
Lee E-PER

<b> O
Xuelong B-PER
Li E-PER

</b> O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Xi'an S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Biao B-PER
Luo E-PER

<b> O
Paola B-PER
Mello E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Francesco B-PER
Mercaldo E-PER

</b> O
National B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Council E-ROLE
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Saleh B-PER
Mobayen E-PER

<b> O
Fernando B-PER
Otero E-PER

<b> O
Emanuele B-PER
Principi E-PER

<b> O
Antonella B-PER
Santone E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Molise E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Stefano B-PER
Squartini E-PER

<b> O
Fatemeh B-PER
Vafaee E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
Sydney S-LOC
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Yevgeniy B-PER
Vorobeychik E-PER

</b> O
Vanderbilt B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Nashville S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Zeshui B-PER
Xu E-PER

</b> O
Sichuan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Dongbin B-PER
Zhao E-PER

Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Beijing S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

Depei B-PER
Qian E-PER
, O
Beihang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Dhabaleswar B-PER
K. I-PER
Panda E-PER
, O
Ohio B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Managing B-ROLE
Editors ROLE
: O

Wenguang B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Guangming B-ORG
Tan E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computing I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Advisory BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

Taisuke B-PER
Boku E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tsukuba E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Andrew B-PER
A. I-PER
Chien E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chicago E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Jack B-PER
Dongarra E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tennessee E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Guangrong B-PER
Gao E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Per O
Stenström B-PER
Chalmers E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

Mateo B-PER
Valero E-PER
, O
Barcelona B-ORG
Supercomputing I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Xianghui B-ORG
Xie E-ORG
, O
Jiangnan B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Computing I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Zhiwei B-PER
Xu E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Weimin B-PER
Zheng E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

Xiaochuan B-PER
Cai E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
Boulder E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Zizhong S-PER
( O
Jeffrey B-PER
) I-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yiran B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
Duke B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Toni B-PER
Cortes E-PER
, O
Barcelona B-ORG
Supercomputing I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
Spain S-LOC

Chen B-PER
Ding E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Rochester E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Haohuan B-PER
Fu E-PER
, O
National B-ORG
Supercomputing I-ORG
Center E-ORG
in I-ROLE
Wuxi S-LOC
, O
China S-LOC

Minyi B-PER
Guo E-PER
, O
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Xubin B-PER
He E-PER
, O
Temple B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Torsten B-PER
Hoefler E-PER
, O
ETH B-LOC
Zürich E-LOC
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

Hong B-PER
Jiang E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Arlington S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

Keqin B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Tao B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yun B-PER
Liang E-PER
, O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Naoya B-PER
Maruyama E-PER
, O
RIKEN B-ORG
Advanced I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
for I-ORG
Computational I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Lawrence B-PER
Racuchwerger E-PER
, O
Texas B-ORG
A I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
M I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Jiwu B-PER
Shu E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Xianhe B-ORG
Sun E-ORG
, O
Illinois B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Chao B-PER
Yang E-PER
, O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Pen-Chung B-PER
Yew E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Minnesota E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yunquan B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O

Salim B-PER
Hariri E-PER

Electrical O
& O
amp O
; O
Computer B-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
Dept O
. O
, O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Arizona E-ORG
, O
Tucson S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

<b> O
Haider B-PER
Abbas E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
Technology O
( O
NUST O
) O
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Youssif B-PER
Al-Nashif E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Arizona E-ORG
</i> O
<b> O
; O
</b> O
<b> O
Mark B-PER
Baker E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
The O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Reading E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<b> O
S O
. O
Balamurugan O
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Quants O
IS O
& O
amp O
; O
Consultancy O
Services O
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Ioana B-PER
Banicescu E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Mississippi B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Adam B-PER
Barker E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
St I-ORG
Andrews E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Arindam B-PER
Biswas E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Kazi B-ORG
Nazrul I-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Ali B-PER
R. I-PER
Butt E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Virginia B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<i> O
</i> O
<b> O
Franck B-PER
Cappello E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
INRIA O
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Abhishek B-PER
Chandra E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
</i> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Minnesota E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Kim-Kwang B-PER
Raymond I-PER
Choo E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
South I-ORG
Australia E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Jeffrey B-PER
J I-PER
Evans E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Purdue B-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Gilles B-PER
Fedak E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
INRIA O
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Marco B-PER
Guazzone E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Piemonte I-ORG
Orientale E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Bin O
Hu O
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Birmingham B-ORG
City I-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Atta B-PER
ur I-PER
Rehman I-PER
Khan E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
King B-ORG
Saud I-ORG
University E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Mohammad B-PER
S I-PER
Khan E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
East B-ORG
Tennessee I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Samee B-PER
Ullah I-PER
Khan E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
North B-ORG
Dakota I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Thilo B-PER
Kielmann E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Vrije O
Universiteit O
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Yoonhee B-PER
Kim E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Sookmyung B-ORG
Women I-ORG
's I-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<i> O
</i> O
<b> O
Tevfik B-PER
Kosar E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
<b> O
, O
</b> O
SUNY B-ORG
University E-ORG
at O
Buffalo S-LOC
<b> O
; O
</b> O
</i> O
<b> O
Naoya B-PER
Maruyama E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
RIKEN O
Advanced O
Institute O
for O
Computational O
Science O
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Gabriele B-PER
Mencagli E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pisa E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Manish O
</b> O
<b> O
Parashar S-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Rutgers B-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Jin B-PER
H. I-PER
Park E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
California B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Fresno S-LOC
; O
</i> O
<b> O
Jean-Marc B-PER
Pierson E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Institut B-ORG
de I-ORG
Recherche I-ORG
en I-ORG
Informatique I-ORG
de I-ORG
Toulouse E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Ioan B-PER
Raicu E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Illinois B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Matei B-PER
Ripeanu E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
British I-ORG
Columbia E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Ivan B-PER
Rodero E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Rutgers B-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Sherif B-PER
Sakr E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Mohammad B-PER
Shojafar E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
University O
</i> O
<i> O
of O
Rome O
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Alireza B-PER
Souri E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Islamic B-ORG
Azad I-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Vaidy B-PER
Sunderam E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
Emory B-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Haluk B-PER
Topcuoglu E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Marmara B-ORG
University E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Athanasios B-PER
Vasilakos E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Macedonia E-ORG
; O
</i> O
<i> O
</i> O
<b> O
Lizhe B-PER
Wang E-PER
</b> O
<i> O
, O
</i> O
<i> O
Earth O
Observation O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science E-ORG
</i> O
; O
<b> O
Rui B-PER
Zhang E-PER
</b> O
, O
<i> O
IBM O
Research O
- O
Almaden O
</i> O
; O
<i> O
</i> O
<b> O
Yeliang B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
</b> O
<i> O
Google B-ORG
Inc E-ORG
. O

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE
: O

Zhiwen B-PER
Yu E-PER
, O
Northwestern B-ORG
Polytechnical I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Anind B-PER
Dey E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Washington E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Advisory BI-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

Diane B-PER
Cook E-PER
, O
Washington B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Guozhong B-PER
Dai E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Yuanchun B-PER
Shi E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Steven B-PER
Yau E-PER
, O
Arizona B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Zhaohui B-PER
Wu E-PER
, O
Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Shumin B-PER
Zhai E-PER
, O
Google S-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE
: O

Christian B-PER
Becker E-PER
, O
Mannheim B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Andrew B-PER
Campbell E-PER
, O
Dartmouth B-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

John B-PER
Canny E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California I-ORG
Berkeley E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Guanling B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Massachusetts I-ORG
Lowell E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Liming B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
De B-ORG
Montfort I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

Yiqiang B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Tanzeem B-PER
Choudhury E-PER
, O
Cornell B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Henry B-PER
Duh E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tasmania E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Raghu B-PER
Ganti E-PER
, O
IBM B-ORG
T I-ORG
. I-ORG
J. I-ORG
Watson I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Ning B-PER
Gu E-PER
, O
Fudan B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Tao B-PER
Gu E-PER
, O
RMIT B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Minyi B-PER
Guo E-PER
, O
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Qi B-PER
Han E-PER
, O
Colorado B-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Mines E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Sumi B-PER
Helal E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Mohammad B-PER
Anwar I-PER
Hossain E-PER
, O
King O
Saud B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia E-LOC

Elaine B-PER
Huang E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich E-ORG
, O
Switzerland S-LOC

Jadwiga B-PER
Indulska E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Queensland E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

James B-PER
Landay E-PER
, O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Ying B-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
Cardiff B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Artur B-PER
Lugmayr E-PER
, O
Curtin B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Qin B-ORG
Lv E-ORG
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
Boulder E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Jianhua B-PER
Ma E-PER
, O
Hosei B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Gang B-ORG
Pan E-ORG
, O
Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Shwetak B-PER
Patel E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Washington E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Kui B-PER
Ren E-PER
, O
State B-ORG
Univesity I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Buffalo E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Xiangshi B-ORG
Ren E-ORG
, O
Kochi B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Daniele B-PER
Riboni E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cagliari E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Francesco B-PER
Ricci E-PER
, O
Free B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bozen-Bolzano E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Frank B-PER
Ritter E-PER
, O
Pennsylvania B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Frode B-PER
Eika I-PER
Sandnes E-PER
, O
Oslo B-ORG
University I-ORG
College E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

Gregor B-PER
Schiele E-PER
, O
University O
Duisburg-Essen S-LOC
, O
Germany S-LOC

Feng B-PER
Tian E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Guoping B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jingtao B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Pittsburg B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yongtian B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Beijing B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Xing B-ORG
Xie E-ORG
, O
Microsoft B-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Laurence B-PER
T. I-PER
Yang E-PER
, O
St B-ORG
Francis I-ORG
Xavier I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Chun B-PER
Yu E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Daqing B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Peking B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jingyu B-PER
Zhang E-PER
, O
Chinese B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Xiaolong S-PER
( O
Luke S-PER
) O
Zhang S-PER
, O
Pennsylvania B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Editors-in-Chief ROLE

<b> O
Oliver B-PER
Carsten E-PER

36-40 O
University B-ORG
Road E-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leeds E-ORG

Leeds S-ORG
LS2 O

United B-LOC
Kingdom E-LOC

<b> O
Frédéric B-PER
Vanderhaegen E-PER

Univ. B-ORG
Polytechnique I-ORG
Hauts-de-France E-ORG

Le B-ORG
mont I-ORG
Houy E-ORG

59313 O
Valenciennes S-ORG
, O
Cedex S-ORG

France S-LOC


<b> O
P O
. O
Carlo B-PER
Cacciabue E-PER

</b> O
Kingston B-ORG
University I-ORG
London E-ORG

Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
& I-ORG
amp I-ORG
; I-ORG
Aircraft I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG

London S-LOC
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Erik B-PER
Hollnagel E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG

Center B-ORG
for I-ORG
Quality I-ORG
, I-ORG
Region I-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

Henning B-PER
Boje I-PER
Andersen E-PER
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Martin B-PER
Baumann E-PER
, O
Ulm B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Klaus B-PER
Bengler E-PER
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Munich E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Christine B-PER
Chauvin E-PER
, O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Bretagne I-ORG
Sud E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Sidney B-PER
Dekker E-PER
, O
Griffith B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Katzuo B-PER
Furuta E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tokyo E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Don B-PER
Harris E-PER
, O
Coventry B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Toshi B-PER
Inagaki E-PER
, O
University O
of O
Tsukuba S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Kenji B-PER
Itoh E-PER
, O
Tokyo B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Chris B-PER
Johnson E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Glasgow E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Tom B-PER
Kontogiannis E-PER
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Crete E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

Andreas B-PER
Luedtke E-PER
, O
OFFIS S-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Romaric B-PER
Marcilly E-PER
, O
EVALAB S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

Franck B-PER
Mars E-PER
, O
CNRS S-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

Nick B-PER
McDonald E-PER
, O
Trinity B-LOC
College I-LOC
Dublin E-LOC
, O
Ireland S-LOC

Christopher B-PER
P I-PER
Nemeth E-PER
, O
Applied B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Associates E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Penelope B-PER
Sanderson E-PER
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Queensland E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

Jan B-PER
Maarten I-PER
Schraagen E-PER
, O
TNO S-ORG
, O
The B-LOC
Netherlands E-LOC

Sarah B-PER
Sharples E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nottingham E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

David B-PER
Shinar E-PER
, O
Ben-Gurion B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Negev E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

Chia-Wen B-PER
Tsai E-PER
, O
Ming B-ORG
Chuan I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Taiwan S-LOC

Mark B-PER
Vollrath E-PER
, O
Ingenieur S-ORG
- O
und B-PER
Verkehrspsychologie E-PER
, O
Germany S-LOC

Patrick B-PER
Waterson E-PER
, O
Loughborough B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Toshi B-PER
Inagaki E-PER
, O
University O
of O
Tsukuba S-LOC
, O
Japan S-LOC

Tom B-PER
Kontogiannis E-PER
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Crete E-ORG
, O
Greece S-LOC

Christopher B-PER
P I-PER
Nemeth E-PER
, O
Applied B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Associates E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

David B-PER
Shinar E-PER
, O
Ben-Gurion B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Negev E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

Frédéric B-PER
Vanderhaegen E-PER
, O
Univsersiy S-PER
of O
Valenciennes S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

Mark B-PER
Vollrath E-PER
, O
Ingenieur S-ORG
- O
und B-PER
Verkehrspsychologie E-PER
, O
Germany S-LOC

For O
all O
Book B-ROLE
<B-MISC> O
Review BI-ROLE
<E-MISC> O
requests O
, O
please O
contact O
P O
. O
Carlo B-PER
Cacciabue E-PER
at O
carlo.cacciabue O
@ O
gmail.com O

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

K. B-PER
K. I-PER
Ramakrishnan E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
Riverside S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Managing B-ROLE
Editor ROLE
: O

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE
: O

Mohammed B-PER
Atiquzzaman E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oklahoma E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Zhipeng B-PER
Cai E-PER
, O
Georgia B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Jiannong B-PER
Cao E-PER
, O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Guihai B-PER
Chen E-PER
, O
Nanjing B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Xiuzhen S-PER
( O
Susan S-LOC
) O
Cheng S-PER
, O
George B-ORG
Washington I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Yong B-PER
Cui E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jian B-PER
Gong E-PER
, O
Southeast B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Tian B-PER
He E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Minnesota E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Weijia B-PER
Jia E-PER
, O
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Baochun B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toronto E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Dan B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jianzhong B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
Harbin B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jie B-PER
Li E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Tsukuba E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

Jiangchuan B-PER
Liu E-PER
, O
Simon B-PER
Fraser E-PER
University O
, O
Canada S-LOC

Geyong B-PER
Min E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Exeter E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Jianwei B-PER
Niu E-PER
, O
Beihang B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Fengyuan B-PER
Ren E-PER
, O
Lanzhou B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Kui B-PER
Ren E-PER
, O
University O
at O
Buffalo S-LOC
, O
The B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Limin B-ORG
Sun E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG
, O
CAS S-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Dan B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Haining B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Ning B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Surrey E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

Wenye B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
North B-ORG
Carolina I-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Xingwei B-PER
Wang E-PER
, O
Northeast B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Jie B-PER
Wu E-PER
, O
Temple B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Gaogang B-ORG
Xie E-ORG
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computing I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
CAS S-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Mingwei B-PER
Xu E-PER
, O
Tsinghua B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

Lian B-PER
Zhao E-PER
, O
Ryerson B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

Wei B-PER
Zhao E-PER
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Macau E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
<i> O
</i> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O
</i> O

<b> O
Kjeld B-PER
Schmidt E-PER

</b> O
Copenhagen B-ORG
Business I-ORG
School E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Deputy B-ROLE
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
: O
</i> O

<b> O
Myriam B-PER
Lewkowicz E-PER

Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Technologie I-ORG
de I-ORG
Troyes E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
<i> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE
: O
</i> O

<b> O
Mark B-PER
Ackerman E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Claus B-PER
Bossen E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aarhus E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
Luigina B-PER
Ciolfi E-PER
, O
</b> O
Sheffield B-ORG
Hallam I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Gunnar S-PER
</b> O
<b> O
Ellingsen S-PER
, O
</b> O
UiT O
- O
the O
Arctic B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Norway E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

<b> O
Carl O
</b> O
<b> O
Gutwin S-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Saskatchewan E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Claudia-Lavinia B-PER
Ignat E-PER
</b> O
, O
Inria S-LOC
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Charlotte B-PER
P. I-PER
Lee E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Washington E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Wayne B-PER
G. I-PER
Lutters E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maryland E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Leysia B-PER
Palen E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
Boulder E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Mark B-PER
Rouncefield E-PER
</b> O
, O
Lancaster B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Aleksandra B-PER
Sarcevic E-PER
</b> O
, O
Drexel B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Luigina B-PER
Ciolfi E-PER
, O
</b> O
Sheffield B-ORG
Hallam I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC


Wil B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Aalst E-PER
, O
</b> O
RWTH B-ORG
Aachen I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Liam B-PER
Bannon E-PER
, O
</b> O
LERO O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Limerick E-ORG
, O
Ireland S-LOC

<b> O
Jakob B-PER
E. I-PER
Bardram E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
Pernille B-PER
Bjørn E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Copenhagen E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

Jeanette B-PER
Blomberg E-PER
</b> O
, O
IBM B-ORG
Research E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Susanne B-PER
Bødker E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aarhus E-ORG
, O
Denmark S-LOC

<b> O
Tone B-PER
Bratteteig E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oslo E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

<b> O
Prasun B-PER
Dewan E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
North I-ORG
Carolina E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Geraldine B-PER
Fitzpatrick E-PER
, O
</b> O
TU B-PER
Wien E-PER
( O
Vienna B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
) O
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Saul B-PER
Greenberg E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Calgary E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Tom B-PER
Gross E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bamberg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

Christine B-PER
Halverson E-PER
, O
</b> O
Nine B-ORG
Dot I-ORG
Designs E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Richard B-PER
Harper E-PER
, O
</b> O
Lancaster B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Mark B-PER
Hartswood E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Christian B-PER
Heath E-PER
, O
</b> O
King B-ORG
's I-ORG
College I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Pamela B-PER
Hinds E-PER
, O
</b> O
Stanford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

Eva B-ORG
Hornecker E-ORG
, O
</b> O
Bauhaus-Universität B-ORG
Weimar E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Marina B-PER
Jirotka E-PER
</b> O
, O
Oxford B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Helena B-PER
Karasti E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oulu E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
John B-PER
Leslie I-PER
King E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Mark B-PER
Klein E-PER
, O
</b> O
Massachusetts B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Timothy B-PER
Koschmann E-PER
, O
</b> O
Southern B-ORG
Illinois I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Kari S-PER
</b> O
<b> O
Kuutti S-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oulu E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Cliff B-PER
Lampe E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Stephan B-PER
G. I-PER
Lukosch E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Canterbury E-ORG
, O
New B-LOC
Zealand E-LOC

<b> O
Maria B-PER
Normark E-PER
</b> O
, O
Södertörn B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

Volkmar B-PER
Pipek E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Siegen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Dave B-PER
Randall E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Siegen E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Madhu B-PER
Reddy E-PER
</b> O
, O
Northwestern B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Ribes E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Washington E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Toni B-PER
</<E-PER> O
b> O
<b> O
Robertson S-PER
, O
</b> O
Sydney B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Pascal B-PER
Salembier E-PER
, O
</b> O
Université B-ORG
de I-ORG
Technologie I-ORG
de I-ORG
Troyes E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Carla B-PER
Simone E-PER
, O
</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Milano-Bicocca E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Lucy B-PER
Suchman E-PER
, O
</b> O
Lancaster B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Ina B-PER
Wagner E-PER
, O
</b> O
Vienna B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

</div> O

<b> O
<i> O
Editor-in-Chief ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
<i> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE
</i> O

<b> O
Wil B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Aalst E-PER
</b> O
, O
RWTH B-ORG
Aachen E-ORG

<b> O
Farhad B-PER
Arbab E-PER
</b> O
, O
Centrum B-PER
Wiskunde E-PER
& O
amp O
; O
Informatica O
<b> O
( O
</b> O
CWI O
) O
, O
Amsterdam S-LOC

<b> O
Boualem B-PER
Benatallah E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
Sydney S-LOC

<b> O
Radu B-PER
Calinescu E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
York E-ORG

<b> O
Silvia B-PER
Chiusano E-PER
</b> O
, O
Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Torino E-ORG

<b> O
Rogério B-PER
De I-PER
Lemos E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kent E-ORG

<b> O
Shuiguang B-PER
Deng E-PER
</b> O
, O
Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG

<b> O
Marios B-PER
Dikaiakos E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Cyprus E-ORG
, O
Nicosia S-LOC

<b> O
Dimitrios B-PER
Georgakopoulos E-PER
</b> O
, O
Swinburne B-ORG
University I-ORG
Melborne E-ORG

<b> O
M O
. O
Anwar B-PER
Hossain E-PER
</b> O
, O
King B-ORG
Saud I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Riyadh S-LOC

Erwin B-PER
Laure E-PER
</b> O
, O
Royal B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
( O
KTH S-ORG
) O
, O
Stockholm S-LOC

<b> O
Sam B-PER
Malek E-PER
</b> O
, O
George B-ORG
Mason I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Fairfax S-LOC
, O
VA S-LOC

<b> O
Alberto B-PER
Montresor E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Trento E-ORG

<b> O
Ernesto B-PER
Pimentel E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Malaga E-ORG

<b> O
Antonio B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Cortés E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Sevilla E-ORG

<b> O
Michael B-PER
Sheng E-PER
</b> O
, O
Macquarie B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Sydney S-LOC
, O
NSW S-LOC

<b> O
Behrooz B-PER
A. I-PER
Shirazi E-PER
</b> O
, O
Washington B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Pullman S-LOC
, O
WA S-LOC

<b> O
WenZhan B-PER
Song E-PER
</b> O
, O
Georgia B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Atlanta S-LOC
, O
GA S-LOC

<b> O
Javid B-PER
Taheri E-PER
</b> O
, O
Karlstad B-ORG
University E-ORG

<b> O
Christof B-PER
Teuscher E-PER
</b> O
, O
Portland B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
OR S-LOC

<b> O
Subbarayan B-PER
Venkatesan E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas E-ORG
at O
Dallas S-LOC
, O
TX S-LOC

<b> O
Massimo B-PER
Villari E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Messina E-ORG

<b> O
Barbara B-PER
Weber E-PER
</b> O
, O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Denmark E-ORG

<b> O
Mathias B-PER
Weske E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Potsdam E-ORG

<b> O
Jianwei B-PER
Yin E-PER
</b> O
, O
Zhejiang B-ORG
University E-ORG

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
Chief E-ROLE
Editor ROLE
: O

Prof O
S O
V B-PER
Raghavan E-PER

Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Madras E-ORG
, O
Chennai S-LOC
- O
600 O

Former O
Scientific O

Office B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Principal I-ORG
Scientific I-ORG
Advisor E-ORG
, O
Government B-ORG
of I-ORG
India E-ORG

+ O
91 O
44 O
22574359 O
; O
Fax O
: O
+ O
91 O
44 O

Executive B-ROLE
Director O
, O
Society O
for O
Electronic O
Transactions O
& O
amp O
; O
Security O
( O
SETS O

Chennai S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC


Professor O
and O
Former O
Director O
, O
Institute B-ORG
of I-ORG
Mathematical I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG

Chennai S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

Mentor O

Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

Guwahati S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

E-mail O
: O
gb O
@ O

Prof. O
Uday B-PER
B.Desai E-PER

Director O
, O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG

E-mail O
: O
ubdesai O
@ O

Prof. O
P. B-PER
Venkat I-PER
Rangan E-PER


Coimbatore S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Associate BI-ROLE
Editors ROLE
: O

India S-LOC

Prof O
Anand B-PER
Sivasubramanian E-PER

Chief E-ROLE
Scientist O
, O
TCS B-ORG
Innovation I-ORG
Lab E-ORG

Chennai S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC


Professor O
, O
CSE S-ORG
, O
Pennsylvania B-ORG
State I-ORG
University E-ORG

USA S-LOC

Email O
: O
anand.sivasubramaniam O
@ O

Prof. O
Arun B-PER
Agarwal E-PER

Professor O
& O
amp O
; O
Dean S-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Hyderabad E-ORG

Email O
: O
aruncs.2011 O
@ O

Prof. O
Ashok B-PER
Agrawala E-PER

College B-LOC
Park E-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

E-mail O
: O
agrawala O
@ O

Prof. O
Bharat B-PER
Jayaraman E-PER

CS S-ORG
, O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York E-ORG

Buffalo S-LOC
, O
USA S-LOC

E-mail O
: O
bharat O
@ O

Dr. O
SM B-PER
Bhaskar E-PER

Director O
, O
NTRO S-ORG

New B-LOC
Delhi E-LOC
, O
India S-LOC


Joint O
Secretary O
& O
amp O
; O
Scientist O
“ O
G O
” O
, O
Government B-ORG
of I-ORG
India E-ORG

Email O
: O
smb O
@ O

Prof. O
Bimal B-PER
Roy E-PER

Indian B-ORG
Statistical I-ORG
Institute E-ORG

Kolkata S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

E-mail O
: O
bimal O
@ O

Mr. O
Dheemanth B-PER
Nagaraj E-PER

Senior B-ROLE

Intel B-ORG
Technologies E-ORG

Email O
: O
dheemanth.nagaraj O
@ O

Prof. O
V B-PER
Kamakoti E-PER

CSE S-ORG
, O
IIT B-ORG
Madras E-ORG

Chennai S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

Email O
: O
veezhi O
@ O

Mr. O
KM B-PER
Madhusudhan E-PER

SVP B-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O
CTO S-ORG
, O
Mndtree S-ORG

Bangalore S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

Email O
: O
Madhusudhan.KM O
@ O

Mr. O
Manish B-PER
Gupta E-PER

VP B-ORG
& I-ORG
amp E-ORG
; O

Xerox B-ORG
Research I-ORG
Center I-ORG
of I-ORG
India E-ORG

Email O
: O
manish.gupta2 O
@ O

Prof. O
Manoj B-PER
S I-PER
Gaur E-PER

CSE S-ORG
, O
MNIT S-ORG

Jaipur S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

Email O
: O
gaurms O
@ O

Prof. O
Prashant B-PER
R.Nair E-PER

Vice O
Chairman O
, O

Amrita B-ORG
Vishwa I-ORG
Vidyapeetham I-ORG
University E-ORG

Coimbatore S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

Bangalore S-LOC
, O
India S-LOC

Email O
: O
ramesh O
@ O

India S-LOC

Email O
: O
sverma O
@ O

Dr. O
Sriram B-PER
Raghavan E-PER

Professor O
, O
Dept O
of O
Computing O
& O
amp O
; O
Information B-ORG
Systems E-ORG

Email O
: O
sriram.raghavan O
@ O

Principal O
Scientific O
Advisor O
to O
the O
Government B-ORG
of I-ORG
India E-ORG

Mr. O
Kiran B-PER
Karnick E-PER

Former O
President O
, O
NASSCOM S-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

Mr. O
S. B-PER
Mahalingam E-PER

Executive B-ROLE
Director O
and O
Chief E-ROLE
Financial O
Officer O
, O
TCS S-ORG

Former O
President O
, O
Computer B-ORG
Society I-ORG
of I-ORG
India E-ORG

Prof. O
S.V O
. O
Raghavan S-PER

Professor O
, O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Engineering E-ORG

Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Madras E-ORG
, O
Chennai S-ORG
600036 O

Former O
Scientific O
Secretary O
, O
Office O
of O
the O
Principal O
Scientific O
Advisor O
, O
Government B-ORG
of I-ORG
India E-ORG

Mr. O
S. B-PER
Ramadorai E-PER

Advisor O
to O
Prime O
Minister O
on O
Skill B-ORG
Development E-ORG

</div> O

<b> O
Claude B-PER
Carlet E-PER

</b> O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Paris E-ORG
8 O
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Editorial B-ROLE
Board E-ROLE

<b> O
Lilya B-PER
Budaghyan E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bergen E-ORG
, O
Norway S-LOC

<b> O
Cunsheng B-PER
Ding E-PER

<b> O
Guang B-PER
Gong E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Tor B-PER
Helleseth E-PER

<b> O
Iiro B-PER
Honkala E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Turku E-ORG
, O
Finland S-LOC

<b> O
Jonathan B-PER
Jedwab E-PER

Simon B-PER
Fraser E-PER
University O
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Thomas B-PER
Johansson E-PER

Lund B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

<b> O
Navin B-PER
Kashyap E-PER

</b> O
Indian B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Andrew B-PER
Klapper E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kentucky E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Subhamoy B-PER
Maitra E-PER

</b> O
Indian B-ORG
Statistical I-ORG
Institute E-ORG
, O
India S-LOC

<b> O
Wilfried B-PER
Meidl E-PER

Johann B-ORG
Radon I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
for I-ORG
Computational I-ORG
and I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Mathematics E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Sihem B-PER
Mesnager E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Paris E-ORG
8 O
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Alexander B-PER
Pott E-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Magdeburg E-ORG
, O
Germany S-LOC

<b> O
Neil B-PER
Sloane E-PER

China B-ORG
West I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
China S-LOC

<b> O
Xiaohu B-PER
Tang E-PER

<b> O
Arne B-PER
Winterhof E-PER

</b> O
RICAM S-ORG
, O
Austrian B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Austria S-LOC

<b> O
Victor B-PER
Zinoviev E-PER

Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Problems I-ORG
of I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Transmission E-ORG
, O
The O
Russian B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Sciences E-ORG
, O
Russia S-LOC

</div> O

<div O
id O
=" O
editorialboard ROLE
" O
class O
=" O
placeholder O
placeholder-editorialBoard O
u-text-sans-serif O
"> O

<b> O
EDITOR-IN-CHIEF ROLE

Michela B-ORG
Milano E-ORG
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bologna E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

Louis B-PER
Martin I-PER
Rousseau E-PER
</b> O
, O
Polytechnique B-ORG
Montréal E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

</b> O
<b> O
Christian B-PER
Schulte E-PER
</b> O
, O
Royal B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

<b> O
SURVEYS O
EDITOR ROLE

Pascal B-PER
van I-PER
Hentenryck E-PER
</b> O
, O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Michigan E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

ADVISORY BI-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

<b> O
Eugene B-PER
C. I-PER
Freuder E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-LOC
College I-LOC
Cork E-LOC
, O
Ireland S-LOC

<b> O
Martin B-PER
Charles I-PER
Golumbic E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Haifa E-ORG
, O
Israel S-LOC

<b> O
Narendra B-PER
Jussien E-PER
</b> O
, O
École B-ORG
des I-ORG
Mines I-ORG
de I-ORG
Nantes E-ORG
, O
LINA B-PER
CNRS E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Alan B-PER
Mackworth E-PER
</b> O
, O
UBC S-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Gilles B-PER
Pesant E-PER
</b> O
, O
École B-ORG
Polytechnique I-ORG
de I-ORG
Montréal E-ORG

<b> O
Michael B-PER
A. I-PER
Trick E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carnegie B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Peter B-PER
van I-PER
Beek E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Waterloo E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

EDITORIAL B-ROLE
BOARD E-ROLE

<b> O
Nicolas B-PER
Beldiceanu E-PER
</b> O
, O
École B-ORG
des I-ORG
mines I-ORG
de I-ORG
Nantes E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Bergman E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Connecticut E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
John B-PER
Chinneck E-PER
</b> O
, O
Carleton B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
David B-PER
Cohen E-PER
</b> O
, O
Royal B-ORG
Holloway I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
London E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Bistra B-PER
Dilkina E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
California E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Alan B-PER
Frisch E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
York E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

<b> O
Maria B-PER
Garcia I-PER
De I-PER
La I-PER
Banda E-PER
</b> O
, O
Monash B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Ian B-PER
Gent E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
St. B-LOC
Andrews E-LOC
, O
Scotland S-LOC

<b> O
Christophe B-PER
Lecoutre E-PER
</b> O
, O
Université B-PER
d'Artois E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Laurent B-PER
Michel E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Connecticut E-ORG
, O
USA S-LOC

<b> O
Francesca B-PER
Rossi E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Padova E-ORG
, O
Italy S-LOC

<b> O
Louis-Martin B-PER
Rousseau E-PER
</b> O
, O
Polytechnique B-ORG
Montréal E-ORG
, O
Canada S-LOC

<b> O
Thomas B-PER
Schiex E-PER
</b> O
, O
INRA B-ORG
Toulouse E-ORG
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Christian B-PER
Schulte E-PER
</b> O
, O
Royal B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology E-ORG
, O
Sweden S-LOC

<b> O
Helmut B-PER
Simonis E-PER
</b> O
, O
Cork O
Constraint O
Computation O
Centre O
, O
Ireland S-LOC

<b> O
Christine B-PER
Solnon E-PER
</b> O
, O
INSA B-PER
de I-PER
Lyon E-PER
, O
France S-LOC

<b> O
Peter B-PER
Stuckey E-PER
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Melbourne E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Toby B-PER
Walsh E-PER
</b> O
, O
NICTA S-ORG
and O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
South I-ORG
Wales E-ORG
, O
Australia S-LOC

<b> O
Makoto B-PER
Yokoo E-PER
</b> O
, O
Kyushu B-ORG
University E-ORG
, O
Japan S-LOC

<b> O
Standa O
</b> O
<b> O
Živný O
</b> O
, O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford E-ORG
, O
UK S-LOC

MEDIA B-ORG
EDITOR ROLE

<b> O
Pierre B-PER
Schaus E-PER
</b> O
, O
Université B-ORG
Catolique I-ORG
de I-ORG
Louvain E-ORG
, O
Belgium S-LOC
